[
  {
    "text": "James Jordan, a junior quality assurance business affiliated with Vishal Fabricators, Email: creidrun@emirates.net.ae Phone number 1-555-123-3938 Technical skills: scientific group mtd, psychiatric assessment.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        16,
        49,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        66,
        84,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        93,
        117,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        131,
        145,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        164,
        184,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        186,
        208,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Court Mary (architect sr at Chiyoda Corporation) Reach at maher@domoferm.ae Call 159-753-3516 They specialize in dsn dentalexec.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        24,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        26,
        38,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        42,
        61,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        72,
        89,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        95,
        107,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        127,
        141,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Salini Impregilo employs Anderson Aiden Charles as a jr developer. email contactus.me@hsbc.com Phone number 321-654-5040 Skills: dynamic energy medact, lakes environmental iscaermod view, qtracs.",
    "entities": [
      [
        25,
        47,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        53,
        65,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        16,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        73,
        94,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        108,
        120,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        129,
        150,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        152,
        186,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        188,
        194,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Manser Laura (senior machine learning scientist at INDIA TODAY GROUP) email kitchen@alboom.ae Phone number 159-753-3421 They specialize in unique identification uid databases, food service positive id, reyburn cybertuner.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        26,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        28,
        61,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        65,
        82,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        90,
        107,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        121,
        133,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        153,
        188,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        190,
        214,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        216,
        234,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Gufic Biosciences employs Price Thomas as a enterprise. Email: thomas.chinnu@gmail.com Call 159-753-5150 Skills: creek goldneseal architect.",
    "entities": [
      [
        26,
        38,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        44,
        54,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        17,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        63,
        86,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        92,
        104,
        "PHONE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Mcguire Ewan is a seasoned user experience working at Disney. Reach at ibitar@emirates.net .ae Experienced in cehf.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        27,
        42,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        54,
        60,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        71,
        94,
        "EMAIL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Simmonds Marshall employs Lewis Chris as a perception integration. email shahla@emirates.net.ae Phone: 159-753-4434 Skills: shipping, drawing.",
    "entities": [
      [
        26,
        37,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        43,
        65,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        17,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        73,
        95,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        103,
        115,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        124,
        132,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        134,
        141,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Williams Nathan is a seasoned healthcare working at The Fern An Ecotel Hotel. No contact provided. Experienced in elite spipe, gift registry, sumtotal totallms.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        15,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        30,
        40,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        52,
        76,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        114,
        125,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        127,
        140,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        142,
        159,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Jarvis Nicole, a guidewire business from Alpha Maier, Tel: 1-555-123-5602 Key expertise: sun nuclear mapcheck, jdbc, medez behavioral healthcare substance abuse.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        21,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        25,
        43,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        49,
        60,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        67,
        81,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        97,
        117,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        119,
        123,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        125,
        168,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Frontline NCR Business S employs Sophia Kew-Moss Rene as a servicenow solutions developer. email zikrilla@list.ru Tel: 987-654-4700 Skills: github, ib sservices tour partner.",
    "entities": [
      [
        33,
        53,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        59,
        89,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        24,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        97,
        113,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        119,
        131,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        140,
        146,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Joseph Poppy currently works as a management program at Som Projects (SPL). Email at ajay@ajbc.com Call 321-654-8849 Core skills include sweetware smallpics, lemkesoft graphicconverter.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        34,
        52,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        56,
        74,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        85,
        98,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        104,
        116,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        137,
        156,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        158,
        184,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Smith Fred currently works as a program at Interface Microsystems. email shabeer@gmail.com Core skills include finite element method fme.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        10,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        32,
        39,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        43,
        65,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        73,
        90,
        "EMAIL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Василева Милена, a business intelligence from Ginger Webs, No contact provided. Key expertise: horizon blood bank.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        23,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        27,
        48,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        54,
        65,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        103,
        121,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Parsons International employs Christian Tracey as a ccbd techology. Email at ssveta@aptecme.com Tel: 987-654-2430 Skills: panitbrush, hp dataprotector, geocomp geocalc.",
    "entities": [
      [
        30,
        46,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        52,
        66,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        21,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        77,
        95,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        101,
        113,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        134,
        150,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        152,
        167,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Gohil Kuldeepsinh - integration architect @ SoftwareONE. Call 987-654-4376 Proficient in exe, ect international raceway multipack, motif myemr.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        22,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        25,
        46,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        49,
        60,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        67,
        79,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        94,
        97,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        99,
        134,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        136,
        147,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Hesketh Kezia - bis @ Vistaar Finance. Email: cheri123@eim.ae Phone number 321-654-3910 Proficient in edimis anesthesia, vue benefits.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        18,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        21,
        24,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        27,
        42,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        51,
        66,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        80,
        92,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        107,
        124,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        126,
        138,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Holmes Richard, a community administrator affiliated with Sadbhav Engineering, Tel: 987-654-2589 Technical skills: fyi dr ceph, gait, erdas er mapper.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        14,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        18,
        41,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        58,
        77,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        84,
        96,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        115,
        126,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        128,
        132,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        134,
        149,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Agić Mido currently works as a business analystmdm at Signature Science. Reach at banah.mustafa@gmail.com Call 1-555-123-2468 Core skills include edible, smoke control ascos.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        9,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        31,
        50,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        54,
        71,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        82,
        105,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        111,
        125,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        146,
        152,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        154,
        173,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Davis Benn, a information developer from Gujarat Industries Power, Email at unniraja@gmail.com Key expertise: expression dna protein sequence, blackobard wimba, geriatric depression scale.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        18,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        22,
        43,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        49,
        73,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        84,
        102,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        118,
        149,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        169,
        195,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Mcdermott Michael - operations administrative assistant @ BAE Systems. email mahmoodn@emirates.net.ae Tel: 987-654-3875 Proficient in gnu image manipulatio nprogram gimp, mir intelligent notification.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        22,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        25,
        60,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        63,
        74,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        82,
        106,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        112,
        124,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        176,
        204,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Challinor Georgina - business operations @ MXC Solutions India. Email: a_oribold@gmx.de Phone number 321-654-9054 Proficient in postal explorer.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        23,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        26,
        45,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        48,
        67,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        76,
        92,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        106,
        118,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        133,
        148,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Sokołek Piotr (life time work at Jmc) Reach at ashrafmahate@uowdubai.ac.ae Phone number 1-555-123-4977 They specialize in petz enterprises vtax, mvs, hardwareintheloop simulation.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        27,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        29,
        43,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        47,
        50,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        61,
        88,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        102,
        116,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        136,
        157,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        159,
        162,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        164,
        192,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Floors Doors, a secondary marketing analytics affiliated with Eskag Sanjeevani, Reach at manishjw@emirates.net.ae Phone number 987-654-4385 Technical skills: digital imaging.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        16,
        45,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        62,
        78,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        89,
        113,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        127,
        139,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        158,
        173,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Dnallaoj Elisabeth is a seasoned senior azure working at Mayfair Hotels & Resorts. Email: rrobispo@belbadi.co.ae Experienced in yieldwerx.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        18,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        33,
        45,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        57,
        81,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        90,
        112,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        128,
        137,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Parekh Henil, a quality tester affiliated with Wolters Kluwer, Reach at moopensaweer@drmoopensgroup.com Technical skills: electronic simaging efi monarch, cloveretl, officemate examwriter.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        16,
        30,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        47,
        61,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        72,
        103,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        155,
        164,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        166,
        187,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Movius Interactive Corporation employs Willighan Kayleigh-Jill as a game. email pastry.rcdubai@ritzcarlton.com Phone number 159-753-2463 Skills: careone careensure, nortonlifelock cybersecurity, internet browser.",
    "entities": [
      [
        39,
        62,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        68,
        72,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        30,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        80,
        110,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        124,
        136,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        145,
        163,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        165,
        193,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        195,
        211,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Hawkins Kieran, a business utility domain from Henkel, Call 159-753-4434 Key expertise: thomson reuters gofileroom.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        22,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        26,
        49,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        55,
        61,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        68,
        80,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        96,
        122,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Garside Mark - engineering intern @ Zicom Electronic Securit. Call 1-555-123-1742 Proficient in chemsw chemical inevntory cis, hsim, refugee.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        17,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        20,
        38,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        41,
        65,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        72,
        86,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        132,
        136,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        138,
        145,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Fearn Lauren, a rpa developer from Aspire Systems, Reach at yasir@promate.net Phone number 987-654-1056 Key expertise: fault tree fta, mailchimp.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        20,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        24,
        37,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        43,
        57,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        68,
        85,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        99,
        111,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        127,
        141,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        143,
        152,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Heacock Adrian - payments compliance analytics @ SICK. email ugce@emirates.net.ae Phone number 987-654-7498 Proficient in esignature, ag underwriting solution, collabroative supply execution.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        19,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        22,
        51,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        54,
        58,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        66,
        86,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        100,
        112,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        127,
        137,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        139,
        163,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Vasava Shailesh, a gm carline specialist from Mahindra Agri Solutions, Email: hr@tomouh.ae Phone number 987-654-4144 Key expertise: casemap, benefitfocus hr touch, conest bidtrac.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        23,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        27,
        48,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        54,
        77,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        86,
        98,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        112,
        124,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        140,
        147,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        149,
        170,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        172,
        186,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Seven Seas Hotel employs Vaswani Suresh as a designer. Phone number 987-654-7868 Skills: icims, egs featurecam.",
    "entities": [
      [
        25,
        39,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        45,
        53,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        16,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        68,
        80,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        89,
        94,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        96,
        110,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Johnson Nigel currently works as a live events producer at Apsara Silks. Email: issam@advance-mn.com Tel: 159-753-6980 Core skills include quadkey hrs erver, ihs kingodm, arts letters express.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        13,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        35,
        55,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        59,
        71,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        80,
        100,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        106,
        118,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        171,
        191,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Baxter Linda - solutions multiple levels @ Manthan. Call 159-753-1731 Proficient in metalcam fikus visualcam, windows preinstallation environment, work record.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        17,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        20,
        45,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        48,
        55,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        62,
        74,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        89,
        113,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        115,
        150,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        152,
        163,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Jones-Bailie Kelly - entry level full stack web developer @ Max Fashion. Phone: 1-555-123-2481 Proficient in labeli nspection, scientific group dd, darwin.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        23,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        26,
        62,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        65,
        76,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        85,
        99,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        132,
        151,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        153,
        159,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Day Ryan, a instructor affiliated with JLL, Call 321-654-2425 Technical skills: atx total tax office, xyleme learning content lcms.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        8,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        12,
        22,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        39,
        42,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        49,
        61,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        80,
        100,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        102,
        130,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Johnson Nigel - product safety @ EASTMAN EXPORTS GLOBAL C. Email at yadav.sudhanshu@gmail.com Proficient in winestimator winest.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        18,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        21,
        35,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        38,
        62,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        73,
        98,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        113,
        132,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Ryan Jane, a maria goeppert mayer fellowship from Nutek, Email: taleb@invest-bank.com Call 987-654-3875 Key expertise: computer aided dispatch, effexoft, galleyr museum.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        17,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        21,
        52,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        58,
        63,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        72,
        93,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        99,
        111,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        127,
        150,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        152,
        160,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Baluch Fatima (movidius deep learning scientist at Prolific Systems & Techn) Reach at ronysb@gmail.com They specialize in kmv famas.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        27,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        29,
        61,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        65,
        89,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        100,
        116,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        136,
        145,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Gardner Richard, a assistant chief bldg affiliated with Harsco, Reach at aali@introplan.com Call 1-555-123-7568 Technical skills: cura cura compliance, thomson scientific dailog, photonics apss.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        15,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        19,
        39,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        56,
        62,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        73,
        91,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        97,
        111,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        130,
        150,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        179,
        193,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Localcube Commerce employs Renard Michele as a offsite technical producer. email mkhan@innokat.com Tel: 321-654-5944 Skills: scientific group oilvol, retail.",
    "entities": [
      [
        27,
        41,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        47,
        73,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        18,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        81,
        98,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        104,
        116,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        125,
        148,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        150,
        156,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Noonan Calissa (director product management at Weatherford) email mark.mitcheson-low@woodsbagot.com.au They specialize in classification web, electronic transcription, automated timekeeping.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        28,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        30,
        57,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        61,
        72,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        80,
        116,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        136,
        154,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        156,
        180,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        182,
        203,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Bower Sarah - equipment @ Sgs Tekniks Manufacturin. Reach at woodtj@emirates.net.ae Tel: 987-654-5961 Proficient in sugarcrm sugar ux.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        16,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        19,
        28,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        31,
        55,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        66,
        88,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        94,
        106,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        121,
        138,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Myatt Lucy is a seasoned customer success architect working at Vikram Hospital. Reach at chris.gardner@xclusive.ae Call 987-654-8179 Experienced in pentagon sql.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        10,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        25,
        51,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        63,
        78,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        89,
        114,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        120,
        132,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        148,
        160,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Milburn Lewis currently works as a process at HealthifyMe. Reach at hr@EUROPCAR-UAE.COM Phone: 321-654-7044 Core skills include health writepad ehr.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        13,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        35,
        42,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        46,
        57,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        68,
        87,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        95,
        107,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        128,
        147,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Munns Hakeem currently works as a build at Statestreet HCL Services. Email: aldharis@emirates.net.ae Phone number 1-555-123-2404 Core skills include pepid esm.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        34,
        39,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        43,
        67,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        76,
        100,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        114,
        128,
        "PHONE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Larkowsky Katailyn, a gaming expert affiliated with Udaan, email nmilani@scadia.ae Tel: 321-654-8159 Technical skills: mergerstat control premiums, stewart computational chemistry mopac.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        18,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        22,
        35,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        52,
        57,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        65,
        82,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        88,
        100,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        119,
        146,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        148,
        185,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Hawkins Kieran is a seasoned microservice developer working at Visa. No contact provided. Experienced in online registration.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        14,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        29,
        51,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        63,
        67,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        105,
        124,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Baines Jordan (security intelligence at Techavera Solutions) Email at highmoon@emirates.net.ae Tel: 987-654-2551 They specialize in vero egdecam, propay payment processing.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        27,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        29,
        50,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        54,
        73,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        84,
        108,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        114,
        126,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        160,
        185,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Whitfield Toby (solutions at Fortune Financial Servic) Phone: 987-654-6210 They specialize in tenant file.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        28,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        30,
        39,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        43,
        67,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        76,
        88,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        108,
        119,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Chilis Grill & Bar employs Whitfield Jodie as a applied scientist. email npage@fusion-mgt.com Phone: 159-753-7688 Skills: emds topsem coder, wisconsin physicians service insurance cms secure net access portal csnap.",
    "entities": [
      [
        27,
        42,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        48,
        65,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        18,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        73,
        93,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        101,
        113,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        122,
        139,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        141,
        214,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Sandle New Chloe currently works as a management consultant at Vectus Industries. Tel: 321-654-6053 Core skills include intac international wintac, psychntoesemr, mergerstat price earnings ratios.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        16,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        38,
        59,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        63,
        80,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        87,
        99,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        120,
        146,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        163,
        195,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Mills Helen - loss control consultant @ Optimal Transnational. Reach at nrdoshi@eim.ae Phone: 159-753-6980 Proficient in healthvision tdsynergy lis, applied flow technology aft fathom, xquery.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        16,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        19,
        42,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        45,
        66,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        77,
        91,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        99,
        111,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        126,
        152,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        154,
        188,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        190,
        196,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Manpower employs Horrocks Ashley Hernandez as a enterprise analytics bi project. Email: qatar@projacstraining.com Tel: 987-654-6651 Skills: isnpection selection iss, strategy.",
    "entities": [
      [
        17,
        42,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        48,
        79,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        8,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        88,
        113,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        119,
        131,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        166,
        174,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Leach Jonny is a seasoned sql database administrator working at Absolute Insurance Surve. Email at rocmet@rocmet.com Call 1-555-123-2730 Experienced in accuweather galileo.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        11,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        26,
        52,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        64,
        88,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        99,
        116,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        122,
        136,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        152,
        171,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Jones Jo currently works as a regular full at MARK EXHAUST SYSTEMS. Phone number 1-555-123-8775 Core skills include reactor ecxursion release program relap, medical wizards er icu toolbox.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        8,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        30,
        42,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        46,
        66,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        81,
        95,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        157,
        187,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Maharishi Markandeshwar employs Rosu Bogdan as a infrastructure developer. Phone number 987-654-3449 Skills: novovision novopath, jda group assortment planning arthur.",
    "entities": [
      [
        32,
        43,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        49,
        73,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        23,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        88,
        100,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        109,
        128,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        130,
        166,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Bains Rupinder Pal (mysql database administrator at Silaris Informations Pvt) Tel: 321-654-8932 They specialize in mac helpmate.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        32,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        34,
        62,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        66,
        90,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        97,
        109,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        129,
        141,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Thakor Bhailal currently works as a kronos application administrator at ABIS Exports. Email at aljanahi@emirates.net.ae Phone number 987-654-6828 Core skills include travii reservation, octagon startingpoint.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        14,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        36,
        68,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        72,
        84,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        95,
        119,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        133,
        145,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        166,
        184,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        186,
        207,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Fernandez Kev (principal enterprise architect at Vascon Engineers) Email at fatimaqasim@gmail.com Phone: 159-753-2904 They specialize in ascensio teamlab.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        27,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        29,
        59,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        63,
        79,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        90,
        111,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        119,
        131,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        151,
        167,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Ward Chris currently works as a assignment coordinator at NOCIL. Email: hr@oliverwyman.com Tel: 987-654-3875 Core skills include iso netmap claims.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        10,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        32,
        54,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        58,
        63,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        72,
        90,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        96,
        108,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        129,
        146,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Lawrence Jack is a seasoned client intelligence unit working at ValueLabs. Phone number 159-753-8484 Experienced in pt pt rental assistnat, compass municipal services camalot, optiwave optifdtd.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        13,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        28,
        52,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        64,
        73,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        88,
        100,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        140,
        174,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        176,
        193,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Bowman Michelle currently works as a rpa architect at DraftKings. Reach at andreas.schmidt@blueplanet.at Core skills include financila, octtools, maya nastran.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        15,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        37,
        50,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        54,
        64,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        75,
        104,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        136,
        144,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        146,
        158,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Kelsall Aaron, a senior quality tester psjh affiliated with SAI Life Sciences, Tel: 159-753-2847 Technical skills: assisi forest.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        13,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        17,
        43,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        60,
        77,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        84,
        96,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        115,
        128,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Kelsall Aaron - ddc recycling processor @ Parul University. Email at aaj.dsn@gmail.com Tel: 987-654-2970 Proficient in cisco hot standby oruter protocol hsrp, vieux associtaes vflow, bmc recovery rman.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        18,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        21,
        44,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        47,
        63,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        74,
        91,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        97,
        109,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        188,
        205,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Garside Mark currently works as a enterprise cloud architect at KPC Projects. Email at itcgulf@eim.ae Tel: 159-753-1530 Core skills include montgomery investment technology exotics xl.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        34,
        60,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        64,
        76,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        87,
        101,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        107,
        119,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        140,
        183,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Holmes David (python analytics at SQUAD Infotech) Reach at gorshi_abdulrahman@nai.com Phone: 321-654-5525 They specialize in elite fire, tetarhex fractal finance.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        26,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        28,
        44,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        48,
        62,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        73,
        99,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        107,
        119,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        139,
        149,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Cowan Cheryl currently works as a diversity inclusion at Achievers Spot. Email: dubai@goltens.com Core skills include session initiation protocol sip.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        34,
        53,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        57,
        71,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        80,
        97,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        118,
        149,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Rzepnicki Marek, a career consultant hr transformation rewards from Ganga Medical Centre & H, Email at nmibrahim@siffy.com Call 987-654-6425 Key expertise: imanage document, servicenow.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        23,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        27,
        70,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        76,
        100,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        111,
        130,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        136,
        148,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        164,
        180,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        182,
        192,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Findlay Tasha - social media @ Hamdard. Email: b00016742@aus.edu Phone number 1-555-123-2468 Proficient in fountains forestry twodog, thomson reuters filecabinet cs, file serve.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        18,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        21,
        33,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        36,
        43,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        52,
        69,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        83,
        97,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        112,
        137,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        139,
        169,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        171,
        181,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Martin Cathal (director operations at Godrej Appliances) Email: sabeshan@alrostamanigroup.ae Phone: 159-753-5732 They specialize in automate schools ats, thomson gosystem mytaxinfo, antitrojan.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        27,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        29,
        48,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        52,
        69,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        78,
        106,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        114,
        126,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        146,
        166,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        168,
        194,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        196,
        206,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Donofrio Elisha, a senior deep learning research scientist affiliated with Apco Infratech, Email: sathar@alta-travel.ae Tel: 159-753-8635 Technical skills: computer aided design drafting cadd, metricstream compliance, drivings imulators.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        15,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        19,
        58,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        75,
        89,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        98,
        119,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        125,
        137,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        156,
        191,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        193,
        216,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Dearie Annmarie (administrative at Foundation Brake Manufac) Tel: 1-555-123-7504 They specialize in milliman reservepro.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        29,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        31,
        45,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        49,
        73,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        80,
        94,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        114,
        133,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Squires Louis (police crime at Indwell) email saleh@dotsandlines.com Call 321-654-1266 They specialize in internet explorer, aesdirect.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        27,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        29,
        41,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        45,
        52,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        60,
        82,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        88,
        100,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        120,
        137,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        139,
        148,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Joshi Niraj, a client executive from Paycom, Email: pdipierro@fonex.com Phone: 1-555-123-2468 Key expertise: scansoft paperport pro.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        19,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        23,
        39,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        45,
        51,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        60,
        79,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        87,
        101,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        117,
        139,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Challinor Georgina is a seasoned technical solutions consultant working at Transocean. Email: carol.dejesus@bhomes.com Experienced in thomosn reuters endnote, enterprise resource planning erp, cloveretl.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        18,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        33,
        63,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        75,
        85,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        94,
        118,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        159,
        191,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        193,
        202,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Barot Dipak currently works as a public works department at J Mitra And Co. Email at usman.z@habtoorengg.ae Phone number 987-654-3352 Core skills include collier research hypersizer, govern land permits, medforce workflow.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        11,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        33,
        56,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        60,
        74,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        85,
        107,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        121,
        133,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        154,
        181,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        183,
        202,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        204,
        221,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Wylie Toby currently works as a autonomous driving algorithm at MSPL. No contact provided. Core skills include tadpoles.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        10,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        32,
        60,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        64,
        68,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        111,
        119,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Shaw Leanne - lead developer @ Safexpress. Email: netdubai@habtoorhotels.com Phone number 987-654-2589 Proficient in scientific group soil vapor extraction biosve.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        16,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        19,
        33,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        36,
        46,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        55,
        81,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        95,
        107,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        122,
        167,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Ttosh Ssamantha - automation @ TransSys Solutions. Reach at saderat@emirates.net.ae Phone number 1-555-123-7044 Proficient in clustermatic.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        20,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        23,
        33,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        36,
        54,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        65,
        88,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        102,
        116,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        131,
        143,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Bantigue John, a microservices developer affiliated with Jarulss Technology Solut, Email at paramveer.singh@redingtongulf.com Phone: 159-753-1530 Technical skills: nslookup, coding database.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        13,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        17,
        40,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        57,
        81,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        92,
        125,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        133,
        145,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        164,
        172,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        174,
        189,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Goff Dani currently works as a global account at Mobiloitte Technologies. Email: graybonn@emirates.net.ae Tel: 1-555-123-7504 Core skills include enfocus pitstop pro, public access electronic court records pacer.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        9,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        31,
        45,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        49,
        72,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        81,
        105,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        111,
        125,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        146,
        165,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        167,
        211,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Smith Dee (disaster recovery at Citi Financial) Call 1-555-123-8775 They specialize in encoded archival ead, ellucian colleague, client information databases.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        23,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        25,
        42,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        46,
        60,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        67,
        81,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        101,
        121,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        123,
        141,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        143,
        171,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Farrimond Charlotte currently works as a information security intern at Rays Power Experts. Reach at lbcdn@emirates.net.ae Tel: 987-654-8546 Core skills include resolve legislative compliance.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        19,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        41,
        68,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        72,
        90,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        101,
        122,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        128,
        140,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        161,
        191,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Siemens Gamesa Renewable employs Smith Dee as a engineering intern. Email at oscarcuevas@dmmha.ae Phone: 1-555-123-7568 Skills: relaibility.",
    "entities": [
      [
        33,
        42,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        48,
        66,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        24,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        77,
        97,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        105,
        119,
        "PHONE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Morgan Charlotte, a cyber security cdc from CT Group of Institutions, Tel: 159-753-7875 Key expertise: windows mobile, aeroplanner.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        24,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        28,
        46,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        52,
        76,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        83,
        95,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        111,
        125,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        127,
        138,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Kumar Manish (assembler at Urbantree Infrastructure) Reach at iom@heston.net Call 321-654-7813 They specialize in spillman records, gemcom whittle.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        26,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        28,
        37,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        41,
        65,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        76,
        90,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        96,
        108,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        128,
        144,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        146,
        160,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Barcelona Rosalina - scientists @ Brahmani River Pellets. Email: marwan@dheerajeastcoast.com Tel: 987-654-4144 Proficient in idms account ability.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        23,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        26,
        36,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        39,
        61,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        70,
        97,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        103,
        115,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        130,
        150,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Penfold Ric - technical integration producer @ Perfetti Van Melle. email munir03@eim.ae Phone: 159-753-1507 Proficient in chesapeake interlink needles, specialized business keystroke pos, lrn ethics compliance alliance.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        16,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        19,
        49,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        52,
        70,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        78,
        92,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        100,
        112,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        127,
        155,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        157,
        191,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        193,
        223,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Grulyo Roman, a full stack java from Mold, email abbas.moiz.sura@eim.ae Tel: 987-654-8179 Key expertise: ecological risk assessment, text scanning, geosoft dap server.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        20,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        24,
        39,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        45,
        49,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        57,
        79,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        85,
        97,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        113,
        139,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        141,
        154,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        156,
        174,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Grant Jentierose (admin systems at SAAB ENGINEERING) Email: engineer@ashitaconsultants.com Phone number 1-555-123-2404 They specialize in psychology tools eprime, spaguru.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        30,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        32,
        45,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        49,
        65,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        74,
        104,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        118,
        132,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        152,
        175,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        177,
        184,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Mckelvie Briony, a computer technician from Himadri Chemicals & Indu, email patrick.damico@gmx.ch Tel: 1-555-123-2481 Key expertise: wrad group neuroshell trader, iso netmap claims, scientific.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        23,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        27,
        46,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        52,
        76,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        84,
        105,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        111,
        125,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        171,
        188,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        190,
        200,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Maggs Susan currently works as a sales representative at Bank of America Securiti. email walid.saad@eiruae.ae Core skills include american legalnet uscourtforms, adsa dvantage.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        11,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        33,
        53,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        57,
        81,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        89,
        109,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        130,
        160,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Vcare Call Center employs Russell Jay as a developer programs. No contact provided. Skills: charting, folxd.",
    "entities": [
      [
        26,
        37,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        43,
        61,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        17,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        92,
        100,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Dinshaws employs Paxton Abbie as a resource. email hitachisales@kanoo.ae Phone number 159-753-5061 Skills: fluidsurveys.",
    "entities": [
      [
        17,
        29,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        35,
        43,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        8,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        51,
        72,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        86,
        98,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        107,
        119,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Ryan Jane currently works as a process at American AgCredit. Phone: 987-654-9011 Core skills include source code scm, ehs carerevolution, imagej.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        9,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        31,
        38,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        42,
        59,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        68,
        80,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        101,
        116,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        118,
        136,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        138,
        144,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Hatfield Claire, a inventory affiliated with VKC Group, Email at nmusroor@sprint-ae.com Call 987-654-6651 Technical skills: bugzilla, project planning.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        15,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        19,
        28,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        45,
        54,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        65,
        87,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        93,
        105,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        124,
        132,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        134,
        150,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Dawson Paul, a learning experience from Bharat Benz, Email at sulieman@petronile.ae Call 987-654-2589 Key expertise: soil mapping, wilsons computer applications realeasy appraisals, real estate application contract transmission react.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        19,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        23,
        42,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        48,
        59,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        70,
        91,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        97,
        109,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        125,
        137,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        139,
        188,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        190,
        241,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Mckelvie Briony - senior quality assurance @ Indo Count Industries. Reach at zeyad@eim.ae Call 987-654-3875 Proficient in little piano.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        20,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        23,
        47,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        50,
        71,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        82,
        94,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        100,
        112,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        127,
        139,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Ritchie Nathan, a customer service agent affiliated with Brihanmumbai Electric Su, Reach at hasanali@visionexports.ae Call 159-753-4308 Technical skills: envision pet grooming, apache struts.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        14,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        18,
        40,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        57,
        81,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        92,
        117,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        123,
        135,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        154,
        175,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        177,
        190,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Hyslop Donald, a analytics solutions affiliated with CompuCom, Reach at mhammad@afcdfc.ae Tel: 159-753-1011 Technical skills: cdi electronics meds, midwest microsystems cow sense.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        13,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        17,
        36,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        53,
        61,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        72,
        89,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        95,
        107,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        126,
        146,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        148,
        178,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Croke David (scientist ml at Affiliated Computer Serv) Phone number 159-753-4470 They specialize in direct motion computer numerically controlled cnc, magiclogic optimization cubeiq, chemoffice chemd.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        25,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        27,
        39,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        43,
        67,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        82,
        94,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        114,
        163,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        165,
        195,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        197,
        213,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Bradley Adam currently works as a end developer at Bazar India. email osama@apceco.ae Call 321-654-7044 Core skills include insightful corporation confirmit, digital image correlation dic.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        34,
        47,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        51,
        62,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        70,
        85,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        91,
        103,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        124,
        156,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        158,
        187,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "DSM Infocom employs Flockhart Lorraine as a sr quality control. Email: adnani06@eim.ae Tel: 321-654-3290 Skills: simple storage service, encit edermatology electronic health records ehr, ca erwin modeler.",
    "entities": [
      [
        20,
        38,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        44,
        62,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        11,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        71,
        86,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        92,
        104,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        113,
        135,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        187,
        203,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Narnolia Securities employs Goff Dani as a director digital technologies. Reach at moharram@qatar.net.qa Phone: 159-753-7688 Skills: collaborative supply execution.",
    "entities": [
      [
        28,
        37,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        43,
        72,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        19,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        83,
        104,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        112,
        124,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        133,
        163,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Kuczynski Nikki currently works as a director product management at Surya Food & Agro. Tel: 987-654-4700 Core skills include acastat.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        15,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        37,
        64,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        68,
        85,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        92,
        104,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        125,
        132,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Wallace Ian, a customer service agent affiliated with Fedders Lloyd, Email at rghanem@alewan.com Call 987-654-4053 Technical skills: apache hadoop.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        11,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        15,
        37,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        54,
        67,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        78,
        96,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        102,
        114,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        133,
        146,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Rennie Caroline (staten island lead fulfillment associate at Vertex Professional Service LLC) Email at ali@dialanerd.co.uk Tel: 1-555-123-3869 They specialize in american printing house blind talking typer, profilers.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        29,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        31,
        71,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        75,
        106,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        117,
        136,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        142,
        156,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        176,
        219,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        221,
        230,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Diakoumakis Pandelis (programmer at ITC Wills Lifestyle) email najeeb@iridiumils.com Phone number 321-654-2923 They specialize in jenmar internatoinal dlplus, salarycom, american legalnet edockets.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        34,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        36,
        46,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        50,
        69,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        77,
        98,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        112,
        124,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        173,
        182,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        184,
        210,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Dunn Sara, a cloud native application architect affiliated with Federal Bank, Email at ciona@econosto.ae Phone number 987-654-1056 Technical skills: crescendo digiscribexl, national instruments multisim, authorit.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        9,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        13,
        47,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        64,
        76,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        87,
        104,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        118,
        130,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        149,
        171,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        173,
        202,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        204,
        212,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Méndez Angie (post at The New Indian Express) Reach at gurmit.anand@bp.com Phone: 987-654-3449 They specialize in vendor.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        26,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        28,
        32,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        36,
        58,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        69,
        88,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        96,
        108,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        128,
        134,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Wright Lilly currently works as a trainer at Goms Electricals. Email: yka@eim.ae Call 159-753-9006 Core skills include cisco cisoc netflow collection engine, vectorworks machine design.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        34,
        41,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        45,
        61,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        70,
        80,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        86,
        98,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        158,
        184,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Dickson John currently works as a analytics solutions at Edward Rose & Sons. No contact provided. Core skills include flow toolkit fast.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        34,
        53,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        57,
        75,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        118,
        135,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Chivers Ricky, a database administrator affiliated with Medfin India, email euphoria@eim.ae Technical skills: waters empower, peoplesoft enterprise supply planning multisite material planner, antispywrae.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        13,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        17,
        39,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        56,
        68,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        76,
        91,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        110,
        124,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        126,
        190,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Mroczkowski Tomasz is a seasoned sr systems admin working at GUILTFREE INDUSTRIES. email faiza@prismeinternational.com Phone number 321-654-5064 Experienced in quorum pgas.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        18,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        33,
        49,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        61,
        81,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        89,
        118,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        132,
        144,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        160,
        171,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Barclays Global Service employs Whitfield Jodie as a operational. Email at naqvi@emirates.net.ae Skills: diving table.",
    "entities": [
      [
        32,
        47,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        53,
        64,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        23,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        75,
        96,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        105,
        117,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Medlife employs Riggott Jack as a facilities. Reach at igt@emirates.net.ae Phone number 321-654-3007 Skills: distributed database.",
    "entities": [
      [
        16,
        28,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        34,
        44,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        7,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        55,
        74,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        88,
        100,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        109,
        129,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Whitfield Jodie (product support representative at Don Bosco School) No contact provided. They specialize in object database odbms.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        29,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        31,
        61,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        65,
        81,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        123,
        144,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Norman Jenny, a contract administrator from TEXMO INDUSTRIES, Reach at rhaddad@ccc.ae Phone number 321-654-5944 Key expertise: money.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        20,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        24,
        46,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        52,
        68,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        79,
        93,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        107,
        119,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        135,
        140,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Scope International employs Gallagher Kenzie as a best buy computing master. Email at sally.meech@cpdubai.com Tel: 321-654-5064 Skills: cowgame, nvdia gelato, profit developers electronic file interchange.",
    "entities": [
      [
        28,
        44,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        50,
        75,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        19,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        86,
        109,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        115,
        127,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        136,
        143,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        145,
        157,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        159,
        204,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Khan Asif currently works as a senior center virtualization at Yuken India. Reach at lovely@maxim-qatar.com Phone: 1-555-123-2481 Core skills include quick notes pdq podiatry, foresoft model, swivel.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        9,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        31,
        59,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        63,
        74,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        85,
        107,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        115,
        129,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        150,
        174,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        176,
        190,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        192,
        198,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Ahmed Heemy (cloud financials solutions architect at Accenture) Phone number 987-654-2551 They specialize in collier research hypersizer, dose unit aclculation.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        25,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        27,
        63,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        67,
        76,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        91,
        103,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        123,
        150,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Burns Steven (business administrator at Airgas) No contact provided. They specialize in rsac riparian mapping tool, rockware jlog, scansoft naturally speaking.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        26,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        28,
        50,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        54,
        60,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        102,
        128,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        130,
        143,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        145,
        172,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Fearnley Janine currently works as a strategy operations associate at Bernhard Schulte Shipman. Reach at samim@npcc.ae Phone: 321-654-5064 Core skills include fftw, us department agriculture usda national nutrient database, isograph markov.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        15,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        37,
        66,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        70,
        94,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        105,
        118,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        126,
        138,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        159,
        163,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        165,
        222,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        224,
        239,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Ball Sarah currently works as a senior strategist at Ideal Group. Phone number 987-654-7498 Core skills include weatlhtec wealthmaster, applied computer jobpowre, watres masslynx.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        10,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        32,
        49,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        53,
        64,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        79,
        91,
        "PHONE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Sowerby Kev (modeler at Ever Electronics) Call 159-753-6980 They specialize in comchart emr.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        25,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        27,
        34,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        38,
        54,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        61,
        73,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        93,
        105,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Gouveia Joseman - quality food safety @ Shiv Nadar University. email arifm@memon.ae Call 159-753-4201 Proficient in mountainside allergy.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        20,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        23,
        42,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        45,
        66,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        74,
        88,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        94,
        106,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        121,
        141,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Goodricke Group employs Kennedy Jake as a senior qa. Reach at mzoheir@eim.ae Call 1-555-123-5288 Skills: skilltran job browser pro, inscribe.",
    "entities": [
      [
        24,
        36,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        42,
        51,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        15,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        62,
        76,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        82,
        96,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        105,
        130,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        132,
        140,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Howard Micha, a communication change management consultant affiliated with IndusInd Bank, Reach at abujabco@eim.ae Tel: 321-654-9108 Technical skills: mainstage.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        16,
        58,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        75,
        88,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        99,
        114,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        120,
        132,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        151,
        160,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Williams Nathan - director broadcast operations @ Satyam Venture Engineeri. Email: rpdcool@emirtes.net.ae Tel: 159-753-2463 Proficient in act, peoplefluent recruiting.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        20,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        23,
        52,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        55,
        79,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        88,
        110,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        116,
        128,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        143,
        146,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        148,
        171,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "CETPA InfoTech employs Jeney Tamás as a digital solution architect. Tel: 987-654-4144 Skills: quickbooks point sale, chemsw mass spec tools.",
    "entities": [
      [
        23,
        34,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        40,
        66,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        14,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        73,
        85,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        94,
        115,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        117,
        139,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Swallow Wayne - quality control project @ Dhanush InfoTech. email jamilabu@gmail.com Phone number 987-654-9011 Proficient in denemo, tailwind tailwind, database testing.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        18,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        21,
        44,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        47,
        63,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        71,
        89,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        103,
        115,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        130,
        136,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        138,
        155,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        157,
        173,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Mannan Sameen is a seasoned cognos developer working at GGK Technologies. Email: walid@sourceit.ae Call 159-753-8993 Experienced in dh imike urban, predator dnc.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        13,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        28,
        44,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        56,
        72,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        81,
        98,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        104,
        116,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        148,
        160,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Iza Paez Sam is a seasoned junior system administrator working at Kaynes Technology. email pradeep.jena@hiexdubai.ae Phone: 159-753-6636 Experienced in slcak.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        27,
        54,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        66,
        83,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        91,
        116,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        124,
        136,
        "PHONE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Hunt Jason, a assistant director affiliated with ABI SHOWA TECH, Email: condxb@emirates.net.ae Phone: 159-753-9275 Technical skills: business continuity, relavis crm portal.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        10,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        14,
        32,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        49,
        63,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        72,
        94,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        102,
        114,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        133,
        152,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        154,
        172,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Barakat Sultz is a seasoned architecture working at Hindustan Pencils. Phone number 321-654-3365 Experienced in choreography, ls avisual easy lean, gavel gown amicus attorney.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        13,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        28,
        40,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        52,
        69,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        84,
        96,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        112,
        124,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        148,
        174,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Benson Hannah currently works as a wireless network at Government of India. Phone: 321-654-3007 Core skills include production planning.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        13,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        35,
        51,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        55,
        74,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        83,
        95,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        116,
        135,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Hical Technologies employs Rushby Sam as a vendor operations compliance. email hatim@nasrtech.com Skills: speech recognition, aspectbench compiler aspectj.",
    "entities": [
      [
        27,
        37,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        43,
        71,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        18,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        79,
        97,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        106,
        124,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        126,
        154,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "1ne Click Online employs Mcmann Douglas as a operations specialist. Email at js@emirates.net.ae Call 1-555-123-5602 Skills: tidepool scientific comprehensive environmental toxicity information cetis.",
    "entities": [
      [
        25,
        39,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        45,
        66,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        16,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        77,
        95,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        101,
        115,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        124,
        198,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Bank of America employs Patel Anisha as a microservice developer. email maamoun@enhc.ae Phone number 1-555-123-5478 Skills: vector vectorcast, four soft visilog.",
    "entities": [
      [
        24,
        36,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        42,
        64,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        15,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        72,
        87,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        101,
        115,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        124,
        141,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        143,
        160,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Mohsin Pathan (dchs initiatives evaluation at Pearl Beverages) Email: jlobo@globalvillage.ae Tel: 987-654-8179 They specialize in patch update, caice visual transpotration, madison technical enviropak.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        27,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        29,
        56,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        60,
        75,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        84,
        106,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        112,
        124,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        144,
        156,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        187,
        214,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Skelton Jasmine - strategy @ SMEC Automation. Email: fbailly@steelcase_me.com Phone number 987-654-8546 Proficient in telephone records.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        20,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        23,
        31,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        34,
        49,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        58,
        82,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        96,
        108,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        123,
        140,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Agarwal Packers & Movers employs Fearnley Janine as a business operations. email vinod.jacob@eim.ae Phone number 1-555-123-9576 Skills: deb taccount collection, zoller.",
    "entities": [
      [
        33,
        48,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        54,
        73,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        24,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        81,
        99,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        113,
        127,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        161,
        167,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Murphy Wayne currently works as a inventory at MGM Medical College & Ho. Reach at pro@profilesrhf.com Core skills include menu nutrition database, genbank, forterss medical clindex.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        34,
        43,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        47,
        71,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        82,
        101,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        122,
        145,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        147,
        154,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Nethues Technologies employs Parekh Henil as a counter measures. email PR-Communication@qsa.gov.qa Skills: check processing control cpsc.",
    "entities": [
      [
        29,
        41,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        47,
        63,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        20,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        71,
        98,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        107,
        136,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Wolf Dan is a seasoned syep service learning facilitator working at Amber Enterprises India. Email: cdhanak@emirates.net.ae Call 1-555-123-4764 Experienced in fielding labs optomizer, reliability, arianna.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        8,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        23,
        56,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        68,
        91,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        100,
        123,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        129,
        143,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        159,
        182,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        184,
        195,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        197,
        204,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Mariee Roksana - build @ Mfar Constructions. email mahiyar.daruwalla@hmeltd.com Tel: 1-555-123-3589 Proficient in canorus, accounting compliance, human resource microsystems hr entre.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        19,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        22,
        27,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        30,
        48,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        56,
        84,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        90,
        104,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        119,
        126,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        128,
        149,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        151,
        187,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Joshi Niraj is a seasoned standardized patient working at BT E Serv. email financejobs@medcarehospital.com Tel: 159-753-6362 Experienced in prosolutions transcend, sun microsystems sun one, athena penelope case.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        11,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        26,
        46,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        58,
        67,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        75,
        106,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        112,
        124,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        140,
        162,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        164,
        188,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        190,
        210,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Taiganides Francesca currently works as a epm architect at RR Donnelley. Email: naseem@emirates.net.ae Phone number 159-753-8715 Core skills include godl.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        20,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        42,
        55,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        59,
        71,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        80,
        102,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        116,
        128,
        "PHONE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Sorger Jozsef currently works as a inventory control specialist at Carestream Health. Reach at advertise@eim.ae Call 159-753-9275 Core skills include ca erwin modeler, micro focus testpartner, uniform residential loan application.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        13,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        35,
        63,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        67,
        84,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        95,
        111,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        117,
        129,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        150,
        166,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        168,
        191,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        193,
        229,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "EPAM Systems employs Mcguire Conal as a member consultant bellevue. email hassan.myounis@rta.ae Skills: fitnesse, agilent advanced design ads, epocraets.",
    "entities": [
      [
        21,
        34,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        40,
        66,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        12,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        74,
        95,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        104,
        112,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        114,
        141,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Holden Ned (contract administrator at World Health Partners) Email at contact@appointmentsdubai.com Call 159-753-7852 They specialize in logical partition plar, nemetschek vectorworks spotlight, follow code.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        24,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        26,
        48,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        52,
        73,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        84,
        113,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        119,
        131,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        175,
        207,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        209,
        220,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Ghasura Sorat Khan is a seasoned general working at Auma. Reach at ginco@emirates.net.ae Phone: 321-654-1266 Experienced in masters cakeboss, smartcamcnc smartcam.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        18,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        33,
        40,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        52,
        56,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        67,
        88,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        96,
        108,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        124,
        140,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        142,
        162,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Wetoszka David, a frontend affiliated with CMA CGM, Email: office.dubai@atkinsglobal.com Phone number 987-654-3875 Technical skills: topaz symplifi crm feature, dealertrax shoporder, geographic resources support grass.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        14,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        18,
        26,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        43,
        50,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        59,
        88,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        102,
        114,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        133,
        159,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        161,
        181,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        183,
        217,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Yaqoob Ali currently works as a quality at Anmol Feeds. Email: adon@emirates.net.ae Phone number 1-555-123-3589 Core skills include paisley focus control assurance, toothpics, avid pro tools.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        10,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        32,
        39,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        43,
        54,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        63,
        83,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        97,
        111,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        132,
        163,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        165,
        174,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        176,
        190,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Stewart Andy, a asst project affiliated with Satguru Travels and Tour, Tel: 159-753-9275 Technical skills: solidthikning.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        16,
        28,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        45,
        69,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        76,
        88,
        "PHONE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Farwell Mick, a helpdesk from Foodvista India, email pierlite@eim.ae Call 159-753-7708 Key expertise: multigen paradigm vega prime, road geomanager, boss didger.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        20,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        24,
        32,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        38,
        53,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        61,
        76,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        82,
        94,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        110,
        138,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        140,
        155,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        157,
        168,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "LSEG (London Stock Exchange Group) employs Gill Charlie as a mnjis assistant director. Email: mowara@emirates.net.ae Tel: 159-753-4308 Skills: adaptive optics ao simulation.",
    "entities": [
      [
        43,
        55,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        61,
        85,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        34,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        94,
        116,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        122,
        134,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        143,
        172,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Atkin Andy, a director technology centers affiliated with Zuari Cement, email airaqi@richbond.ma Phone number 1-555-123-2730 Technical skills: specsintact, sierras cientific cris.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        10,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        14,
        41,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        58,
        70,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        78,
        96,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        110,
        124,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        143,
        154,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Stockwell Russell is a seasoned industrial working at Al Mulla Group. Reach at info@tceqatar.com.qa Phone number 159-753-6431 Experienced in digital cnotrol dcs, kant.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        17,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        32,
        42,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        54,
        68,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        79,
        99,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        113,
        125,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        162,
        166,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Karvy Data Management Se employs Smith Courtneyy as a client engagement professional. Reach at tim.shields@aig.com Skills: olrac electronic logbook solution, soltarce, detnet viewshot.",
    "entities": [
      [
        33,
        48,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        54,
        84,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        24,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        95,
        114,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        123,
        156,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        168,
        183,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Kelly Kate, a infra architect from Ingersoll Rand, email bhargavan.pillai@dbbcg.com Tel: 987-654-2589 Key expertise: patien tscheduling, bmc remedy service suite.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        18,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        22,
        37,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        43,
        57,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        65,
        91,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        97,
        109,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        145,
        169,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Catello Laura, a fhcu community assistant from Bechtel Enka, Email at tadgulf@emirates.net.ae Phone: 159-753-4470 Key expertise: memscap mems pro, kinesis, wyndgate safetrace.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        21,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        25,
        49,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        55,
        67,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        78,
        101,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        109,
        121,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        137,
        153,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        155,
        162,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        164,
        182,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Meet Byrne Ethan - machine learning big @ Karunya University. No contact provided. Proficient in luntbuild, continuous emissions monitroing cems.",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        16,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        19,
        39,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        42,
        60,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        97,
        106,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Dolan Andrew is a seasoned java developer working at EMRI(108). Email: dubai@royaltonholdings.com Phone: 321-654-3007 Experienced in shape, adaptmodeler, domin enterprise tenant pro.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        12,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        27,
        41,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        53,
        62,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        71,
        97,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        105,
        117,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        133,
        138,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        140,
        152,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        154,
        181,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Kelsall Aaron currently works as a admin systems at Lycatel BPO. email baigs@emirates.net.ae Phone: 1-555-123-3684 Core skills include quest central, teletracking preadmittracking.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        13,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        35,
        48,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        52,
        63,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        71,
        92,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        100,
        114,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        135,
        148,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        150,
        179,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Marr Nathan currently works as a investigator at Toyota Material Handling. Email at bened@emirates.net.ae Core skills include manhattan supply process platform.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        11,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        33,
        45,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        49,
        73,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        84,
        105,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        126,
        159,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "JBM Group employs Masukume Scott as a program administrator. Phone number 321-654-9108 Skills: river lake altimetry product.",
    "entities": [
      [
        18,
        32,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        38,
        59,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        0,
        9,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        74,
        86,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        95,
        123,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Mckendrick Paul is a seasoned developer intern working at Trawex Technologies. Reach at navendu.rai@atkins-dxb.ae Tel: 159-753-8635 Experienced in winsteps, research suite, softrisk softrisk sql.",
    "entities": [
      [
        0,
        15,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        30,
        46,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        58,
        77,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        88,
        113,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        119,
        131,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        147,
        155,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        157,
        171,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        173,
        194,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "Contact Costa Federico, a marketing from Aakash Institute, Email at rahman@bukhatir.ae Phone: 987-654-4996 Key expertise: factsage, coda engine, pemimic patient relations suite.",
    "entities": [
      [
        8,
        22,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        26,
        35,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        41,
        57,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        68,
        86,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        94,
        106,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        122,
        130,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        132,
        143,
        "SKILL"
      ],
      [
        145,
        176,
        "SKILL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": "You can reach Elliott-Low Rebecca (trade business development financial at Western Railway) email bipin@dollarauto.ae Call 159-753-1011 They specialize in landmark geoprobe.",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        33,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        35,
        71,
        "JOB_TITLE"
      ],
      [
        75,
        90,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
