[
    {
        "text": "Emma Doe is a data scientist at Google. Contact: emmadoe@google.org, 987-654-3449. Skills: TensorFlow, Linux, C#, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                28,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                32,
                38,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                49,
                67,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                69,
                81,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                91,
                101,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                108,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "David Davis is a machine learning engineer at Facebook. Contact: david.davis@facebook.com, 987-654-7878. Skills: TensorFlow, Kubernetes, SQL, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                65,
                89,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                91,
                103,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                113,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                135,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                137,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                142,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Olivia Clark is a AI researcher at Google. Contact: olivia_clark@google.net, 987-654-3352. Skills: C#, Python, Java.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                41,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                52,
                75,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                77,
                89,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                99,
                101,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                109,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emily Clark is a cloud architect at Amazon. Contact: emily_clark@amazon.net, +1-555-123-9576. Skills: SQL, Linux, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                42,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                53,
                75,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                77,
                92,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                102,
                105,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Liam Hernandez is a software engineer at Oracle. Contact: liamhernandez@oracle.org, 321-654-1266. Skills: SQL, Java, Agile.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                84,
                96,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                106,
                109,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jane Clark is a cybersecurity analyst at Amazon. Contact: jane.clark@amazon.com, 321-654-9945. Skills: Docker, Kubernetes, Linux.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                79,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                103,
                109,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                128,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael Johnson is a data scientist at Adobe. Contact: michael.johnson@adobe.com, 321-654-4302. Skills: Agile, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                44,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                55,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                82,
                94,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                104,
                109,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                117,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sophia Brown is a AI researcher at Oracle. Contact: sophia_brown@oracle.net, 159-753-5150. Skills: Agile, Scrum.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                41,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                52,
                75,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                77,
                89,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                99,
                104,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sophia Doe is a cybersecurity analyst at Tesla. Contact: sophia.doe@tesla.com, 321-654-8159. Skills: Kubernetes, C#, Java.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                46,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                77,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                79,
                91,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                101,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael Hernandez is a senior software developer at IBM. Contact: michael_hernandez@ibm.net, 321-654-2353. Skills: C#, SQL, TensorFlow, Scrum.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                91,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                93,
                105,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                115,
                117,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                134,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael Lee is a machine learning engineer at IBM. Contact: michael.lee@ibm.com, +1-555-123-6372. Skills: Scrum, TensorFlow, Kubernetes, Linux.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                49,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                79,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                96,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                106,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                135,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                137,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Liam Johnson is a senior software developer at IBM. Contact: liamjohnson@ibm.org, +1-555-123-6776. Skills: C#, Scrum, Python, Kubernetes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                61,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                82,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                107,
                109,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Liam Wilson is a AI researcher at Amazon. Contact: liam.wilson@amazon.com, 987-654-8179. Skills: Docker, SQL.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                34,
                40,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                51,
                73,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                75,
                87,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                97,
                103,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                108,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emily Wilson is a cybersecurity analyst at Oracle. Contact: emily_wilson@oracle.net, +1-555-123-3513. Skills: Kubernetes, Java, Linux, Agile.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                49,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                110,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                126,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                128,
                133,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jane Clark is a project manager at Netflix. Contact: janeclark@netflix.org, 159-753-6150. Skills: Scrum, Agile, SQL, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                42,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                53,
                74,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                76,
                88,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                98,
                103,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael Hernandez is a AI researcher at Oracle. Contact: michael_hernandez@oracle.net, +1-555-123-5288. Skills: Kubernetes, Agile, Scrum.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                46,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                87,
                102,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                112,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Olivia Davis is a data scientist at Amazon. Contact: olivia.davis@amazon.com, 159-753-3828. Skills: Kubernetes, SQL, Java, TensorFlow.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                42,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                53,
                76,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                78,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                100,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                133,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sophia Smith is a AI researcher at Netflix. Contact: sophiasmith@netflix.org, 321-654-3580. Skills: Docker, Java, Agile, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                42,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                53,
                76,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                78,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                100,
                106,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                119,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emily Johnson is a backend developer at Adobe. Contact: emily.johnson@adobe.com, 321-654-7044. Skills: Linux, Docker, SQL.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                45,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                56,
                79,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                103,
                108,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jane Brown is a cloud architect at Adobe. Contact: jane_brown@adobe.net, 159-753-7708. Skills: SQL, Docker, Java, Kubernetes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                40,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                51,
                71,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                73,
                85,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                95,
                98,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                106,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jane Hernandez is a senior software developer at Netflix. Contact: janehernandez@netflix.org, 987-654-3981. Skills: C#, Linux.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                92,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                94,
                106,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                116,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                125,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "John Smith is a AI researcher at Amazon. Contact: johnsmith@amazon.org, 987-654-3653. Skills: Agile, Java, Scrum.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                39,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                50,
                70,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                72,
                84,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                94,
                99,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                101,
                105,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jane Brown is a backend developer at Netflix. Contact: janebrown@netflix.org, 987-654-5961. Skills: Linux, SQL, Docker, Scrum.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                44,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                55,
                76,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                78,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                100,
                105,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                125,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emma Johnson is a project manager at Intel. Contact: emma_johnson@intel.net, 321-654-1674. Skills: SQL, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                42,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                53,
                75,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                77,
                89,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                99,
                102,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emma Brown is a backend developer at Intel. Contact: emmabrown@intel.org, +1-555-123-9159. Skills: Linux, Scrum, TensorFlow, Agile.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                42,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                53,
                72,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                74,
                89,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                99,
                104,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                130,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emily Martinez is a machine learning engineer at Adobe. Contact: emily.martinez@adobe.com, +1-555-123-3589. Skills: C#, Kubernetes, Linux.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                65,
                89,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                91,
                106,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                116,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                130,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                132,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emily Wilson is a DevOps engineer at Amazon. Contact: emilywilson@amazon.org, 321-654-6658. Skills: Docker, Java, SQL.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                43,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                54,
                76,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                78,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                100,
                106,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                117,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sophia Davis is a senior software developer at Facebook. Contact: sophiadavis@facebook.org, 159-753-5061. Skills: SQL, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                90,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                92,
                104,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                114,
                117,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                125,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "David Martinez is a DevOps engineer at Oracle. Contact: david.martinez@oracle.com, 987-654-6364. Skills: Java, Agile, Docker, Linux.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                45,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                56,
                81,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                83,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                105,
                109,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                131,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Daniel Hernandez is a senior software developer at Tesla. Contact: danielhernandez@tesla.org, +1-555-123-2475. Skills: Linux, Kubernetes, Agile.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                92,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                94,
                109,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                119,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                143,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emily Clark is a cybersecurity analyst at Google. Contact: emily.clark@google.com, 321-654-9108. Skills: Kubernetes, Scrum, Python, C#.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                81,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                83,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                105,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                130,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                132,
                134,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jane Martinez is a project manager at Tesla. Contact: jane_martinez@tesla.net, 321-654-7606. Skills: Python, C#, TensorFlow.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                43,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                54,
                77,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                79,
                91,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                101,
                107,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emma Lee is a backend developer at IBM. Contact: emma_lee@ibm.net, 321-654-2204. Skills: Linux, Kubernetes, Scrum.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                38,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                49,
                65,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                67,
                79,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                89,
                94,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                96,
                106,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                113,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emma Clark is a data scientist at Amazon. Contact: emma.clark@amazon.com, 159-753-7114. Skills: Linux, Java, Docker.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                34,
                40,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                51,
                72,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                74,
                86,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                96,
                101,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                107,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emily Clark is a AI researcher at Oracle. Contact: emily_clark@oracle.net, +1-555-123-1742. Skills: Docker, Java.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                34,
                40,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                51,
                73,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                75,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                100,
                106,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Olivia Lee is a senior software developer at Amazon. Contact: olivia_lee@amazon.net, 987-654-6373. Skills: Java, Docker, C#, Scrum.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                107,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                119,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                130,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "David Clark is a cybersecurity analyst at Netflix. Contact: david_clark@netflix.net, 159-753-5911. Skills: Python, Java, Linux.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                49,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                107,
                113,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                119,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                126,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jane Martinez is a DevOps engineer at Tesla. Contact: jane_martinez@tesla.net, +1-555-123-8775. Skills: TensorFlow, Agile, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                43,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                54,
                77,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                79,
                94,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                104,
                114,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emma Hernandez is a project manager at Netflix. Contact: emma_hernandez@netflix.net, 159-753-3421. Skills: Agile, Python, SQL, Kubernetes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                46,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                107,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                125,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "John Hernandez is a cybersecurity analyst at Oracle. Contact: john.hernandez@oracle.com, 159-753-4340. Skills: Linux, Kubernetes, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                87,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                89,
                101,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                111,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                128,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                130,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael Lee is a backend developer at Netflix. Contact: michaellee@netflix.org, 159-753-9609. Skills: Java, Docker, Kubernetes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                45,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                56,
                78,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                80,
                92,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                102,
                106,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                114,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                126,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Daniel Wilson is a AI researcher at IBM. Contact: daniel_wilson@ibm.net, 321-654-8932. Skills: Agile, Scrum.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                39,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                50,
                71,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                73,
                85,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                95,
                100,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                107,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Daniel Brown is a backend developer at Tesla. Contact: danielbrown@tesla.org, 987-654-9011. Skills: Kubernetes, Java, Scrum.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                44,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                55,
                76,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                78,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                100,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "David Smith is a DevOps engineer at Netflix. Contact: davidsmith@netflix.org, 159-753-6654. Skills: Scrum, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                43,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                54,
                76,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                78,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                100,
                105,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                113,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "David Smith is a cybersecurity analyst at Adobe. Contact: david_smith@adobe.net, 321-654-8849. Skills: Agile, Linux.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                79,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                103,
                108,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "David Lee is a machine learning engineer at Amazon. Contact: david.lee@amazon.com, 987-654-4972. Skills: Linux, Agile.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                61,
                81,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                83,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                105,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                117,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emily Doe is a data scientist at Oracle. Contact: emilydoe@oracle.org, 159-753-2647. Skills: Docker, Python, TensorFlow, Agile.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                39,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                50,
                69,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                71,
                83,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                93,
                99,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                101,
                107,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                119,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                126,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Olivia Hernandez is a backend developer at Tesla. Contact: oliviahernandez@tesla.org, 321-654-1969. Skills: TensorFlow, Agile.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                84,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                86,
                98,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                108,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                125,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Daniel Doe is a project manager at Oracle. Contact: daniel.doe@oracle.com, +1-555-123-7504. Skills: Docker, Scrum, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                41,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                52,
                73,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                75,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                100,
                106,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                113,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "John Brown is a DevOps engineer at Intel. Contact: john.brown@intel.com, 321-654-5662. Skills: Linux, TensorFlow, Kubernetes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                40,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                51,
                71,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                73,
                85,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                95,
                100,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael Lee is a senior software developer at Tesla. Contact: michael.lee@tesla.com, +1-555-123-6417. Skills: Kubernetes, Scrum.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                110,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael Doe is a cybersecurity analyst at Tesla. Contact: michael_doe@tesla.net, 987-654-3875. Skills: C#, TensorFlow, Java, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                79,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                103,
                105,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                117,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                131,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Liam Smith is a project manager at Amazon. Contact: liamsmith@amazon.org, 321-654-5064. Skills: Scrum, C#.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                41,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                52,
                72,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                74,
                86,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                96,
                101,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                105,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emily Hernandez is a machine learning engineer at IBM. Contact: emilyhernandez@ibm.org, +1-555-123-5285. Skills: Java, Agile, Python, TensorFlow.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                53,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                64,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                103,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                113,
                117,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                132,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                134,
                144,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jane Hernandez is a machine learning engineer at Amazon. Contact: janehernandez@amazon.org, 321-654-2923. Skills: Scrum, Java, Agile, SQL.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                90,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                92,
                104,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                114,
                119,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                125,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                132,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                134,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael Hernandez is a project manager at Adobe. Contact: michael_hernandez@adobe.net, 321-654-7813. Skills: Linux, Kubernetes, Agile, C#.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                87,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                109,
                114,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                126,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                128,
                133,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emily Clark is a data scientist at Netflix. Contact: emilyclark@netflix.org, 321-654-2279. Skills: SQL, Python, Agile, Scrum.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                42,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                53,
                75,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                77,
                89,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                99,
                102,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                117,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Daniel Johnson is a project manager at IBM. Contact: daniel_johnson@ibm.net, 159-753-2904. Skills: Agile, Kubernetes, SQL, Scrum.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                42,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                53,
                75,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                77,
                89,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                99,
                104,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                128,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Olivia Doe is a senior software developer at Amazon. Contact: olivia_doe@amazon.net, 159-753-8484. Skills: Python, Linux, Kubernetes, Java.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                107,
                113,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                132,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                134,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "David Doe is a cloud architect at Tesla. Contact: david.doe@tesla.com, 987-654-2196. Skills: C#, Java.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                34,
                39,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                50,
                69,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                71,
                83,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                93,
                95,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                97,
                101,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jane Lee is a software engineer at Facebook. Contact: janelee@facebook.org, +1-555-123-5703. Skills: Docker, TensorFlow, C#.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                43,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                54,
                74,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                76,
                91,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                101,
                107,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                119,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sophia Martinez is a senior software developer at Oracle. Contact: sophiamartinez@oracle.org, +1-555-123-9835. Skills: Java, SQL.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                92,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                94,
                109,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                119,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                128,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael Lee is a cloud architect at Netflix. Contact: michael.lee@netflix.com, 987-654-1056. Skills: Scrum, Kubernetes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                43,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                54,
                77,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                79,
                91,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                101,
                106,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Daniel Martinez is a AI researcher at Oracle. Contact: daniel.martinez@oracle.com, 987-654-8546. Skills: Docker, Scrum, Agile.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                44,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                55,
                81,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                83,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                105,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                125,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jane Doe is a cloud architect at Intel. Contact: jane.doe@intel.com, 987-654-4376. Skills: SQL, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                38,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                49,
                67,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                69,
                81,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                91,
                94,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                96,
                102,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Olivia Clark is a software engineer at Microsoft. Contact: olivia_clark@microsoft.net, +1-555-123-7590. Skills: Agile, Linux, TensorFlow.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                87,
                102,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                112,
                117,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "John Johnson is a AI researcher at Tesla. Contact: john.johnson@tesla.com, 321-654-6253. Skills: Scrum, Docker.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                40,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                51,
                73,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                75,
                87,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                97,
                102,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Daniel Davis is a cloud architect at Tesla. Contact: danieldavis@tesla.org, +1-555-123-3869. Skills: C#, Linux, Kubernetes, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                42,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                53,
                74,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                76,
                91,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                101,
                103,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                130,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sophia Martinez is a AI researcher at IBM. Contact: sophia_martinez@ibm.net, 159-753-7688. Skills: Scrum, C#.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                41,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                52,
                75,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                77,
                89,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                99,
                104,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                108,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael Lee is a senior software developer at Microsoft. Contact: michael.lee@microsoft.com, 321-654-3365. Skills: Python, Linux, C#.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                91,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                93,
                105,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                115,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                128,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                130,
                132,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Liam Lee is a AI researcher at Amazon. Contact: liamlee@amazon.org, 987-654-5177. Skills: Java, SQL.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                27,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                31,
                37,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                48,
                66,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                68,
                80,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                90,
                94,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                96,
                99,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Olivia Wilson is a data scientist at Netflix. Contact: olivia_wilson@netflix.net, 987-654-1844. Skills: C#, Python, SQL.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                44,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                55,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                82,
                94,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                104,
                106,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                114,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                119,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emily Clark is a AI researcher at Microsoft. Contact: emilyclark@microsoft.org, 987-654-6455. Skills: Python, Agile, Linux.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                34,
                43,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                54,
                78,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                80,
                92,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                102,
                108,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jane Hernandez is a backend developer at Intel. Contact: jane_hernandez@intel.net, 987-654-7498. Skills: Linux, Java.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                46,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                81,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                83,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                105,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "David Martinez is a senior software developer at Netflix. Contact: david_martinez@netflix.net, 321-654-6053. Skills: Java, Linux, Kubernetes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                93,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                95,
                107,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                117,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                128,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                130,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Olivia Smith is a senior software developer at IBM. Contact: olivia.smith@ibm.com, 321-654-6126. Skills: Python, Agile, Docker.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                61,
                81,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                83,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                105,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                126,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "John Brown is a AI researcher at Intel. Contact: john_brown@intel.net, 159-753-5836. Skills: Agile, Java.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                38,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                49,
                69,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                71,
                83,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                93,
                98,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                104,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emily Martinez is a DevOps engineer at Microsoft. Contact: emilymartinez@microsoft.org, 321-654-5216. Skills: Kubernetes, TensorFlow, Docker.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                110,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                132,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                134,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sophia Johnson is a project manager at Netflix. Contact: sophiajohnson@netflix.org, 987-654-9882. Skills: Python, Linux, TensorFlow, C#.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                46,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                84,
                96,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                106,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                119,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                131,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                133,
                135,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jane Doe is a software engineer at Oracle. Contact: jane.doe@oracle.com, 987-654-2113. Skills: Docker, Python, Agile, Scrum.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                41,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                52,
                71,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                73,
                85,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                95,
                101,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                109,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Olivia Wilson is a software engineer at Intel. Contact: olivia_wilson@intel.net, 159-753-8993. Skills: Python, Linux.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                45,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                56,
                79,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                103,
                109,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Daniel Martinez is a software engineer at Google. Contact: daniel_martinez@google.net, 321-654-9777. Skills: Python, Linux, C#.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                87,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                109,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                126,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael Smith is a data scientist at Netflix. Contact: michael.smith@netflix.com, 987-654-4144. Skills: Linux, Scrum, Java, Docker.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                44,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                55,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                82,
                94,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                104,
                109,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                130,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Liam Smith is a cybersecurity analyst at Oracle. Contact: liamsmith@oracle.org, 987-654-4700. Skills: SQL, Python, TensorFlow.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                78,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                80,
                92,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                102,
                105,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                113,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                125,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Liam Martinez is a cloud architect at Netflix. Contact: liammartinez@netflix.org, +1-555-123-1154. Skills: Docker, SQL, Kubernetes, C#.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                45,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                56,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                82,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                107,
                113,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                130,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                132,
                134,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Liam Wilson is a DevOps engineer at Facebook. Contact: liam_wilson@facebook.net, +1-555-123-4764. Skills: TensorFlow, Kubernetes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                44,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                55,
                79,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                96,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                106,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                128,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "David Doe is a data scientist at Tesla. Contact: david_doe@tesla.net, +1-555-123-3938. Skills: Python, Agile, Docker.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                38,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                49,
                68,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                70,
                85,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                95,
                101,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                108,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Liam Smith is a machine learning engineer at Amazon. Contact: liam_smith@amazon.net, 987-654-7375. Skills: Linux, Java, C#, Kubernetes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                107,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                134,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael Smith is a AI researcher at IBM. Contact: michael.smith@ibm.com, +1-555-123-8161. Skills: SQL, Java.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                39,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                50,
                71,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                73,
                88,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                98,
                101,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                107,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emma Clark is a DevOps engineer at Oracle. Contact: emmaclark@oracle.org, +1-555-123-5478. Skills: Kubernetes, Agile, Java.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                41,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                52,
                72,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                74,
                89,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                99,
                109,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Daniel Martinez is a cloud architect at Amazon. Contact: daniel_martinez@amazon.net, 159-753-2404. Skills: Scrum, Agile, SQL, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                46,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                107,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                119,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                132,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "David Johnson is a cloud architect at Amazon. Contact: david_johnson@amazon.net, 159-753-6188. Skills: SQL, TensorFlow, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                44,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                55,
                79,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                103,
                106,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                126,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "David Hernandez is a cybersecurity analyst at Tesla. Contact: david.hernandez@tesla.com, 987-654-2430. Skills: C#, Kubernetes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                87,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                89,
                101,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                111,
                113,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                125,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Daniel Lee is a AI researcher at Oracle. Contact: daniel.lee@oracle.com, +1-555-123-2468. Skills: Linux, SQL, Java.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                39,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                50,
                71,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                73,
                88,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                98,
                103,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                108,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                114,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Liam Doe is a machine learning engineer at Oracle. Contact: liamdoe@oracle.org, +1-555-123-4977. Skills: Linux, Docker, C#, SQL.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                49,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                78,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                80,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                105,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael Brown is a machine learning engineer at Tesla. Contact: michaelbrown@tesla.org, 987-654-2036. Skills: C#, Scrum.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                53,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                64,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                110,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                119,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Liam Brown is a senior software developer at Facebook. Contact: liambrown@facebook.org, 321-654-5040. Skills: Kubernetes, Agile, TensorFlow, Python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                53,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                64,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                110,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                141,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael Brown is a software engineer at Oracle. Contact: michaelbrown@oracle.org, 159-753-6399. Skills: Java, C#, Docker.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                46,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                82,
                94,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                104,
                108,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "David Wilson is a DevOps engineer at Microsoft. Contact: davidwilson@microsoft.org, 321-654-3910. Skills: Java, Scrum, Kubernetes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                46,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                84,
                96,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                106,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                117,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emma Davis is a cybersecurity analyst at Oracle. Contact: emmadavis@oracle.org, 159-753-6980. Skills: TensorFlow, Agile.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                78,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                80,
                92,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                102,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                119,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emma Lee is a project manager at Netflix. Contact: emma.lee@netflix.com, 159-753-4434. Skills: Scrum, SQL, C#.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                40,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                51,
                71,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                73,
                85,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                95,
                100,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                105,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                109,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Olivia Johnson is a machine learning engineer at Microsoft. Contact: oliviajohnson@microsoft.org, 987-654-7932. Skills: SQL, Kubernetes, Linux.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                69,
                96,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                98,
                110,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                120,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                135,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                137,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emma Martinez is a AI researcher at Netflix. Contact: emma_martinez@netflix.net, 159-753-9907. Skills: Java, Linux.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                43,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                54,
                79,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                103,
                107,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                114,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emma Smith is a data scientist at Microsoft. Contact: emma_smith@microsoft.net, 321-654-3725. Skills: TensorFlow, Python, C#, Kubernetes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                34,
                43,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                54,
                78,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                80,
                92,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                102,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sophia Martinez is a data scientist at Google. Contact: sophia.martinez@google.com, 321-654-4637. Skills: Linux, TensorFlow, Agile, Kubernetes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                45,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                56,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                84,
                96,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                106,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                130,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                132,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sophia Martinez is a senior software developer at Intel. Contact: sophia_martinez@intel.net, 987-654-6651. Skills: Kubernetes, SQL.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                91,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                93,
                105,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                115,
