[
    {
        "text": "Mills Helen is a administrative project coordinator at LendingKart. You can contact them at daniel_wilson@ibm.net or 987-654-8546. Skills: operational excellence, c taxation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                87,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                89,
                101,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kelsall Aaron is a accountant systems at Ask Me. You can contact them at michael_martinez@tesla.net or 987-654-6651. Skills: syrup, business targets salary.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                45,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                47,
                73,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                75,
                87,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                125,
                130,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Oneill Jack is a address change clerk at AARGEE STAFFING SERVICES. You can contact them at davidwilson@netflix.org or 159-753-9907. Skills: cnc business development, ise.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                65,
                88,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                90,
                102,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Preston Joshua is a actuarial analyst at Vidal Health Tpa. You can contact them at janeclark@netflix.org or 1-555-123-3938. Skills: meghana mehek sanam, application management services.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                78,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                80,
                94,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                132,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Romeyer Arthur is a adult literacy instructor at BANKEDGE. You can contact them at jane.clark@amazon.com or 159-753-7708. Skills: voice accent, job description send.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                78,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                80,
                92,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Taggart Dominic is a accounts officer at Precision Techserve. You can contact them at liam.wilson@oracle.com or 1-555-123-6417. Skills: hindco recruitment, experience needed.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                84,
                98,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Palubinskas Elvinas is a adult day care worker at Border Security Force. You can contact them at david.davis@facebook.com or 987-654-4376. Skills: round graduate, round aptitude.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                71,
                95,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                97,
                109,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Savalia Milan is a agency recruiter at Wilo Mather and Platt Pu. You can contact them at david_doe@tesla.net or 1-555-123-6097. Skills: shades, manager nsm team.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                84,
                98,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jones Pat is a acid concentrator at Gujarat Energy Transmiss. You can contact them at olivia.davis@amazon.com or 321-654-4657. Skills: details ites, goods &amp; service tax.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                34,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Gradowska Ewelina is a aadc plans staff officer at Avontix. You can contact them at david.lee@amazon.com or 987-654-7375. Skills: supermarkets, advisor marketing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                78,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                80,
                92,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Close Olivia is a advertising assistant at Gmmco. You can contact them at davidjohnson@oracle.org or 159-753-7852. Skills: trms, also apply.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                46,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                48,
                71,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                73,
                85,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Metcalfe Alice is a addiction counselor at DS Spiceco. You can contact them at liam.wilson@amazon.com or 159-753-4340. Skills: international non, dv.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                53,
                75,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                77,
                89,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                127,
                144,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Badham Sophie is a adjuster electrical contacts at Unibeton Readymix. You can contact them at david.martinez@oracle.com or 321-654-3755. Skills: integrated supply chain management, uni sankyo otsira.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                68,
                93,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                95,
                107,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                145,
                179,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rogers Justin is a agricultural equipment salesperson at Godrej Group. You can contact them at jane_doe@facebook.net or 987-654-6210. Skills: successful, lakh experienced.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                52,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                55,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                69,
                90,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                92,
                104,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Flockhart Lorraine is a admission liaison at Gontermann Peipers. You can contact them at oliviadoe@amazon.org or 321-654-1266. Skills: cloud consulting, software agents.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Whittingham Jamie is a acid correction hand at Aneja Associates. You can contact them at michael.lee@ibm.com or 987-654-5177. Skills: sankyo, name financial.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                84,
                96,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Brown Agnes is a adult neurologist at Dmi Housing Finance. You can contact them at olivia_lee@amazon.net or 321-654-1266. Skills: glycopeptide, candidates backlogs.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                78,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                80,
                92,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Warren Abbie is a admissions dean at Government Medical Colle. You can contact them at emily_clark@oracle.net or 321-654-1439. Skills: hotsos, economic development research.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                61,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mullarkey Mark is a acds block 1 operator at Abbott Truecare Pharma. You can contact them at liambrown@facebook.org or 987-654-7868. Skills: bcp model, ansi y14.5.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                89,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                91,
                103,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bowman Michelle is a accounts payable or receivable clerk at Renewsys India. You can contact them at daniel.wilson@netflix.com or 159-753-3421. Skills: struts 2.x, specialist seller.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                114,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                152,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "White Lisa is a advertising account manager at JSW Cement. You can contact them at emmadavis@intel.org or 321-654-6053. Skills: apply possess, legal agreements lease abstraction lease admin lease abstraction lease document.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                76,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                78,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                128,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Costa Federico is a advertising layout worker at Ramkrishna Care Hospital. You can contact them at david_johnson@amazon.net or 159-753-6980. Skills: fresenius, mareting.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                73,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                99,
                111,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                149,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Gildea Leanne is a administrative services manager at Sheth Creators. You can contact them at jane_johnson@amazon.net or 159-753-6150. Skills: end end solution, zero liquid discharge.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                68,
                91,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                93,
                105,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dhengale Pramod is a aerophysicist at KEM Hospital. You can contact them at michael_wilson@tesla.net or 159-753-6980. Skills: p l, relevant experience.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                50,
                74,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                76,
                88,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                126,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Marcinkowska Dominika is a adjustment supervisor at Mynd Solutions Private. You can contact them at emilymartinez@microsoft.org or 1-555-123-2481. Skills: ms office, download ppt photo.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                74,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                117,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                155,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Wright Lilly is a academy director at Mapro Foods. You can contact them at sophia_lee@amazon.net or 321-654-1266. Skills: io characterization, focal point.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                49,
                70,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                72,
                84,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                122,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jones-Campbell Steven is a abrading machine tender at Bright Power Projects. You can contact them at emily_clark@amazon.net or 159-753-1981. Skills: sap mii, postgraduate mba.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                99,
                111,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                149,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mcdermott Michael is a agricultural equipment sales engineer at Kaar Technologies. You can contact them at john.doe@amazon.com or 321-654-5216. Skills: ranked, corporate communications.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                59,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                62,
                79,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                114,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                152,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Louise Saskia is a advisory intern at Acg Pampac Machines. You can contact them at michael_clark@netflix.net or 987-654-7868. Skills: otsira genetica, manpower incorporated.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                84,
                96,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hillyard Chloe is a 6th grade teacher at Power2sme. You can contact them at sophia_martinez@intel.net or 321-654-2353. Skills: specialization company profile, assemblies.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                50,
                75,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                77,
                89,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                127,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Binoy Luxeena is a accounting recruiter at Sri Ramachandra Medical . You can contact them at emily.martinez@adobe.com or 159-753-5732. Skills: target education, oracle data integrator (odi).",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                91,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                93,
                105,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Power Chantelle is a advertising vice president at ISKCON. You can contact them at emmaclark@oracle.org or 321-654-8932. Skills: people pan india, tech span.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                77,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                79,
                91,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                129,
                145,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Burns Steven is a acquisition associate at U.S. Polo Assn. You can contact them at olivia_wilson@oracle.net or 159-753-1072. Skills: reail store manager, x-ray diffraction analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                81,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                83,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Whitelaw Lynsey is a admitting representative at Cyient DLM. You can contact them at olivia_clark@microsoft.net or 987-654-3352. Skills: years sales, us staffing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                87,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rogers Justin is a admissions manager rn at Kotak Securities. You can contact them at emilyclark@microsoft.org or 987-654-3174. Skills: igcse maths, ways provided.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                84,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                86,
                98,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Singleton Susan is a admitting coordinator at RR Projects. You can contact them at liam_smith@amazon.net or 1-555-123-5703. Skills: kpo ites, industry chemistry.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                78,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                80,
                94,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                132,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jiang Joyce is a after school caregiver at Crystal Ceramic Industri. You can contact them at danielbrown@oracle.org or 1-555-123-9835. Skills: pharma company, hr round.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                89,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                91,
                105,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Fox Iri is a active directory specialist at Infozech Software. You can contact them at janehernandez@amazon.org or 987-654-9788. Skills: partner service manager, scheduling.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                7,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                12,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                61,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                87,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sargent Calum is a acid tester at Godrej Infotech. You can contact them at david_martinez@facebook.net or 321-654-5216. Skills: anjali, also provided.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                32,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                49,
                76,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                78,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                128,
                134,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ball Jake is a ada accommodation consultant at Eastern Book Company. You can contact them at jane.davis@amazon.com or 159-753-4201. Skills: experience, field force effectiveness.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                88,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                90,
                102,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Day Ryan is a accounting manager cpa at Euronet Global Developme. You can contact them at liamjohnson@ibm.org or 987-654-2589. Skills: checkpoint security, attitude committed.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                13,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                64,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Cheshire Caz is a absorption operator at H&M. You can contact them at michael.smith@netflix.com or 321-654-3365. Skills: role category, sap application.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                42,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                44,
                69,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                71,
                83,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                121,
                134,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Murrihy Nardein G is a afterschool babysitter at Kitex Garments. You can contact them at daniel_martinez@amazon.net or 1-555-123-2468. Skills: customer need, sage crm.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                89,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                91,
                105,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mckinlay Charlie is a agricultural equipment sales manager at SITA. You can contact them at danielbrown@tesla.org or 159-753-7875. Skills: category senior management, bangalore download.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                57,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                60,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                87,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                89,
                101,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Carrigan Denise is a admitting representative at NAVEEN KUMAR. You can contact them at janehernandez@amazon.org or 321-654-8932. Skills: rhcs, python testing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                61,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                87,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Johnson Shane is a admissions coordinator at Glass Wall Systems. You can contact them at liamsmith@intel.org or 987-654-7375. Skills: electronic payments, sales and marketing executive.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                84,
                96,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Morgan Nicole is a accounts payable supervisor at Park Avenue. You can contact them at jane_martinez@netflix.net or 987-654-2589. Skills: engineering training, ansi y14.5.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                61,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                138,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Savalia Milan is a acquisition marketing coordinator at Annet Technologies. You can contact them at david_martinez@facebook.net or 159-753-3458. Skills: mentioned, consultancies.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                74,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                153,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Polley Zak is a 3d modeler at IANT. You can contact them at jane_lee@ibm.net or 321-654-9108. Skills: wockhardt novo nordisk, view contact details.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                25,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                28,
                32,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                34,
                50,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                52,
                64,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                102,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Abdi Ali is a accounting supervisor at Alghanim Industries. You can contact them at john.doe@amazon.com or 321-654-4827. Skills: manager round, motherson sumi.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                13,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                77,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                79,
                91,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                129,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Cupitt Martin is a aerial photogrammetrist at ECOS (I) MOBILITY & HOSP. You can contact them at olivia_wilson@oracle.net or 987-654-6373. Skills: software engineer (android developer), capital markets.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                70,
                94,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                96,
                108,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                146,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Iza Paez Sam is a agricultural equipment salesperson at Sanofi-Aventis. You can contact them at olivia_wilson@oracle.net or 321-654-6053. Skills: clinical research functional, microsoft.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                70,
                94,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                96,
                108,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                146,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Greatrex Carly is a after school caregiver at SAAB ENGINEERING. You can contact them at liamdavis@microsoft.org or 321-654-1439. Skills: zydus fresenius kabi, track record achieving.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                87,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Squires Louis is a accounts payable accountant at Radiant Export. You can contact them at danieldavis@tesla.org or 159-753-9006. Skills: sql servr 2000, managing sales.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                64,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                87,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Cammack Calum is a acoustics teacher at Dalmia Bharat Sugar & In. You can contact them at daniel.lee@oracle.com or 321-654-5794. Skills: hiring - bulk, aristo uni.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                64,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                87,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rowe Kai is a accounting policy consultant at Trident Group. You can contact them at jane_doe@facebook.net or 321-654-8511. Skills: contract negotiation, ms office.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                13,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                82,
                94,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                132,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kennedy Caitlin is a accountant clerk at Polyhose. You can contact them at davidsmith@netflix.org or 1-555-123-1017. Skills: gas stations, medical equipment devices.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                49,
                71,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                73,
                87,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                125,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Brookes Matty J is a advance agent at Shakti Bhog Foods. You can contact them at jane.doe@facebook.com or 159-753-4340. Skills: data maintaining, ways rounds.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                53,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                55,
                76,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                78,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                128,
                144,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dearie Annmarie is a acid loader at ABC Consultants. You can contact them at sophiamartinez@ibm.org or 159-753-4434. Skills: qualifications, p salary.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                34,
                49,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                51,
                73,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                75,
                87,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                125,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Loks Thomas is a adobe block maker at Srinivasa Sales & Servic. You can contact them at olivia.lee@netflix.com or 1-555-123-9835. Skills: financial close process, oriented.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                84,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                86,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                138,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Wright Sammie is a adjunct faculty at Jumbo Finvest India. You can contact them at emilyclark@microsoft.org or 1-555-123-5602. Skills: anjali openings, application frameworks.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                81,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                83,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Athey-Burns Marie is a administrative professional at Radnik Exports. You can contact them at emma.wilson@oracle.com or 987-654-9882. Skills: remote i/o, icd-10.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                68,
                90,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                92,
                104,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Halabrin Radim is a africana studies professor at Ezeego One Travel Tours. You can contact them at daniel.clark@amazon.com or 1-555-123-5026. Skills: dgm quality, pg postgraduate mba.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                73,
                96,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                98,
                112,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                150,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Gradowska Ewelina is a accredited farm manager at ANZ Operations & Technol. You can contact them at emma.smith@facebook.com or 1-555-123-3938. Skills: support helpdesk, service technical.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                74,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                99,
                113,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                151,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Gregory Peter is a account management assistant at Narayana Multispeciality. You can contact them at liam.smith@intel.com or 159-753-7852. Skills: appreciated, p salary.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                95,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                97,
                109,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Stewart Chloe is a acidizer helper at Ebco. You can contact them at emilymartinez@microsoft.org or 987-654-3981. Skills: references would highly, front office development.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                40,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                42,
                69,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                71,
                83,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                121,
                144,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Khan Irfan is a agile tester at Brandix. You can contact them at sophia.clark@amazon.com or 321-654-3007. Skills: oracel applications technical consultant, lakh freshers.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                27,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                30,
                37,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                39,
                62,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                64,
                76,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                114,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Summers Stephanie is a account resolution analyst at ANY Graphics. You can contact them at michael.lee@tesla.com or 159-753-3421. Skills: business development planning, merchandise planning.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                65,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                138,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Barcelona Rosalina is a accounts officer at Supreme Industries. You can contact them at emma_davis@ibm.net or 987-654-9882. Skills: bayer pfizer, consultants mentioned.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                82,
                94,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                132,
                144,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Head Alan is a account services representative at Aon Services. You can contact them at oliviahernandez@tesla.org or 987-654-7498. Skills: marketing advertising mr, p r.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                87,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                89,
                101,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hughes Rob is a aerospace physiological technician at BRIGHTVIEW TELECOM. You can contact them at emilyclark@netflix.org or 159-753-9773. Skills: designated, disclosed recruiter industry.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                72,
                94,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                96,
                108,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                146,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Smith Robert is a aerial gunner at State Street Global Advi. You can contact them at janehernandez@amazon.org or 987-654-8546. Skills: informatica mdm developer, fresenius kabi aristo.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Farrell Annmarie is a abnormal psychology teacher at KGK Group. You can contact them at olivia.smith@ibm.com or 1-555-123-6417. Skills: ptms, pharmaceutical ingredients.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                84,
                98,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bourne Gordon is a adjunct faculty mathematics department at Kevin Process Technologi. You can contact them at daniel.doe@ibm.com or 987-654-3653. Skills: spirent, zydus fresenius.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                83,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                103,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                117,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                155,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hogg Lee is a after school program teacher at Ani Instruments. You can contact them at david_clark@netflix.net or 159-753-1613. Skills: cloud consulting, expense reports.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                13,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                61,
                84,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                86,
                98,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Marsh Cassie is a aeronautical engineering teacher at Barclays. You can contact them at john.doe@amazon.com or 159-753-1072. Skills: public budgeting, postgraduate mba pgdm.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                81,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                83,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Barakat Sultz is a actuarial associate at Hatsun Agro Product. You can contact them at john_brown@intel.net or 321-654-4302. Skills: kitchen design, online retail.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                61,
                81,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                83,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hunter Abbie is a 8th grade mathematics teacher at Hfcl Infotel. You can contact them at michael.brown@adobe.com or 987-654-7878. Skills: airwoot, ingredients apis end.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                138,
                145,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Conn Stuart is a account developer at Madhav Infra Projects. You can contact them at sophia.johnson@google.com or 321-654-2204. Skills: online marketer, wcs suite.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                84,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                86,
                98,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Westrip Jacy is a accreditation manager at Zenith Infotech. You can contact them at davidsmith@facebook.org or 321-654-6253. Skills: bpo technical, area marketing advertising.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                81,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                83,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                146,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Di Monte Martina is a adaptive physical education teacher at Sterling Indo Tech Consu. You can contact them at michael_hernandez@ibm.net or 1-555-123-9159. Skills: education ug, mortgage ocwen.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                83,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                126,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                164,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Smith Stacie is a advanced registered nurse at G.V.K. You can contact them at daniel.hernandez@adobe.com or 159-753-8635. Skills: banding, must successful.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                52,
                78,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                80,
                92,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kuczynski Nikki is a abstracter at GE Transportation. You can contact them at davidsmith@google.org or 159-753-1530. Skills: education ug graduate, ordinances.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                52,
                73,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                75,
                87,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                125,
                146,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Norman Jenny is a aegis operations specialist at SecUR Credentials. You can contact them at jane_martinez@netflix.net or 159-753-9773. Skills: candidates freshers, graduates post.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                91,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                93,
                105,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Robertson David is a acoustic engineer at Rudra Real Estate. You can contact them at davidsmith@google.org or 987-654-3875. Skills: support marketing, game-play.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                82,
                94,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                132,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Griffin Carl is a acute care physical therapist at Birlasoft. You can contact them at sophiamartinez@oracle.org or 321-654-3007. Skills: aisc, area marketing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                87,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Barakat Sultz is a account installer at MFX. You can contact them at david.lee@amazon.com or 159-753-7875. Skills: oracle administrator, pwa.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                41,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                43,
                63,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                65,
                77,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                115,
                135,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Savalia Milan is a agency service coordinator at Sentec India Company. You can contact them at sophiamartinez@ibm.org or 159-753-9275. Skills: kabi aristo uni, cosmetology.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                69,
                91,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                93,
                105,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Green Callum is a agent broker at Eaton Industrial Systems. You can contact them at emmadavis@oracle.org or 159-753-3421. Skills: salary hikes, company evolved.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                32,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                78,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                80,
                92,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Welsh Kerry Louise is a aadc plans staff officer at Bata. You can contact them at michael.smith@netflix.com or 987-654-2430. Skills: combat, medical software sales.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                56,
                81,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                83,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hellyer Holly is a advanced manufacturing consultant at Ind-Swift Laboratories. You can contact them at emma.lee@netflix.com or 1-555-123-7270. Skills: comscore, industry pharma.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                76,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                78,
                98,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                114,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                152,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Xue Jingyi is a advocacy director at Dynamic Engineering. You can contact them at michael.doe@intel.com or 159-753-1507. Skills: specialization company, disclosed.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                56,
                77,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                79,
                91,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                129,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Miah Alamin is a agricultural economics teacher at Classic Fashion Apparel . You can contact them at emmadoe@google.org or 987-654-6210. Skills: online application, graphic design software.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                93,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                95,
                107,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                145,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Evans Andrea N Andrew is a adult psychiatrist at Medipulse Hospital. You can contact them at emilybrown@adobe.org or 159-753-9907. Skills: microsoft, implementation marketing strategies.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                87,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                89,
                101,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Stares Elliot is a advice line rn at Utkarsh India. You can contact them at michael_martinez@tesla.net or 159-753-9609. Skills: please note, gas stations.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                50,
                76,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                78,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                128,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Leitão Ana is a administrative assistant receptionist at Amara Raja Infra. You can contact them at michael.wilson@ibm.com or 159-753-4470. Skills: studio.net, different therapies team.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                52,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                55,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                73,
                95,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                97,
                109,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Fricker Chris is a adjunct art history instructor at ZOMATO. You can contact them at olivia_wilson@netflix.net or 1-555-123-6776. Skills: analyse de données, thompson drop.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                84,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                86,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                138,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Robinson Georgia is a active directory administrator at Pricol. You can contact them at jane_martinez@tesla.net or 1-555-123-1742. Skills: biotech clinical research, bangalore salary.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                87,
                101,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hollis Neil is a acid plant helper at Indian Synthetic Rubber. You can contact them at jane_hernandez@intel.net or 159-753-7708. Skills: application, job description.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                61,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                87,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Widdowson Kevin is a aerial gunner at Ceat Tyres. You can contact them at davidjohnson@oracle.org or 987-654-6455. Skills: peering, sanam pushpa.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                46,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                48,
                71,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                73,
                85,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                130,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Starr Roger is a agency service representative at JK Cement. You can contact them at liam_smith@amazon.net or 159-753-6150. Skills: digital signal 3 (ds3), possess good.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                82,
                94,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                132,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Lindsay George is a accounting office manager at Armstrong International. You can contact them at jane_doe@intel.net or 159-753-4470. Skills: st.mary, actd.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                72,
                90,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                92,
                104,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": " Tony is a acute dialysis nurse at Shivashakti Bio Technolo. You can contact them at jane_brown@adobe.net or 321-654-8849. Skills: office good, online application.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                5,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                10,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                79,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Murray Michael is a agricultural chemist at United Capital Club. You can contact them at liam.smith@intel.com or 1-555-123-5026. Skills: smps, android).",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Williams Nathan is a accounts payable or receivable clerk at ATS Infrastructure. You can contact them at daniel_martinez@amazon.net or 159-753-6636. Skills: site selection, support marketing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                119,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                157,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Pattison Sinead is a aerographer at General Mills. You can contact them at liamsmith@intel.org or 1-555-123-3684. Skills: glycopeptide, casting.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                34,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                49,
                68,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                70,
                84,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                122,
                134,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kennedy Jake is a aerial advertiser at Ul India. You can contact them at emmabrown@intel.org or 159-753-4470. Skills: ftth, available process name.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                45,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                47,
                66,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                68,
                80,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                118,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Reid Colin is a account services specialist at Seth M R Jaipuria School. You can contact them at sophia_lee@amazon.net or 987-654-7375. Skills: sql servr 2000, strategies achieve business.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                71,
                92,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                94,
                106,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                144,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Patel Pradip is a after school tutor at KSA PowerInfra. You can contact them at liam.johnson@facebook.com or 321-654-5662. Skills: manufacturer, hindco recruitment consultants.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                52,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                54,
                79,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                143,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Nemeth Cox Sue is a adjunct phlebotomy instructor at Aries Agro. You can contact them at emily_martinez@amazon.net or 321-654-5525. Skills: senior management role, food coupons.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                88,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                90,
                102,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Westrip Jacy is a aeronautical research engineer at Maithan Ispat. You can contact them at daniel.doe@ibm.com or 321-654-1969. Skills: role associate, online submission application.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                65,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mills Rhonda is a acct exec at Relevance Lab. You can contact them at jane.doe@facebook.com or 321-654-8511. Skills: manufacturer pharmaceutical, superannuation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                26,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                29,
                42,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                44,
                65,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                67,
                79,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                117,
                144,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Navin Eve is a agility instructor at AppsDaily. You can contact them at emmabrown@intel.org or 1-555-123-8161. Skills: healthcare group leading, leading manufacturer pharmaceutical.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                44,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                46,
                65,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                67,
                81,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                119,
                143,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Silva Elias is a administrative resources associate at Patil Automation. You can contact them at david.doe@tesla.com or 987-654-4700. Skills: bpo big, goods &amp; service tax.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                71,
                90,
