[
    {
        "text": "Costain Danniella is a Consultant at Caparo Group. You can contact he/she at janelee@facebook.org or 987-654-9788. Skills: Performance improvement initiatives, Sourcing strategies, Open Directory.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                49,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                101,
                113,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                181,
                195,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                160,
                179,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Merdekawati Syeni is a Backend Architect at Rashmi Group. You can contact he/she at olivia_lee@amazon.net or 1-555-123-5602. Skills: multivariate), Software performance analysis, Word processing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                146,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                194,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                148,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Cannings Mark is a Project Manager Big Data Analytics at Rashi Peripherals. You can contact he/she at janeclark@netflix.org or 1-555-123-1480. Skills: Amazon Web Services), Maintaining application code, Parallel Processing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                53,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                102,
                123,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                141,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                203,
                222,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                173,
                201,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                151,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tighe Shannon is a Application Programmer Analyst/Developer I at Tulip Infratech. You can contact he/she at liamdoe@oracle.org or 321-654-2923. Skills: Scenario planning, TPM (Total Productive Maintenance), Deploy/Maintain Exchange 2013.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                61,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                65,
                80,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                108,
                126,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                130,
                142,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                171,
                205,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                207,
                236,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                169,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Willighan Kayleigh-Jill is a Global Mobility Specialist at Appasamy Associates. You can contact he/she at michael.lee@tesla.com or 159-753-1530. Skills: Document Management (Laserfiche), KNIME, Solid project organization.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                23,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                78,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                106,
                127,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                143,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                187,
                192,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                153,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                194,
                220,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Diakoumakis Pandelis is a Social Media Analyst at Madras Engineering Indus. You can contact he/she at jane_doe@facebook.net or 159-753-1613. Skills: Core networking principles, Remote Windows OS Administration, Digital Signage solutions.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                102,
                123,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                211,
                236,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                177,
                209,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Fox Iri is a Youth Recreation Program Manager at SAI Life Sciences. You can contact he/she at emily.brown@tesla.com or 159-753-9609. Skills: Streaming, Network security best practices, Shell scripting (Bash or PowerShell).",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                7,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                13,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                115,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                131,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                185,
                221,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                141,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Patterson Eileen is a Planner 1 at Antithesis. You can contact he/she at daniel.martinez@oracle.com or 1-555-123-2730. Skills: Server/Desktop Computing, Processing orders, Cisco routing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                45,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                73,
                99,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                117,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                153,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Fatima Nusrat is a Test Engineer - Data Centric Testing at Data Entry. You can contact he/she at sophiamartinez@oracle.org or 1-555-123-5602. Skills: HR Information Systems (HRIS), Enterprise Security Architecture, Production switcher operation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                97,
                122,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                140,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                150,
                179,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                181,
                213,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                215,
                244,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tipping Summer is a Software Dev Engineer - Computer Science at Vanisb Technology. You can contact he/she at michael.smith@netflix.com or 987-654-7498. Skills: Entity relationship diagrams, Administration of ECM system (Hyland’s Perceptive Content Server, and JCR.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                64,
                81,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                109,
                134,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                150,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                256,
                263,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                160,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                190,
                254,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jones Charlie is a Business and Reporting Analyst at TONI&GUY. You can contact he/she at emmadoe@google.org or 159-753-8993. Skills: Data encryption, Demonstrated knowledge of routing/switching, Use of JReview or other analytical/visualization tools (e.g..",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                89,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                195,
                255,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                150,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Xue Jingyi is a Manager at Prione Business Services. You can contact he/she at daniel.hernandez@adobe.com or 159-753-2904. Skills: Process efficiency improvement, Software/web development, Querying.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                23,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                27,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                189,
                197,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Carter Anne is a Sr. Data Scientist at Applied Materials. You can contact he/she at janeclark@ibm.org or 159-753-3236. Skills: Process coordination, Table functions, Microsoft technologies (Windows networking.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                117,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                149,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                166,
                208,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Smith Fred is a Software Systems Engineer TS/SCI CI poly at Transcentra FTS. You can contact he/she at davidwilson@netflix.org or 159-753-9773. Skills: CUBE, Zen Desk, Lenovo.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                60,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                103,
                126,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                130,
                142,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                158,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                168,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Smyth Noreen is a CREATIVE DESIGN ENGINEER I at Synergy Infonet. You can contact he/she at jane.lee@amazon.com or 987-654-7498. Skills: Distributed version control systems (Git), Strong analytical skills, IT Advancements and Automation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                91,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                126,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                179,
                203,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                205,
                235,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kumar Rinku is a Network Solutions Architect at Presidium School. You can contact he/she at sophiajohnson@netflix.org or 159-753-3458. Skills: Amazon Redshift), High-level functional programming languages (e.g., CREO.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                92,
                117,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                133,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                212,
                216,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                161,
                210,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                143,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Chris Hargreaves Amy Hargreaves is a Software Engineer - Full Stack at BFG International. You can contact he/she at michael.lee@microsoft.com or 321-654-4827. Skills: User Feedback Prioritization, Web Servers (Apache), Layout techniques.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                31,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                37,
                67,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                71,
                88,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                116,
                141,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                145,
                157,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                167,
                195,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                219,
                236,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                197,
                217,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rosu Bogdan is a Software Development Analyst at SGD PHARMA. You can contact he/she at olivia_wilson@netflix.net or 159-753-2350. Skills: Salesforce.com reporting tools, Datacentre, Data Management disciplines (Data Vault.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                87,
                112,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                128,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                170,
                180,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                182,
                221,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ocula Antoine is a Computer Operator: ATMP : Grand Prairie at Rentokil Initial. You can contact he/she at emily.johnson@adobe.com or 159-753-8635. Skills: Network Security Technologies, User training, Upstream oil and gas land management.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                58,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                62,
                78,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                106,
                129,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                133,
                145,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                201,
                237,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                184,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                186,
                199,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Robinson Georgia is a BURBANK Campus Recruiting 2018 - I&D - Data Analyst at Communications Test Desi. You can contact he/she at liamhernandez@oracle.org or 987-654-6364. Skills: Business research tools, Capital Investment Analysis, Technology roadmap.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                73,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                77,
                101,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                129,
                153,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                157,
                169,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                233,
                251,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                202,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                204,
                231,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dnallaoj Elisabeth is a Data Analyst (226 Days) at LM Wind Power. You can contact he/she at liamhernandez@oracle.org or 159-753-6431. Skills: Web Services, subnets, Economic analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                92,
                116,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                165,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                142,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kumar Rinku is a Sr Software Engineer at Epiroc Mining India. You can contact he/she at john.smith@microsoft.com or 987-654-2120. Skills: Server 2012 and 2016, JMeter), Code versioning tools (e.g..",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                112,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                128,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                169,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                160,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Webster Hayley is a OneStream Software Systems Engineer at Gar Corporation. You can contact he/she at johnsmith@amazon.org or 159-753-5061. Skills: Database management system installation, NoSQL (Couchbase, Apache Web Server Configuration.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                102,
                122,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                138,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                148,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                189,
                205,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                207,
                238,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mcintyre Hannah is a Application Administrator at AXIS MY INDIA. You can contact he/she at david_johnson@amazon.net or 1-555-123-1154. Skills: Binary data, IT policy framework development, Maintenance Contractor Oversight.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                91,
                115,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                133,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                189,
                221,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Robertson Liam is a Employee Relations Consultant at Jaguar Land Rover. You can contact he/she at olivia.davis@amazon.com or 1-555-123-6488. Skills: Currency exchange knowledge, Security and auditing frameworks understanding, Mac Software.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                98,
                121,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                178,
                224,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                226,
                238,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hogg Steven is a Best Buy Mobile Sales Consultant at Swal Corporation. You can contact he/she at janesmith@netflix.org or 1-555-123-5026. Skills: Domo, and access support, Data visualization tools like Tableau and Kibana.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                97,
                118,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                136,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                146,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                220,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Turner Shane is a User Experience Designer at Gontermann Peipers. You can contact he/she at emma.lee@netflix.com or 159-753-4340. Skills: Parallel programming models, Predictive analytics, Anti-Virus Infrastructure.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                92,
                112,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                128,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                189,
                214,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rzepiel Dominik is a Full Stack Software Engineer at WHOOP. You can contact he/she at michaelbrown@oracle.org or 1-555-123-8231. Skills: Broadcast equipment knowledge, MS Access, Boxing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                109,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                168,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bocskai Eniko is a Data Center Facility Operations Chemical Engineer at LNJ Bhilwara Group. You can contact he/she at jane.lee@amazon.com or 987-654-9788. Skills: Recruitment programs implementation, Data processing procedures, Parallel Programming (CUDA.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                68,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                72,
                90,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                118,
                137,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                141,
                153,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                228,
                254,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                198,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                200,
                226,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jairam Jagdish is a APC Operator - KNTV/KSTS at Ericsson. You can contact he/she at sophiajohnson@netflix.org or 159-753-7431. Skills: IT Skills, Automation Anywhere, Data organization.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                109,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                144,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                184,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                146,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Gil Tomasz is a Video Software Engineer at NBCUniversal. You can contact he/she at michael.clark@oracle.com or 987-654-4972. Skills: Cloudera or Hortonworks, High-Performance Computing Methodologies, Operating small tractors and riding lawn mowers.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                198,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                200,
                247,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hiren Chaudhari is a Software Engineer (Aerodynamics) - TRU Simulation Training at Religare Securities. You can contact he/she at daniel.lee@oracle.com or 987-654-4972. Skills: Experience with MSS, Cloud Implementations (AWS EC2/EBS, Infrastructure Automation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                79,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                83,
                102,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                130,
                151,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                167,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                177,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                198,
                232,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                234,
                259,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Merrilees Marnie is a Urban Farmer & Installation Team Member at Forest Essentials. You can contact he/she at liam.johnson@facebook.com or 987-654-4700. Skills: Large-Scale Optimization, RackSpace, Database skills.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                61,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                65,
                82,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                110,
                135,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                139,
                151,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                187,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                198,
                213,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                161,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Everton Brooke is a Quality Control Technician at MXC Solutions India. You can contact he/she at daniel_martinez@amazon.net or 1-555-123-2730. Skills: Informatica product stack, multi-threading, SharePoint.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                97,
                123,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                141,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                151,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                178,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                195,
                205,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Winter James is a Quality Assurance Manager at SCIO Health Analytics. You can contact he/she at jane_martinez@tesla.net or 1-555-123-4977. Skills: Physics-based approaches, and technologies, Data exfiltration techniques.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                96,
                119,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                137,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                191,
                219,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                173,
                189,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                147,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Smith Fred is a Data Science Manager at KEM Hospital. You can contact he/she at michaelbrown@tesla.org or 159-753-3141. Skills: Traceability from requirements to test status, Loss prevention, SVN.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                52,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                80,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                118,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                175,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                128,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                192,
                195,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ramsamy Palmeshiven is a JavaScript Software Engineer – Analytics UI Team at Jeevan Jyoti Hospital. You can contact he/she at emily.johnson@oracle.com or 987-654-3320. Skills: Network Architecting, Word documents, Propensity Modeling.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                73,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                77,
                98,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                126,
                150,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                154,
                166,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                214,
                233,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                176,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                198,
                212,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Doherty Sharon is a Data Analyst II at Innovative Logistics. You can contact he/she at jane_johnson@amazon.net or 159-753-8715. Skills: Technical designs, Denodo Platform Control Center, Master Data Management Applications.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                87,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                126,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                155,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                187,
                222,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Whitehead Lewis is a Maintenance Engineer (Entry-Level) at Ambrane India. You can contact he/she at liammartinez@netflix.org or 159-753-3141. Skills: ICMP, Object Oriented Programming, Agile team leadership.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                100,
                124,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                128,
                140,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                156,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                185,
                206,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                150,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mcvie Megan is a Statistical Analyst at NIFA Infocomp Services. You can contact he/she at liam.wilson@amazon.com or 159-753-1731. Skills: GCIH, PostgreSQL) (related to experience), Data Gathering skills/tools (e.g. SQL.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                112,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                128,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                181,
                218,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                144,
                179,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Pearson Tom is a Sr Data Analyst at International Data Corpo. You can contact he/she at liam.johnson@facebook.com or 159-753-6980. Skills: Data Querying, Electronic records management system, Java applications deployment.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                192,
                220,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                154,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Astley Denis is a Solutions Engineer at Oberoi Group of Hotels. You can contact he/she at danieldavis@tesla.org or 1-555-123-8161. Skills: RDMA Offloading, Cloud technologies, Knowledge of display metrics and optimization.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                111,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                176,
                221,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Cotterill Amy is a Software Engineer III at Early Warning Services. You can contact he/she at michaelbrown@oracle.org or 987-654-6373. Skills: Production Operations, User Entitlement Management, BI Architectures.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                117,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                133,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                166,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                195,
                211,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Smith Fred is a IT Consultant at J Pan Tubular Components. You can contact he/she at olivia.smith@ibm.com or 987-654-2551. Skills: Micro Services, Memcache), Climate science.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                145,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Patel Maulik is a General Supervisor Quality (GSQ) at R K Enterprises. You can contact he/she at daniel.hernandez@adobe.com or 321-654-5064. Skills: Network Resources, MIRTH Software, Data Visualization Tools (R.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                97,
                123,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                168,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                184,
                211,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Clarke Harry is a Quality Food Safety (QFS) Manager-Spokane at XpressBees. You can contact he/she at danielhernandez@tesla.org or 321-654-6340. Skills: Complete Streets Design, Data strategy, Soapbox Engage.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                59,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                63,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                101,
                126,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                130,
                142,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                192,
                206,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                177,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Chris Hargreaves Amy Hargreaves is a Technical Team Lead at Viveks. You can contact he/she at liamjohnson@ibm.org or 987-654-6364. Skills: Physical), Security and information gathering tools (Snort, Application Architectures.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                31,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                37,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                60,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                199,
                224,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                150,
                197,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jones Amy is a Front-End Developer at FINE COMPONENTS AND TOOL. You can contact he/she at janedavis@microsoft.org or 987-654-3352. Skills: Analyzing large data sets, Surface mount technology (SMT), HubSpot certification.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                166,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                139,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                198,
                219,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Swallow Wayne is a Data Architect/Engineer at AKR TEXTILE. You can contact he/she at jane_martinez@tesla.net or 1-555-123-1017. Skills: Testing (TDD, Hyperion planning/Essbase, Operating equipment safely.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                126,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                150,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                177,
                203,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Marks Shaun is a Sr. Systems Admin at Aster (India). You can contact he/she at olivia_wilson@intel.net or 987-654-4053. Skills: CircleCI, Experience with Windows 10, Fundamental Statistical Concepts.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                118,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                128,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                166,
                198,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Brady Eddie is a Data Analyst at Christ Nishotech Water S. You can contact he/she at emilywilson@amazon.org or 159-753-3236. Skills: International Transactions, Radware, Project Quality Control Program Development.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                170,
                213,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                161,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mackie Linda is a Data Engineer - University Students at Development Consultants. You can contact he/she at sophia_martinez@intel.net or 1-555-123-8775. Skills: PowerBI or Tableau, Data Privacy Knowledge, Conducting health screenings and assessments.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                53,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                80,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                108,
                133,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                137,
                151,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                181,
                203,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                161,
                179,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                205,
                249,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Wilding Aaron is a Software Engineer - I Cloud/Microservices at Som Projects (S.P.L). You can contact he/she at michael.doe@intel.com or 1-555-123-2481. Skills: Bug tracking tools (JIRA), Commercial off the shelf solutions configuration, Blackbaud Raiser's Edge/NXT.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                64,
                84,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                112,
                133,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                137,
                151,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                238,
                265,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                188,
                236,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                161,
                186,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Crane Alan is a Learning Consultant at JSW Ispat Steel. You can contact he/she at david.martinez@oracle.com or 321-654-8511. Skills: Cellular technology, Automation writing, Integration with Internet of Things (IoT) devices.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                154,
                172,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                174,
                223,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                133,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Stringer Ed is a Software Engineer at PingWind. You can contact he/she at liammartinez@netflix.org or 1-555-123-6372. Skills: Object Recognition/Tracking, Data strategies, Agile).",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                46,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                74,
                98,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                126,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Siwak Magda is a Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence Senior Scientist at SS Construction. You can contact he/she at davidsmith@facebook.org or 987-654-4972. Skills: Network components (firewalls, Market knowledge, UI/HTML/JavaScript analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                78,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                82,
                97,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                125,
                148,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                164,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                174,
                203,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                205,
                221,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                223,
                250,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Naik Vinay is a Part Time - Statistician at Harvard University. You can contact he/she at jane.doe@intel.com or 987-654-5961. Skills: Operating forklifts, customer service skills, Julia).",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                124,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                155,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                134,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                180,
                186,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Willighan Kayleigh-Jill is a Senior Network Security Analyst for Information Technology at Crimson Interactive. You can contact he/she at emily_martinez@amazon.net or 159-753-4695. Skills: Real-time processing, Applicant tracking systems (ATS), SQL/PLSQL.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                23,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                87,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                91,
                110,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                138,
                163,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                179,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                189,
                209,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                211,
                243,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                245,
                254,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Owens Drew is a Business Systems Analyst Specialist at Sidvin Core-Tech. You can contact he/she at michael.smith@ibm.com or 987-654-6651. Skills: and Acrobat Reader, Mobile Authentication, Configuration and Release / Deployment Process.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                55,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                99,
                120,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                136,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                166,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                146,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                189,
                235,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hunter Abbie is a Quality & Commercialization Manager at RASI SEEDS. You can contact he/she at emily_martinez@amazon.net or 321-654-9777. Skills: Postman, Product evaluation, Kimball Design Methodology.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                53,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                95,
                120,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                136,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                175,
                201,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                146,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Choos Choo is a Senior IT Business Analyst - Human Resources at Oracle. You can contact he/she at john.hernandez@oracle.com or 987-654-5961. Skills: Management Coaching, Data processing, Sales Cloud Consultant.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                64,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                98,
                123,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                170,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                187,
                209,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Maxwell Michael is a Drexel Co-Op Student - Business Intelligence at Suhail Bahwan Automobile. You can contact he/she at liam_wilson@facebook.net or 1-555-123-8231. Skills: Ability to navigate systems and assist with routine auditing and monitoring activities, Excel skills, Data center switching.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                65,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                69,
                93,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                121,
                145,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                163,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                173,
                259,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                261,
                273,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                275,
                296,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rich Ben is a Basketball Data Analyst at Billroth Hospitals. You can contact he/she at emily.clark@google.com or 987-654-3320. Skills: Technical documentation, Linux/Windows administration, Data Warehouse Data Modeling.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                87,
                109,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                160,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                190,
                218,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mckean Phil is a Technology Sales Consultant at Kudos Chemie. You can contact he/she at danieldoe@ibm.org or 321-654-4637. Skills: BAT scripting, marketing practices, Strong organization skills.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                146,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                144,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Moran Amy is a Associate Director at Rudra Real Estate. You can contact he/she at david.hernandez@tesla.com or 987-654-4376. Skills: Motion graphics creation, Docker and containerization concepts, Visualization capabilities.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                159,
                195,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                197,
                223,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Navrátil Lukáš is a Sr. Analytics Consultant at Kamachi Group. You can contact he/she at oliviadoe@tesla.org or 321-654-8159. Skills: Switch configuration, SSAE 16/ ISAE3402), CS Awareness Training Compliance.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                89,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                124,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                176,
                208,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Pita Vanessa is a Principal Enterprise Architect at Shriram Properties. You can contact he/she at liamlee@amazon.org or 159-753-1613. Skills: Core Java Development, AAA, Design standards.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                98,
                116,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                165,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                170,
                186,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Buchot Nicolas is a Quality Coordinator II at Louis Dreyfus Commoditie. You can contact he/she at janehernandez@netflix.org or 321-654-5444. Skills: iOS development (Objective-C, Business intelligence software (Tableau), Machine Learning with Spark Mllib or similar.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                98,
                123,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                221,
                265,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                219,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Acres Mcguigan Amber is a Networks - Embedded Software Engineer at Divyasree Developers. You can contact he/she at michaelbrown@tesla.org or 159-753-6188. Skills: Adherence to Standards, LAN/WAN infrastructure design and maintenance, Programming in Java.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                63,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                67,
                87,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                115,
                137,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                141,
                153,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                234,
                253,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                187,
                232,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Navin Eve is a Quality Analyst - Minneapolis at Kunstocom India. You can contact he/she at emily_clark@oracle.net or 159-753-3828. Skills: Databases (SQL, Academic research, Online database data upload.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                91,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                174,
                201,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                172,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                139,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Brady Michelle is a Deep Learning Software Engineer at Piramal Healthcare. You can contact he/she at oliviadoe@amazon.org or 321-654-1266. Skills: Application deployment, ERP Systems, Microsoft Dynamics.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                55,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                101,
                121,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                137,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                184,
                202,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                147,
                169,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                171,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Patel Krishna is a Information Management Consultant at Fukoku. You can contact he/she at daniel.martinez@oracle.com or 987-654-9011. Skills: Smart Integration, Server support, Managing user access.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                52,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                56,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                116,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                161,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                142,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                177,
                197,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Duthie Jake is a Front-end Software Developer at ASAP Infosystems Pvt.Ltd. You can contact he/she at emmadavis@google.org or 159-753-1507. Skills: Reporting cadence & dashboard development, Asset and Config Management, Business data synthesis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                101,
                121,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                137,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                190,
                217,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                219,
                242,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                147,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hunter Abbie is a Game Analytics Designer at Novopay Solutions. You can contact he/she at john.doe@amazon.com or 1-555-123-5602. Skills: multi-tiered applications and infrastructure, Data migration and scripting, Native frameworks for desktop applications.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                109,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                211,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                213,
                255,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Constantin Tudor is a Associate-Client Services Proj Mgmt at Indovision Services. You can contact he/she at david_johnson@amazon.net or 987-654-6425. Skills: Data repository management, SaaS products, Sampling techniques.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                57,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                61,
                80,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                108,
                132,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                148,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                158,
                184,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                201,
                220,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                186,
                199,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Begum Syeda is a Full Stack Web/Mobile Developer at ART Affordable Housing F. You can contact he/she at sophiamartinez@oracle.org or 321-654-7606. Skills: Multimedia data systems, PowerCLI, Cyber threat management capabilities and functions.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                76,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                104,
                129,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                133,
                145,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                180,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                190,
                240,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Whitelaw Lynsey is a MSBI - ETL Architect - ETL Designer at Capital Float. You can contact he/she at liam.davis@microsoft.com or 987-654-2196. Skills: AWS S3, ELB, Azure Cloud).",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                60,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                101,
                125,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                141,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                164,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                151,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                159,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Semels Andris is a Learning Consultant at Guardian India Operation. You can contact he/she at michael_brown@intel.net or 159-753-1613. Skills: Software collaboration tools, Magento 2 configuration management, Legal proceedings.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                117,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                133,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                173,
                207,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                209,
                226,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                143,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kotak Divyesh is a Analyst at Red Carpet. You can contact he/she at david_johnson@amazon.net or 321-654-6126. Skills: Banking applications knowledge, Risk assessment and risk management, Online/offline data integration.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                26,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                30,
                40,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                68,
                92,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                96,
                108,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                187,
                218,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                150,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Malviya Nikhil is a Cloud Solution Architect - Advanced Analytics & AI at ICRA. You can contact he/she at sophiamartinez@oracle.org or 321-654-2353. Skills: MAM, Dynamic SIMS), Microsoft SharePoint.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                70,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                74,
                78,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                106,
                131,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                147,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                177,
                197,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                162,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                157,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Merdekawati Syeni is a JPMorgan Chase Institute- Big Data Engineer at Ramoji Film City. You can contact he/she at david_johnson@amazon.net or 1-555-123-4742. Skills: Updating systems, Supervision, Legal document preparation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                66,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                70,
                86,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                114,
                138,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                142,
                156,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                184,
                195,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                197,
                223,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                166,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dohollo Maxime is a HSS Specialist at Wonderchef Home Applianc. You can contact he/she at liam_johnson@intel.net or 321-654-8849. Skills: Emerging Technologies, Convolutional Neural Networks, ACL (Audit Command Language).",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                112,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                128,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                192,
                220,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                161,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hiren Chaudhari is a Manager - Data Manager at Lyrus Life Science. You can contact he/she at janeclark@netflix.org or 321-654-9945. Skills: Risk Assessment Management, Programming languages such as C, Eviction Laws.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                93,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                130,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                201,
                214,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                168,
                199,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                140,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Smith Shakira is a Deputy Chief Information Officer - Data and Information Management at Saudi Airlines Catering. You can contact he/she at liam_smith@amazon.net or 159-753-4201. Skills: Implementing standard engineering practices, BIRST), CDC.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                85,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                89,
                112,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                140,
                161,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                165,
                177,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                187,
                230,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                232,
                238,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                240,
                243,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Whitehead Lewis is a BI Implementation Expert at Neurable. You can contact he/she at danieldavis@tesla.org or 1-555-123-7270. Skills: Analyzing marketing data, Loopback, Fault-Tolerant Software Solutions.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                106,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                124,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                160,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                170,
                203,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Holmes Richard is a Salesforce Admin & Data Systems Manager at Brooks Automation. You can contact he/she at johndavis@adobe.org or 987-654-7932. Skills: Ganglia, Use of electrical and RF test equipment, Root-cause analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                59,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                63,
                80,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                108,
                127,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                143,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                162,
                201,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                203,
                222,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                153,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Braine Sammi is a Account Director at Bel. You can contact he/she at danielmartinez@microsoft.org or 159-753-1507. Skills: Phone systems, MySQL Knowledge, CLI (PowerShell or CMD).",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                41,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                69,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                101,
                113,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                155,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Murzyn Jakub is a Service Development Architect-Allstream at Sodexo. You can contact he/she at michael_hernandez@ibm.net or 159-753-2463. Skills: MDM Integration, Continuous deployment, Financial reconciliation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                57,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                61,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                95,
                120,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                136,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                186,
                210,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                184,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                146,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Pearson Tom is a HUMAN RESOURCES ASSISTANT at Sonata Software. You can contact he/she at jane.lee@amazon.com or 159-753-3141. Skills: DVD/BluRay/VHS Players, MS Word, Standard computer operating systems.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                89,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                124,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                202,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Chris Hargreaves Amy Hargreaves is a Intern - IT Operations (Fall 2018) at Lamprell. You can contact he/she at emily.brown@tesla.com or 987-654-2113. Skills: Formulating business intelligence reports, Test case creation, Education.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                31,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                37,
                71,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                75,
                83,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                111,
                132,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                148,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                201,
                219,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                221,
                230,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                199,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Greig Beth is a RESEARCH STUDY ASSISTANT at CES. You can contact he/she at emma_davis@ibm.net or 321-654-4827. Skills: Distributed data processing systems, Data Review and Analysis, Use of portable power tools.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                93,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                97,
                109,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                119,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                180,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                182,
                209,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Begum Syeda is a Artificial Intelligence (AI) Engineer at Wellington Management. You can contact he/she at emilyclark@microsoft.org or 1-555-123-4079. Skills: System Simulation, Audio Teleconferencing, SDLC methodologies.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                58,
                79,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                107,
                131,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                149,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                202,
                220,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                159,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                178,
                200,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Peters Caroline is a Program Manager - School Counseling - 1.0 FTE at Sovereign Pharma. You can contact he/she at michael.lee@ibm.com or 1-555-123-4764. Skills: Architecture, Symantec End-Point Protection, TOGAF Certification.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                66,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                70,
                86,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                114,
                133,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                137,
                151,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                175,
                204,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                161,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                206,
                225,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Taggart Dominic is a VP Cloud Operations at Seagate. You can contact he/she at emily_clark@google.net or 159-753-6150. Skills: **Related to Education:** All Technical Skills, Instructional Leadership, Fixture alignment.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                117,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                175,
                199,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                201,
                218,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ritchie Jay is a RCIS - Database Analyst at SMR Automotive Systems I. You can contact he/she at emilyhernandez@adobe.org or 159-753-2904. Skills: Computing and data services, Programming in C++, Optimization methods.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                96,
                120,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                136,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                146,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                175,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                195,
                215,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dawson Paul is a Circulation Supervisor at Gulf Petrochemical Servi. You can contact he/she at jane.doe@intel.com or 321-654-9945. Skills: Network communication protocols, Development and implementation of best practices, Security Auditing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                95,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                222,
                239,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                220,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
