[
    {
        "text": "Meet Griffin Carl - 3d graphic designer @ NeST Information Technol. Reach at universal@emirates.net.ae Call 159-753-9849 Proficient in cross platform experience.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                120,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Potts Potar - consumer & community banking compliance data analyst associate @ Saraca Laboratories. Email at vmbhatia@panda-uae.com Tel: 159-753-2350 Proficient in multi factor authentication implementation, application coding.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                81,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                84,
                103,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                114,
                136,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                142,
                154,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                169,
                211,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                213,
                231,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Myatt Lucy, a java full affiliated with Gvk Power & Infrastructu, Email: najib@foxconn.ae Phone number 321-654-3365 Technical skills: gtfs, microservices architecture.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                23,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                73,
                89,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                140,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kinnear Ross is a seasoned associate data scientist working at ICICI Bank. Email at james@rshme.co.ae Call 159-753-1613 Experienced in remote access design.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                63,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                119,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                155,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Walker Michelle is a seasoned data analyst working at Mawana Sugars. Email: bhavesh.desai@jotundxb.ae Phone: 987-654-1056 Experienced in stock receipts handling, business requirements understanding, design dveelopment.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                30,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                76,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                162,
                197,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Harrower Declan - inventory data analyst @ Kronos Solutions. Email at fimran@afcarililon.ae Tel: 987-654-4951 Proficient in display programmatic partners research, threat mdoelling.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                102,
                114,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                129,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Synowiecki Kamil - research intern @ Rural Electrification Co. email habshanh@adco.ae Phone: 321-654-3365 Proficient in study accrual management, iscp, cvs.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                74,
                90,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                98,
                110,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                125,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                151,
                155,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                157,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Penfold Ric - solution architect big data @ S & T Engineers (p). Email at gulfdata@gdia.e Tel: 159-753-9275 Proficient in advanced sql siklls, ssytems understanding.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                100,
                112,
                "PHONE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Kerry Jayson, a classified cyber security analyst sr from Sify Technologies, Email at rildub01@emirates.net.ae Call 1-555-123-4079 Key expertise: clarity.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                66,
                83,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                118,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                138,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                154,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet O Londraigh Mattiu - data warehouse programming specialist @ Arth Design Build. Phone number 159-753-7098 Proficient in cluster management, scholarly publishing projects.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                23,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                63,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                66,
                83,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                98,
                110,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                125,
                143,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                145,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Windcare India employs Anderson Terry as a data scientist job. Call 1-555-123-5478 Skills: software defined radio.",
        "entities": [
            [
                23,
                37,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                43,
                61,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                14,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                68,
                82,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                91,
                113,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Badham Sophie is a seasoned information technology specialist working at Groupe Seb. email ajayd@gulffidelity.com Call 987-654-3449 Experienced in githubo r other version control platforms.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                61,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                73,
                83,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                91,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                131,
                "PHONE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Garside Mark, a specialist roles from Zuari Cement, Email: mktg@jafza.ae Phone: 321-654-2279 Key expertise: build processes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                116,
                131,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Abbas Ali, a weekend security analyst from Arabian Construction Com, Email: maic@emiratesbank.ae Tel: 159-753-1731 Key expertise: python script.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                104,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                138,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Wipro Infrastructure Eng employs Rafferty Rosie as a associate quality engineer. Reach at nabeeldr@emirates.net.ae Tel: 321-654-3755 Skills: audit plans, design concepts.",
        "entities": [
            [
                33,
                47,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                53,
                79,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                24,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                154,
                169,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact West Lucy, a escalation engineer from Hindalco Industries, email hr@rmicorp.cmo Call 987-654-7868 Key expertise: service providers, mathematical and statistical concepts, subpoena generation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                93,
                105,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                121,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                140,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                198,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "P R Packaging employs Williams Natasha as a sr assoc software engineer. Email at info@olivesecurity.com Skills: transition management, network device health checking.",
        "entities": [
            [
                22,
                38,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                44,
                70,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                13,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                103,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                133,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Williamson Andy - analytic solutions @ Polyplastics. Email at recruitemnt@hmc.org.qa Proficient in strategic goal setting, experience supporting saas products.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                104,
                126,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                128,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Palmer Sheila - senior devops engineer @ Hilex. Phone: 321-654-4637 Proficient in ad ops.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                72,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                87,
                93,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Sowerby Kev - clinic data analyst @ Milkbasket. Email at itcauh@itc.ae Phone number 987-654-7868 Proficient in meatdata modeling techniques.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                75,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                89,
                101,
                "PHONE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Richardson Sophie currently works as a product data management specialist at Aakash Institute. Email at plastcos@emirates.net.ae Phone number 987-654-4144 Core skills include transportation and logistics operations, operating office machines.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                39,
                73,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                77,
                93,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                104,
                128,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                142,
                154,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                175,
                214,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                216,
                241,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Donnelly Sharon Anne, a computer hardware engineer from Maven Infotech, email avarma@airarabia.com Key expertise: react, transcad.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                28,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                32,
                58,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                64,
                78,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                106,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Pearson Tom - sr machine learning researcher @ Aujas Networks. No contact provided. Proficient in manufacturing process optimization, analytical algorithsm.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                103,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Ramsamy Palmeshiven, a field software support engineer from Ramco Systems, Email: shankjay@emiartes.net.ae Phone number 1-555-123-9159 Key expertise: uat coordination.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                27,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                62,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                68,
                81,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                128,
                142,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                158,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Simpson John is a seasoned asst project manager working at Brandix India Apparel Ci. Email: dantha@eim.ae Call 1-555-123-5026 Experienced in itil v3 methodologies, apache flink.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                83,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                92,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                164,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Gudgin Louise currently works as a cloud native application architect at Jindal Fittings. email pmg@eim.ae Tel: 321-654-5444 Core skills include website design industry standards, macros, materials development.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                35,
                69,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                73,
                88,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                96,
                106,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                124,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                145,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                180,
                186,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                188,
                209,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Bintley Chris (computer repair technician at SeQuent Scientific) Reach at dennies999@gmail.com Phone number 159-753-6188 They specialize in continuous delivery, test environment management, business process model.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                27,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                134,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                154,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                175,
                202,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                204,
                226,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ali Shuaib currently works as a technical sales support at US Polo Assn. Email: rms_uae@emirates.net.ae Core skills include physical, through e mail.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                32,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                80,
                103,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                132,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                134,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Scally Tony, a records analyst from Shiva Engineering Servic, email medhatsolimon@tecs.com.eg Call 1-555-123-6372 Key expertise: pricing analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                76,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Wylie Toby is a seasoned developer application services working at Kentz Engineers & Constr. email icasanova@iberincointl.com Phone number 321-654-5216 Experienced in ec2, process scalability, cloud certifications.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                67,
                91,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                99,
                125,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                139,
                151,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                167,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                191,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                193,
                213,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Wizcraft International E employs Cleaver Kirsty as a quantitative analyst. Email: ignacio.blanco@idom.com Call 1-555-123-3589 Skills: lms administration.",
        "entities": [
            [
                33,
                47,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                53,
                73,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                24,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Pisani Nicolas, a terminal custodian affiliated with Western Coalfields, email khodari@emirates.net.ae Phone: 159-753-4308 Technical skills: information security controls.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Fear Jane currently works as a sr manager data governance at Armed Forces Tribunal. Reach at fb@dubaigrandhotel.ae Call 321-654-3725 Core skills include dusting, knowledge and use of personal computers, due diligence.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                57,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                61,
                82,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                93,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                153,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                162,
                201,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                203,
                216,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Smith Stacie is a seasoned jr systems administrator & desktop support working at Jawed Habib Hair & Beaut. Reach at mumpower1@jvi-global.com Experienced in navigating ambiguity.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                69,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                81,
                105,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                116,
                140,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Brockett Maddie, a survey data analyst from ASK, Phone number 987-654-4700 Key expertise: tableau or cognos, video production.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                23,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                70,
                82,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                98,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                133,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Hodgson Jamie - big data software engineer @ ICSIL. Email at inamdarumar@gmail.com Phone number 159-753-1530 Proficient in iso27001, cucumber automated acceptance test software, social media content development.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                87,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                101,
                113,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                128,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                215,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Baines Jordan - mdm developer @ Cubical Laboratories. Email: jyk.ae@alteratvi-cis.com Tel: 159-753-6188 Proficient in technology and information security risks analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                96,
                108,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Burton Stephen, a real world evidence informatician affiliated with FANUC, email zafco@emirates.net.ae Technical skills: large scale system design, understand and translate business and product questions into analytics projects, payroll.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                68,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                146,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                148,
                227,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                229,
                236,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kokuyo Camlin employs Tony as a jr developer. email rahim@savrina.ae Phone: 159-753-7431 Skills: managing production sql environments, persistence solutions.",
        "entities": [
            [
                22,
                26,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                32,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                13,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                52,
                68,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                76,
                88,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                97,
                133,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Westrip Jacy currently works as a lab support administrator at O2 Spa. No contact provided. Core skills include knowledge of data analysis and intervention strategies, big data datasets.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                34,
                59,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                63,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                112,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                168,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Duthie Jake, a mdm developer affiliated with Grownmind Education Serv, email s.halal@futurepipe.com Tel: 987-654-2113 Technical skills: knowledge of online services applications.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                28,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                99,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                117,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Milano De Souza Larissa - sr software developer @ Baker Hughes. No contact provided. Proficient in aws and azure cloud, sap data services, test driven development.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                28,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                52,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                55,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                104,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                144,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Hannah Cain, a business strategy consultant from My Home Constructions, email emailsales@safetyplus.qa Key expertise: system malfunction root cause analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                78,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Acres Mcguigan Amber currently works as a msbi at Datawind Innovations. Email at a.elkhatib@tessco-uneco.com Core skills include geo spatial analytics.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                42,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mannan Sameen is a seasoned full stack developer working at SPS Apollo Hospital. Email at binzahoor@rediffmail.com Phone: 321-654-2204 Experienced in alteryx data blending tool.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                60,
                79,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                134,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                150,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Laity Demelza currently works as a recruiting associate at Shirodkar Preci Comp. email asqalan@emirates.net.ae Core skills include data documentation, datasync, oem software maintenance.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                35,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                79,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                87,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                151,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                161,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jordan Rose is a seasoned chief information security officer working at Hitachi Solutions. email reshna.m@megavision.ae Phone: 987-654-2036 Experienced in database reporting tools, command and control architecture, mysql database performance tuning.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                72,
                89,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                97,
                119,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                155,
                179,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                181,
                213,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                215,
                248,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Constantin Tudor is a seasoned leasing consultant working at ERPA. Email at s112464@emirates.com Experienced in cloud infrastructure.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                61,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                76,
                96,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                132,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Gomes Dos Santos Isaac, a global data insight & analytics from Jayem Warehousing, Email: afshin_salehi@msn.com Phone: 1-555-123-5288 Key expertise: printers, marketing automation platforms.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                30,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                34,
                65,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                71,
                88,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                97,
                118,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                140,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                156,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                166,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Horrocks Ashley Hernandez is a seasoned trainer working at Royal Research. Reach at interclr@emirates.net.ae Phone number 321-654-4302 Experienced in functional architecture design.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                40,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                134,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                150,
                180,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Weaver Ben (software dev engineer at AARGEE STAFFING SERVICES) Email at younesiraki@amplus.ma Tel: 1-555-123-2215 They specialize in etls and data federation pipelines, netbackup administration.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                24,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                207,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Brennan Clair, a warehouse lead from Cordlife Sciences India, Email at bitaaa@bitafzc.com Call 321-654-4657 Key expertise: iso 27001.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Smith Robert, a deep learning computer architect affiliated with Ginni Filaments, Phone number 321-654-3365 Technical skills: custmoer relationship management, expertise in excel and data analysis, continuous delivery and deployment tools.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                65,
                80,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                95,
                107,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                160,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                198,
                238,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Marie Louise - java full stack developer @ ProConnect Supply Chain. Reach at camille.abusaba@acetrna.com Proficient in luiig.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Porteck India Infoservic employs Mctaggart Karen as a admissions consultant. Email: pankja@unc.ae Tel: 159-753-9006 Skills: data warehousing technologies, overtime management, client management.",
        "entities": [
            [
                33,
                48,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                54,
                75,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                24,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                103,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                124,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                176,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Miah Alamin currently works as a dyson stylist at Eidiko Systems Integrato. Email: masood@alghurairgroup.com Call 159-753-4470 Core skills include software and hardware support, troubleshooting support, problem solving tools.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                33,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                126,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                178,
                201,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                203,
                224,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Webb Cameron currently works as a business intelligence financial analyst at Hipower Support Center. Reach at naz.awan@buid.ac.ae Call 987-654-9011 Core skills include nispom.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                34,
                73,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                77,
                99,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                110,
                129,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                147,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                168,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Whitehead Lewis, a hr business analytics manager affiliated with Snowcem Paints, Call 159-753-5061 Technical skills: cloud dashboards.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                65,
                79,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                98,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                117,
                133,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Marie Louise, a full stack javascript developer from Gala Precision Engineeri, Reach at ebamps@emiratse.net.ae Call 321-654-2279 Key expertise: sanitatio nmanagement, bi tools develompent, event participation measurement.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                61,
                85,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                124,
                136,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                197,
                228,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Guest Ilondon, a research engineer affiliated with State Street Syntel, email kgaweesh@uaeu.ac.ae Call 159-753-8993 Technical skills: system upgrades and maintenance, hibernate.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                78,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Turkoglu Semih (operations manager at Annora Pharma) email ameen@clubhotel.com Phone number 987-654-6707 They specialize in udp, lab and system debug, baisc math skills.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                28,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                30,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                73,
                92,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                118,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                138,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                143,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Wetoszka David - sr regulatory writer @ Responsive Industries. Email: travelmanager@aerovista.ae Phone number 1-555-123-8231 Proficient in fishbone and pareto charts, active directory integration, data quality audits.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                144,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                200,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                202,
                221,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Fox Iri - software developer ray optics @ Adani Ports and Special. Phone: 1-555-123-3194 Proficient in scikit learn, os command line operation, hipaa and privacy guidelines.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                108,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Eden Aaron is a seasoned learning specialist working at Saudi Telecom Company. Email at dbaadm@ccgate.apl.com Phone number 321-654-1908 Experienced in system support, relational and columnar database stores, product requirements definition.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                56,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                109,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                135,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                151,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                206,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                208,
                239,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Mccormick Carole, a revenue collector from Next Retail, Email: qatar@awicompany.com Phone number 987-654-6707 Key expertise: quality tolos.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                24,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                71,
                91,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                117,
                "PHONE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I Yogi Technical Service employs Williams Nathan as a backend python software engineer. Reach at FINANCE@MAJESTICA.E Tel: 321-654-6340 Skills: srevice level architecture development, webiste analysis, literature review.",
        "entities": [
            [
                33,
                48,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                54,
                86,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                24,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                122,
                134,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                201,
                218,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Avineon India employs Hellyer Holly as a mysql database administrator. Call 1-555-123-9576 Skills: nis environment.",
        "entities": [
            [
                22,
                35,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                41,
                69,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                13,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                76,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                99,
                114,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Williams Jessica (computer repair technician at Envision Enterprise Solu) Email: junaidfarooq@gmail.ocm Phone: 321-654-4657 They specialize in other platforms, software development kits.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                30,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                32,
                58,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                62,
                86,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                125,
                137,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                157,
                172,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                174,
                199,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Watts James is a seasoned background investigator working at Megafine Pharma. Email at rkhatib@nes-lb.com Tel: 987-654-3981 Experienced in information analytics.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                61,
                76,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                87,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Jarvis Nicole (remote help desk tech at Royal Sundaram General I) Email at dkshah@bdsa.e Tel: 987-654-4996 They specialize in design engineering, data product design and delivery.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                27,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                78,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                108,
                120,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                160,
                192,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tetley Will is a seasoned liquid studios working at Mywish Marketplaces. Reach at arujnartgallery@gmail.com Experienced in file archiivng, healthcare experience.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                139,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Oakley Gemma (service order coordinator at Shri Mata Vaishno Devi N) Email at recruitment@bmj-qatar.com Tel: 321-654-3290 They specialize in x86 hardware, canalyzer, excel proficiency.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                26,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                53,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                81,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                92,
                117,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                135,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                155,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                169,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                180,
                197,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Herbut Jacek (billing database specialist at WALGREENS) email yamamoto@sanyogulf.com Tel: 159-753-5150 They specialize in vulnerability management scanners.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                26,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                76,
                98,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                169,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Holmes Richard is a seasoned software release engineer working at Sahara Prime City. Email: mac-ja@emirates.net.ae Experienced in airline revenue management, deploying, health care trends research.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                66,
                83,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                92,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                130,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                169,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Esko Die Casting employs Isaac Paul as a b36. Email at bisher.barazi@idfc.ae Skills: sdlc in an agile environment, wbe analytics assessment.",
        "entities": [
            [
                25,
                35,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                41,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                16,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                113,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Василева Милена (trainer at Niit Foundation) Email at amitagni2@gmail.com Phone number 159-753-6399 They specialize in denodo platform control center, java server faces.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                29,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                68,
                87,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                101,
                113,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                165,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Badham Sophie, a senior software engineer in test affiliated with SML Isuzu, Email at hmostafa@eim.ae Technical skills: data science basics, aircraft maintenance.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                66,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                141,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Moore Cameron, a data visualization specialist affiliated with Shri Bajrang Power & Isp, Call 987-654-9882 Technical skills: contarcting.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                63,
                87,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                106,
                "PHONE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Grant Jentierose is a seasoned sr full stack software engineer working at Tops Security. Email at tba@diwan-capital.com Experienced in cisco unified communications manager, servicenow.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                62,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                74,
                87,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                98,
                119,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                173,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "CDS employs Jarvis Nicole as a identity architect. Reach at simnet1@emirates.net.ae Phone: 321-654-6253 Skills: consumer electronics delivery, pega, relational database tools.",
        "entities": [
            [
                12,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                3,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                91,
                103,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                112,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                143,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Murzyn Jakub currently works as a enterprise cloud sales rep at Deloitte. Reach at hr@tryphotelauh.com Phone: 321-654-3876 Core skills include mass id theft regulation 201 cmr 17, adoption of new technologies, security architecture improvement.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                34,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                64,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                180,
                208,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                210,
                243,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hudson Sarah currently works as a software release engineer at Scholarly. Email: joban.c@habtoorengg.ae Tel: 159-753-8993 Core skills include webstorm.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                34,
                59,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                63,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                103,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "BeWo Technologies employs Obyrne Justin as a executive director. Phone number 321-654-7813 Skills: demonstrated knowledge of active directory, test case review.",
        "entities": [
            [
                26,
                39,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                45,
                63,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                17,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                78,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                99,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                143,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Meyer Kyle, a chief data scientist solution architect from Wizard e, Reach at msabah@villa-moda.com Key expertise: computational tehcniques, data integrator tool.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                61,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                67,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                169,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kuczynski Nikki currently works as a data center operations engineer at Pride Purple Group. Email at peter.stelzer@wuerth.com Phone number 321-654-5444 Core skills include excel vba, product ownership.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                37,
                68,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                72,
                90,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                101,
                125,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                139,
                151,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                172,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                200,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Andrew Holly, a full stack mobile engineer from EASi Technologies, email info@finanzoptimierung.de Phone number 159-753-5732 Key expertise: devops tools, warehouse distribution and storage operations.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                56,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                106,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                148,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                162,
                207,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Sophia Kew-Moss Rene - financial business analyst @ K L University. Email: cplus@emirates.net.ae Call 159-753-5836 Proficient in improve database backups and test recoverability, visual object classification.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                80,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                119,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                184,
                212,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kezia Princess is a seasoned telecom analyst working at S Mobile Devices. Email: info@hydroseal.ca Phone: 1-555-123-4742 Experienced in enterprise data management strategies, audio engineering.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                56,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                98,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                120,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                175,
                192,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tighe Caron is a seasoned compliance analyst working at Cummins Power Generation. Tel: 987-654-9882 Experienced in property accountability.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                56,
                80,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                87,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                115,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Shivam Autotech employs Whitelaw Lynsey as a supply chain integration developer. email sylvia.schoonderbeek@gmail.com Tel: 1-555-123-7092 Skills: security monitoring and access control, video processing for launch range activities.",
        "entities": [
            [
                24,
                39,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                45,
                79,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                15,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                87,
                117,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                137,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                146,
                184,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                186,
                230,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mccormick Carole currently works as a expert software engineer at Kaseware. Call 1-555-123-6097 Core skills include ips.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                38,
                62,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                66,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                116,
                119,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "VIP Industries employs Smith Liam as a department administrator. Reach at ayhaoc@emirates.net.ae Phone number 321-654-5525 Skills: basel iii, surveys, edr design.",
        "entities": [
            [
                23,
                33,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                39,
                63,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                14,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                110,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                142,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "JConnect Infotech employs Purser Brooke as a product manager. Email at tariq@i2i-group.com Phone: 159-753-7688 Skills: architecture design for scalability.",
        "entities": [
            [
                26,
                39,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                45,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                17,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                71,
                90,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                98,
                110,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                119,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Twigg Sarah, a staff data scientist from IIC Technologies, Email: wimb@but.be Phone number 987-654-2196 Key expertise: sheets, quality optimization, learning materials organization.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                74,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                99,
                111,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                127,
                133,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                155,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                157,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Hester Jamieleigh, a software engineer for mobile robots from M J Logistic Services, Email at ceo@diamondgroupqatar.com Phone: 1-555-123-6776 Key expertise: modern patterns and practices for the cloud, network and host based log analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                64,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                70,
                91,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                102,
                127,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                149,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                165,
                208,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                210,
                245,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Ball Jake - partner consultant @ Hindustan Steelworks Con. email mudathir@emirates.net.ae Phone: 159-753-5061 Proficient in large scale systems.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                70,
                94,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                114,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                129,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Batliboi employs Turner Sian as a senior artificial intelligence researcher. Reach at alvin@zelan.com.my Phone: 321-654-5662 Skills: construction management, data driven reliability, video and graphics technologies.",
        "entities": [
            [
                17,
                28,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                34,
                75,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                8,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                104,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                124,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                214,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Beadle Natalie currently works as a media analyst at Unisoft Infotech. Call 987-654-9882 Core skills include design an darchitectural concepts, employee data analytcis, cybersecurity policies.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                36,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                76,
                88,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                169,
                191,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Malviya Nikhil - integration support analyst @ NXP Semiconductors. Reach at mulville@mailme.ae Phone number 159-753-5150 Proficient in minnesota government access, network and server maintenance, pega.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                99,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                169,
                199,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                201,
                205,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Simpson Fred currently works as a global account manager at Eltech Appliances. Email at ahir123@rediffmail.com Phone number 159-753-8412 Core skills include majorn etworking, benefitc harging.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                34,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                60,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                136,
                "PHONE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Central Reserve Police F employs Gohil Kuldeepsinh as a finance analyst. No contact provided. Skills: securtiy incidents troubleshooting, cross platform development, systems security.",
        "entities": [
            [
                33,
                50,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                56,
                71,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                24,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                138,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                166,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Close Tracie is a seasoned trademark administrator working at Steelcast. No contact provided. Experienced in retail standards understanding, 11g and 12c.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                62,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                109,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                141,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Norman Jenny - business expert @ Euclid Infotech. Tel: 1-555-123-3684 Proficient in apis, financial operating model development, structural steel detailing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                53,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                74,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                89,
                93,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                95,
                132,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                134,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Elliott Mikala (sr it administrator at S Mobile Devices) Phone number 321-654-1674 They specialize in software versioning tools, data management software.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                28,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                30,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                96,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                116,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                143,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Fear Jane currently works as a chief of staff at Edward Food Research and. Phone number 159-753-5061 Core skills include java extensibility.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                121,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Marsden Philip - senior full @ Universal Corporation. email info@unitedsupplies.co.ae Call 159-753-1072 Proficient in loss prevention, knowledge of sacda systems and ability to read network drawings.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                65,
                90,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                96,
                108,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Winter James is a seasoned law enforcement intelligence analyst working at Lotus Dairy Products. Email: johannes@emirates.net.ae Experienced in safety regulations enforcement.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                63,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                75,
                95,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                104,
                128,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                144,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Indian Drugs and Pharmac employs Lewis Melissa as a operational intelligence analyst. Email: deepak@technocare.ae Tel: 987-654-1056 Skills: rest web services, end to end data pipeline solutions.",
        "entities": [
            [
                33,
                46,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                52,
                84,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                24,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                93,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                131,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                159,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kle Jade is a seasoned sr data warehouse engineer working at Romsons Group Of Industr. Email: purplenezz@gmail.com Experienced in curriculum management, relational and dimnesional modeling.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                61,
                85,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                130,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Norman Jenny is a seasoned microsoft mim developer working at Spectrum. Reach at a.floyds@emirates.net.ae Experienced in shipping an dreceiving, vbscript, systems of record definition.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                62,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                145,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Garside Mark - technical architect @ Quatrro Mortgage Solutio. Email at vbagaria@fns.com.au Phone number 987-654-2113 Proficient in ad hoc functionality, sap hana database design, data science projects.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                96,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                159,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                185,
                206,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Bloom Abbey, a data center infrastructure administrator from Govind Milk & Milk Produ, Call 987-654-5961 Key expertise: it security network infrastructure design and implementation, intermediate web programming skills, trade recording.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                63,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                69,
                93,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                100,
                112,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                128,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                190,
                225,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                227,
                242,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Wardle Callum, a deep learning performance architect from Dr Oetker, Reach at bibin@autobahnuae.com Tel: 987-654-6364 Key expertise: reporting tools like tableau, database clustering.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                66,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                169,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                171,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Navin Eve currently works as a software development itam engineer at Skylark Infra Engineerin. Email: admin@almahaschools.org.qa Phone: 159-753-3458 Core skills include d mlt echniques, lean agile methodologies, axure.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                65,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                69,
                93,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                102,
                128,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                148,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                186,
                210,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                212,
                217,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mills Rhonda, a warehouse expediter affiliated with ShopX, Email: jose.gumabao@bsbgulf.com Phone number 159-753-7688 Technical skills: cloud based prorgamming, hbaes, customer interaction.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                90,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                167,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Stellar Information Tech employs Murphy-Fawcett Zoe as a senior network security analyst for information technology. Email: charlse@create905.com Tel: 321-654-1969 Skills: variance analysis, classo f service.",
        "entities": [
            [
                33,
                51,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                57,
                115,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                24,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                151,
                163,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                172,
                189,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Gomes Dos Santos Isaac (sr sw engineer at Sony India Software Cent) Email at a.venkat.y@gmail.com Call 159-753-6636 They specialize in i2tms.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                36,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                38,
                52,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                56,
                80,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                91,
                111,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                149,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Jones-Campbell Steven (servicenow systems administrator at Hindustan Coca Cola Beve) Email at contact@alfahadgroup.com Phone: 159-753-6636 They specialize in customer feedback analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                35,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                37,
                69,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                73,
                97,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                108,
                132,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                140,
                152,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                172,
                198,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Marie Ellie - servicenow intern @ Engineering Technology Associates. Email at meher.fazal@fairmont.com Tel: 987-654-3320 Proficient in gpu services.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Fell Ashleigh (sales engineer at Bhaskar Industries) Email: takdc@takuae.com Phone number 987-654-3653 They specialize in information technology strategic planning.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                27,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                74,
                90,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kanani Shrey, a data center operations engineer affiliated with Institute of Computer Ac, Email: abdulbasit@wallstreet.ae Call 321-654-3755 Technical skills: database upgrades and migrations, hr programs oversight, understanding of complex information.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                64,
                88,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                97,
                121,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                158,
                190,
                "SKILL"
