[
    {
        "text": "Dickson John is a sitecore developer at Park Avenue. You can contact them at janelee@facebook.org or 159-753-4201. Skills: recognition and classification algorithms, ability to navigate between programs by using shortcut keys, big data expertise.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                101,
                113,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                166,
                225,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                227,
                245,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dhengale Pramod is a hr & quality assurance coordinator at Thapar University. You can contact them at liamdoe@netflix.org or 987-654-6651. Skills: user story development, tabular and graphical data representation, server maintenance plans.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                76,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                102,
                121,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                137,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                169,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                171,
                212,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                214,
                238,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bagworth Laura is a plc software engineer at BGR Energy Systems. You can contact them at sophia_martinez@intel.net or 159-753-7875. Skills: architecture, desktop productivity suites, research experience in statistics.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                89,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                130,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                154,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                216,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Divito Nanette is a it ia consultant jn at Hero Motors. You can contact them at michael_hernandez@ibm.net or 159-753-6631. Skills: broadcast equipment knowledge, ibm information governance catalog, dhcp troubleshooting.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                80,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                162,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                198,
                218,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Cartledge Paul is a inspector at Nippon Konpo India. You can contact them at michaellee@netflix.org or 987-654-6373. Skills: security protocol development, compliance monitoring, methodologic approaches.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                99,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                125,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                202,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Fatima Nusrat is a systems engineer at Olive Bar & Kitchen. You can contact them at michaelbrown@ibm.org or 321-654-1908. Skills: cluster management, new database technologies evaluation, engineering design patterns articulation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                104,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                120,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                150,
                186,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                188,
                228,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Vidler Adam is a data analyst at Uber. You can contact them at davidsmith@netflix.org or 1-555-123-2730. Skills: a.i., progress reports preparation, javascript or similar scripting language.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                37,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                89,
                103,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                113,
                117,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                189,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Fearn Lauren is a software engineer trainee at Batchmaster Software. You can contact them at olivia_lee@amazon.net or 159-753-4559. Skills: digital and hard copy drawings management, business operations management, workflow design.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                93,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                130,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                213,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                215,
                230,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Loks Thomas is a community consultant at Rockland Hospital. You can contact them at jane.davis@amazon.com or 1-555-123-5602. Skills: application systems, managing, analytic functions.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                154,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                164,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Vasava Sandip is a computer scientist at Avon Beauty Products. You can contact them at emily.martinez@adobe.com or 159-753-7895. Skills: couchdb, jobsite audits, partnership and licensing assessment.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                87,
                111,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                144,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                146,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                162,
                198,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Heatley Adam is a technical data analyst at Natco Pharma. You can contact them at liamdavis@microsoft.org or 321-654-9054. Skills: designing and developing complex distributed systems in aws, yardi, understanding of devops principles.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                192,
                197,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                199,
                233,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Marcel Cristian is a software verification engineer at Trantor. You can contact them at daniel.hernandez@adobe.com or 321-654-5944. Skills: minnesota justice information systems, rest api, system management.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                55,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                130,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                189,
                206,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Doherty Paulie is a data architect & etl manager at Valkyrie Enterprises. You can contact them at sophia_davis@oracle.net or 1-555-123-2475. Skills: developing and publishing example code, knowledge of avalaras product and global tax compliance, sourcing techniques.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                98,
                121,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                149,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                189,
                244,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                246,
                265,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Smith Liam is a principal data scientist at Kharafi National. You can contact them at michael.clark@oracle.com or 321-654-4827. Skills: intercom, oceana, brain imaging.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                126,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                144,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                146,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                154,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Khan Asif is a quality assurance specialist at Koye Pharmaceuticals. You can contact them at michael.smith@adobe.com or 987-654-7868. Skills: use of diagnostic test equipment, linux based software, market metrics.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                93,
                116,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                176,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                198,
                212,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mcdonnell Conor is a control systems engineer at Government of West Benga. You can contact them at emilyclark@netflix.org or 1-555-123-2475. Skills: image editing tools, portfolio analysis, security protocol compliance.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                99,
                121,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                149,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                170,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                190,
                218,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bellis Lee is a software engineer senior consultant level at Kanohar Electricals. You can contact them at john_davis@oracle.net or 321-654-5662. Skills: slas, cloud computing, thin client technologies.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                57,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                61,
                80,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                106,
                127,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                143,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                153,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                159,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                176,
                200,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rzepnicki Marek is a mnjis assistant director at Varun Beverages. You can contact them at daniel.brown@netflix.com or 1-555-123-1154. Skills: ip telephony systems, process skills, research database management.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                164,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                180,
                208,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Garnerr Nicolaa is a application developer analyst at The Peerless General Fin. You can contact them at david_martinez@facebook.net or 159-753-1011. Skills: system center, case manager, monitoring key performance indicators.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                78,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                104,
                131,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                147,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                157,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                184,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                186,
                223,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Thrussell-Day Stephanie is a virtualization architect at Mahesh Tutorials. You can contact them at jane_johnson@amazon.net or 321-654-7044. Skills: multi line telephone console operation, multi modal transportation planning, it security network infrastructure design and implementation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                23,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                53,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                99,
                122,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                138,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                148,
                186,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                188,
                223,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                225,
                285,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rob Phil is a cloud integration developer at Lennox India Technology. You can contact them at olivia.smith@ibm.com or 159-753-5732. Skills: application migration methodologies, knowledge of autism and early development, reliability engineering.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                130,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                177,
                218,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                220,
                243,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Banks Lois is a amundsen consulting at Reliance Footprint. You can contact them at oliviadoe@tesla.org or 1-555-123-4079. Skills: traceability management, data security controls, servers and storage.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                120,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                198,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kle Jade is a data quality analyst at The Phoenix Mills. You can contact them at jane.clark@amazon.com or 159-753-7114. Skills: spacy, iam products, risk and fraud investigation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                118,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                128,
                133,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Miller John is a youth recreation program manager at Rhydburg Pharmaceuticals. You can contact them at emily.johnson@oracle.com or 1-555-123-2481. Skills: archer grc knowledge, oracle package knowledge, political science.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                103,
                127,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                145,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                155,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                177,
                201,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                203,
                220,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Johnson Shane is a data management & integration engineer at Daebu Automotive Seat. You can contact them at johnwilson@tesla.org or 159-753-1731. Skills: characterizing fet devices, resource scheduling, biochemistry.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                57,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                61,
                82,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                108,
                128,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                132,
                144,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                154,
                180,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                182,
                201,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                203,
                215,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ryan Jane is a consumer & community banking compliance data analyst associate at Sodexo. You can contact them at oliviadoe@tesla.org or 159-753-4201. Skills: machine learning and computer vision, synthesizing data, technical product analyst.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                77,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                81,
                87,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                113,
                132,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                148,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                158,
                194,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                196,
                213,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                215,
                240,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tseng Claire is a analytics manager at Suryalakshmi Cotton Mill. You can contact them at michaelbrown@tesla.org or 321-654-1969. Skills: microsoft environments, repair of technology systems, business operations optimization.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                89,
                111,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                161,
                189,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                191,
                223,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Thupsee Richard is a sales operations specialist at Mcnally Sayaji Engineeri. You can contact them at emily_clark@amazon.net or 159-753-3141. Skills: consumer behavior analysis, intelligent transportation systems, security processes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                76,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                102,
                124,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                128,
                140,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                150,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                178,
                212,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                214,
                232,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dunn Bird Sean is a asset protection associate at Degustibus Hospitality. You can contact them at davidclark@adobe.org or 321-654-3290. Skills: asp.net mvc, bi tools, configuration monitoring.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                98,
                118,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                134,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                144,
                155,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                157,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                191,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Campbell Billy is a entry level to senior level software developers at Jaquar. You can contact them at emmadavis@intel.org or 321-654-4827. Skills: experience with customer experience technologies, knowledge of linux systems in the public cloud, maintaining copiers.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                67,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                71,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                103,
                122,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                138,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                148,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                198,
                244,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                246,
                265,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bower Sarah is a web project manager at Gruh Finance. You can contact them at daniel_martinez@google.net or 159-753-1011. Skills: batch automation tasks, deal structuring, backup and recovery operations.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                52,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                78,
                104,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                120,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                154,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                202,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Barbour Sally is a price strategist at Indiafilings. You can contact them at danielhernandez@adobe.org or 321-654-8849. Skills: datacom development in c language, intermediate pol telecommunication officer certification, deploying new systems.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                118,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                128,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                219,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                221,
                242,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bryce Shauna is a program support assistant at Deepak Fasteners. You can contact them at david_davis@facebook.net or 1-555-123-4079. Skills: work order management, materials expertise, ecmascript.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                89,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                131,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                164,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                185,
                195,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Basikiti Varaidzo Pamcakes is a api services at Beshenich Muir & Associates Llc. You can contact them at michaelbrown@tesla.org or 321-654-4657. Skills: custom template creation, relational database development, vagrant.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                26,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                32,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                79,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                105,
                127,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                143,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                153,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                210,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                212,
                219,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sheldon Philip is a data analytics manager at Webtrackker Technology. You can contact them at emmasmith@netflix.org or 1-555-123-7590. Skills: os support, troubleshooting and performance tuning, presentation preparation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                115,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                133,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                195,
                219,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dean Jasmine is a advocacy intern at Electrical Manufacturing. You can contact them at sophiamartinez@ibm.org or 159-753-5061. Skills: specification writing, electronics knowledge, design development.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                87,
                109,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                179,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                181,
                199,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rennie Caroline is a hr technology program director supervisor at Endeavor Careers. You can contact them at emily.johnson@oracle.com or 1-555-123-3194. Skills: google products, lean concepts, update.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                62,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                66,
                82,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                108,
                132,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                150,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                160,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                177,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                192,
                198,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Nicol John Paul is a customer service agent at Excel Industries. You can contact them at emmajohnson@microsoft.org or 321-654-2353. Skills: integrations and apis development, r or python, cybersecurity requirements.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                89,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                130,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                175,
                186,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                188,
                214,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Porter Ann is a professional services architect at Tv18 Broadcast. You can contact them at michaelbrown@oracle.org or 159-753-8635. Skills: rd party connectivity, object oriented databases, knowledge of technologies.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                91,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                130,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                190,
                215,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mills Rhonda is a technology sales consultant at NSIC. You can contact them at david.lee@amazon.com or 321-654-6053. Skills: user replication policies, spreadsheet proficiency, benefit charging.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                53,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                99,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                125,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                177,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Williams Brandon is a cloud devops engineer at Loylty Rewardz Mngt. You can contact them at sophia_martinez@intel.net or 321-654-5444. Skills: e commerce retail basics knowledge, value stream mapping, inventory reports.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                92,
                117,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                133,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                199,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                201,
                218,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "King Stephenrichard is a data center facility operations chemical engineer at Skechers. You can contact them at jane_martinez@tesla.net or 159-753-6654. Skills: entity relationship diagrams, ability to create and edit written communication, customer training.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                74,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                78,
                86,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                112,
                135,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                139,
                151,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                161,
                189,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                191,
                239,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                241,
                258,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Wilding Aaron is a data quality analyst at International Combustion. You can contact them at davidclark@adobe.org or 1-555-123-5285. Skills: operating kitchen equipment, strong written and verbal communications skills, fast and accurate transaction processing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                93,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                131,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                170,
                217,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                219,
                259,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kotak Divyesh is a technology integration designer at Enzen Global Solutions. You can contact them at jane_martinez@tesla.net or 321-654-8511. Skills: development of strategies, category management, architecting applications.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                76,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                102,
                125,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                141,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                151,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                178,
                197,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                199,
                224,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Pittendrigh Rosemary is a senior information security analyst at Quatrro Mortgage Solutio. You can contact them at jane.lee@amazon.com or 159-753-7431. Skills: microsoft cluster server, customer service management, linux systems administration.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                61,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                65,
                89,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                115,
                134,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                150,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                160,
                184,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                186,
                213,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                215,
                243,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Lawrence Kalvin is a lead integration technician at Lucy Electric. You can contact them at emilymartinez@microsoft.org or 1-555-123-2475. Skills: currency exchange knowledge, web services integration, database administration procedures.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                91,
                118,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                136,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                146,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                175,
                199,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                201,
                235,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Muller Andy is a energy industry technology specialist at Pan Gulf Technologies. You can contact them at emma.lee@netflix.com or 321-654-7606. Skills: ranking systems, testifying at legal proceedings, cybercrime investigation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                58,
                79,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                105,
                125,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                141,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                151,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                168,
                199,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                201,
                225,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Carrigan Denise is a data science engineer at Coupang. You can contact them at johndavis@adobe.org or 159-753-7688. Skills: mulesofts mule enterprise service bus, welligent ehrs, database management systems evaluation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                53,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                98,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                114,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                124,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                217,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Gruar Caryl is a security software engineer at Ardom Telecom. You can contact them at david.davis@facebook.com or 159-753-3236. Skills: technical file development, yaml data exchange formats, network redesign.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                126,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                164,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                192,
                208,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Chiu Yufen is a researcher at ICFAI Business School. You can contact them at david_hernandez@ibm.net or 987-654-4951. Skills: fieldmanager software, classroom support, net web applications.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                26,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                30,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                126,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                168,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Baggaley Thomas is a autonomous vehicle operations specialist at Wood Group. You can contact them at janelee@facebook.org or 321-654-1266. Skills: report writing, it administrative skills, sql dbms management.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                61,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                65,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                101,
                121,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                137,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                189,
                208,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Botham Kieran is a assoc software engineer at Galvion. You can contact them at liammartinez@netflix.org or 1-555-123-3194. Skills: user centered design methodologies, research information, it engineering.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                53,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                103,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                189,
                203,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ga Claudio is a microservices developer at S H Electronics. You can contact them at john_davis@oracle.net or 987-654-6455. Skills: results orientation, ccnp certification, multipathed configuration.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                197,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mcclelland Jamie is a mediabrands at Eon Electric. You can contact them at david.hernandez@tesla.com or 987-654-2196. Skills: fire suppression systems, budget preparation, data insights transformation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                49,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                126,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                200,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Synowiecki Kamil is a magento developer at HAN IT. You can contact them at davidsmith@netflix.org or 159-753-1152. Skills: restful web services, mainframe, cms supervisor.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                49,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                101,
                113,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                143,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                145,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Devlin Emily is a database manager at Adani Power. You can contact them at emilymartinez@microsoft.org or 987-654-9011. Skills: batch and stream processing technologies, knowledge of medicare part d regulatory requirements, splunk dashboards.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                49,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                118,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                128,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                170,
                222,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                224,
                241,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sponder Kaya is a computer support specialist at Enrich Hair And Skin Sol. You can contact them at oliviadoe@tesla.org or 1-555-123-6417. Skills: big data systems, adobe indesign, meta directory services.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                99,
                118,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                136,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                146,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                164,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                180,
                203,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Okorokov Volodymyr is a senior technology consultant at Avanti Feeds. You can contact them at michael.brown@adobe.com or 1-555-123-1742. Skills: core measures analysis, operational procedures, cloud security gateways.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                52,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                56,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                117,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                135,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                145,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                169,
                191,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                193,
                216,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Oloughlin Paul is a bilingual russian cybercrime intelligence analyst at NKC Projects. You can contact them at liammartinez@netflix.org or 321-654-3580. Skills: user education, bootstrap, pcf knowledge.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                69,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                73,
                85,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                111,
                135,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                139,
                151,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                161,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                177,
                186,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                188,
                201,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dickson John is a it help desk analyst at Vaco Binary Semantics LL. You can contact them at olivia.davis@amazon.com or 987-654-9788. Skills: broadcast equipment knowledge, legal compliance, equipment qualification..",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                92,
                115,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                131,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                190,
                214,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Shah Shruti is a customer experience advocate at Ricoh. You can contact them at daniel.doe@ibm.com or 1-555-123-5602. Skills: scalable application design, development of internal procedures, is is.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                80,
                98,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                126,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                189,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                191,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Brown Agnes is a infrastructure architect at Macurex Sensors. You can contact them at liamdoe@netflix.org or 159-753-1981. Skills: compensation programs, kafka streams api, pmp certification.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                154,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                173,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bgrd Florentine is a data and evaluation manager at Kalpataru Power Transmis. You can contact them at emily_martinez@amazon.net or 1-555-123-9159. Skills: recognition and classification algorithms, visual inspection of parts, statistical and predictive modeling.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                76,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                102,
                127,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                145,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                155,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                198,
                224,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                226,
                261,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bellis Lee is a staff software engineer at Amber Road Software. You can contact them at michaelbrown@ibm.org or 987-654-7878. Skills: cloud based application deployment architectures, rails, migration of applications.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                124,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                184,
                189,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                191,
                216,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Inrig William is a mongodb admin at Ankit Kumar. You can contact them at davidjohnson@oracle.org or 159-753-3516. Skills: risk management, equipment repairs, software design optimized for large scale distributed software systems.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                73,
                96,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                112,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                122,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                139,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                228,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Inrig William is a computer and information research scientist at Golden Star Facilities S. You can contact them at johnwilson@tesla.org or 159-753-2463. Skills: sql report creation, injection machine operation, unix like os.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                62,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                66,
                90,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                116,
                136,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                140,
                152,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                162,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                210,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                212,
                224,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ball Rachel is a immigration paralegal consultant at Oriflame. You can contact them at david_johnson@amazon.net or 321-654-3007. Skills: source control and configuration management frameworks, facilities operations, can bus architecture.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                87,
                111,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                191,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                193,
                214,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                216,
                236,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Louise Saskia is a global account manager at Acrysil. You can contact them at emma_johnson@intel.net or 321-654-1674. Skills: quality planning tools, patches implementation, chat bots.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                52,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                78,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                126,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                150,
                172,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                174,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tucki Piotr is a database administrator servicenow at Synopsys. You can contact them at emmadavis@google.org or 1-555-123-6488. Skills: risk adjustment concepts, scientific software installation and maintenance, data security controls.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                126,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                162,
                210,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                212,
                234,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dawe-Smith Owen is a regulatory writer at Coromandel International. You can contact them at john.brown@intel.com or 321-654-2425. Skills: data collection and integration techniques., end user computing, high availability strategies.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                92,
                112,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                128,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                138,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                201,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                203,
                231,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Peters Caroline is a midlevel site reliability engineer at Accion Labs. You can contact them at emilymartinez@microsoft.org or 159-753-5150. Skills: laboratory test experience, large systems software design, mode.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                96,
                123,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                149,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                177,
                206,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                208,
                212,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tipping Kim is a software engineer iv at Pasco Automobiles. You can contact them at sophia_martinez@ibm.net or 987-654-8179. Skills: etl orchestration frameworks, engineering data structures, data mapping.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                192,
                204,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Shaw Loren is a uctg solution assurance at Castex Technologies. You can contact them at emma_smith@microsoft.net or 321-654-1674. Skills: data set naming convention, sla monitoring, meditech.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                112,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                128,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                138,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                166,
                180,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                182,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hafidi Amanie is a industrial engineer at Michelin. You can contact them at jane.brown@netflix.com or 1-555-123-2481. Skills: fd.io, patient handling equipment usage, salesforce service cloud.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                76,
                98,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                126,
                131,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                133,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                191,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Glynn Kieran is a big data solutions architect at Tanishq. You can contact them at michael.smith@adobe.com or 1-555-123-5478. Skills: system deployment, motion graphics creation, qlickview.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                106,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                124,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                153,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Lakatos Emese is a corporate strategy business analyst at Oriental Structural Engi. You can contact them at david.doe@tesla.com or 159-753-5150. Skills: social media data analytics, apple siri, database programming languages.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                58,
                82,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                108,
                127,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                143,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                153,
                180,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                182,
                192,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                194,
                224,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sheldon Philip is a director of technology at Shri Mata Vaishno Devi N. You can contact them at olivia_wilson@netflix.net or 159-753-2463. Skills: reporting and analytics design, cli development, nonconformance trend assessment.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                96,
                121,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                137,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                194,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                196,
                227,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rzepnicki Marek is a data center services at Zilla Parishad\r\nAvenues India\r\nAdaequare\r\nRacold Thermo\r\nHarbinger Group\r\nUsha Fire Safety Equipme\r\nXebia IT Architects\r\nRNA Corp\r\nProcess Construction And\r\nPall Corporation\r\nMiranda Tools\r\nSitec Labs\r\nCentre For Monitoring In\r\nBrahmaputra Infrastructu\r\nIntec Infonet\r\nSnowcem Paints\r\nInsta Exhibition\r\nStraVis IT Solutions\r\nNetsoft Consulting Servi\r\nKamat Hotels India\r\nCivil court Peddapuram\r\nKarvy Private Wealth\r\nElgi Ultra Industries\r\nPrasad Group\r\nTele Access E\r\nApalya Technologies\r\nRavi\r\nArk Cyber Solutions\r\nStanadyne Amalgamations\r\nSurePrep\r\nSidmak Laboratories (Ind\r\nCitizen Co\r\nEpicor Software Corporat\r\nM M Enterprises\r\nMayfair Housing\r\nForbes Facility Services\r\nAtlanta (Mumbai)\r\nSanjay\r\nLuxor International\r\nDaimler Financial Servic\r\nConcept Hospitality\r\nAon Consulting\r\nM & M\r\nPhoenix Group India\r\nMIPL\r\nVarian Medical Systems\r\nSrijan Realty\r\nKintetsu World Express\r\nNational Organic Chemica\r\nDAV College\r\nKonstelec Engineers\r\nChina Gate Restaurants\r\nUltratech India\r\nMachine Tools India\r\nClutch Group\r\nCalyx Chemicals & Pharma\r\nGrey Matter India\r\nTransworld Group of Comp\r\nJohnson Electric\r\nBristol\r\nAlgoworks Technologies\r\nRSP Design Consultants\r\nDiverse Lynx\r\nEltek Sgs\r\nWorld Class Services\r\nRun Service Infocare\r\nHarrisons Malayalam\r\nCIMS\r\nStone India\r\nTriton Valves\r\nEncore Healthcare\r\nPanchsheel Buildtech\r\nWrangler\r\nMitashi Edutainment\r\nAyurwin Pharma\r\nJagati Publications\r\nIndication Instruments\r\nTayo Rolls\r\nTalent Anywhere\r\nBharti Hospital\r\nOpen Access Technology I\r\nThe Kothari Wheels\r\nOrris Infrastructure\r\nSharda Hospital\r\nTextual Analytics Soluti\r\nShuttl\r\nTMI Network\r\nNews Nation\r\nRenishaw Metrology Syste\r\nDanone Foods Beverages\r\nAkash Enterprises\r\nBelmaks\r\nDKM Online\r\nSabs Exports\r\nCohnReznick\r\nNew Saraswati House\r\nTricolite Electrical Ind\r\nSietz Technologies\r\nCreative Engineers\r\nYMCA\r\nPacifica Companies\r\nGujarat Industries Power\r\nAhuja Radios\r\nThe Velammal Internation\r\nWizertech Informatics\r\nAtyati Technologies\r\nPepperl+Fuchs\r\nNew Horizon College of E\r\nSpl Infrastructure\r\nRadius Developers\r\nNational Remote Sensing\r\nElysium Pharmaceuticals\r\nMantri Metallics\r\nSac Engine Components\r\nZephyr\r\nDivya And Co\r\nK Raheja Constructions\r\nFinearc Systems\r\nAnjan Drug\r\nAcebright Pharma\r\nGuala Closures\r\nHush Puppies ( Bata Indi\r\niLabz Technology\r\nGlobe Ecologistics\r\nInd Innovations\r\nNouveau Technologies\r\nXentrix Studios\r\nGlatt Systems\r\nKOHINOOR TELEVIDEO\r\nOremus Corporate Service\r\nKanodia Technoplast\r\nSmc Infrastructure\r\ninfoAnalytica\r\nPrakash Retail\r\nKnack BPO\r\nTata Group\r\nA\r\nKomal Tex Fab\r\nGinza Industries\r\nPioneer Urban Land & Inf\r\nVibrant\r\nCenlub Systems\r\nLotus Dairy Products\r\nNIIT Yuva Jyoti\r\nTmeic Industrial Systems\r\nSewells Group\r\nGoldmedal Electricals\r\nKun Aero Space\r\nGokaldas Intimatewear\r\nDexters Logistics\r\nCabcon India\r\nDonaldson India Filter S\r\nZeiss Pharma\r\nStellapps Technologies\r\nResil Chemicals\r\nPacific It Consulting\r\nNovotel Hyderabad Airpor\r\nTrinity Mobility\r\nSona Group\r\nUrbantree Infrastructure\r\nArcotech\r\nSpringdales School\r\nEenadu Television\r\nVergo Pharma Research La\r\nMicro Tech Cnc\r\nBosch Electrical Drives\r\nDrytech Processes (I)\r\nPrayag Polymers\r\nMadras Radiators And Pre\r\nPlan International\r\nAnkit Fasteners\r\nZenpower Technologies\r\nMax Speciality Films\r\nAmandeep Hospital\r\nRossell Techsys\r\nGlobal Gourmet\r\nLEAP India\r\nMicrogen Hygiene\r\nVDart\r\nHobel Bellows\r\nAbsolute Insurance Surve\r\nFiberHome\r\nKomet Precision Tools In\r\nEssar Ports\r\nGetco\r\nTechnocrats Institute of\r\nREVA University\r\nGrand Polycoats\r\nPremier Plasmotec\r\nQatar Petrochemical Comp\r\nVigour Mobile\r\nExport Trading group\r\nBEC Chemicals\r\nRavenbhel Healthcare\r\nCopper Chimney\r\nClear Secured Services\r\nSaif Bin Darwish\r\nDhan Foundation\r\nMedico Electrodes Intern\r\nDigital india Payments\r\nShaarc Project\r\nGood Shepherd Internatio\r\nTriFid Research\r\nDefsys Solutions\r\nNepa\r\nDBM Geotechnics & Constr\r\nSt.marthas Hospital\r\nGala Precision Engineeri\r\nHallmark\r\nPerennial Technologies\r\nNew India Co\r\nMtg Learning Media\r\nBeam Global Spirits & Wi\r\nAga Khan Foundation\r\nNetmeds Marketplace\r\nOmega Engineering LLC\r\nIMS Proschool\r\nNac Jewellers\r\nAir India Engineering Se\r\nIntec Infra\r\nSunil Healthcare\r\nVerga Attachments\r\nEnergizer\r\nBrij Gopal Construction\r\nStructures Online\r\nGaruda Polyflex Foods\r\nMb Power (m.p)\r\nAcadecraft\r\nHitachi Zosen Corporatio\r\nMarwadi University\r\nLavazza\r\nMigsun Group\r\nSynergy Steels\r\nBellona Hospitality Serv\r\nCanpac Trends\r\nRampex Labs\r\nChiyoda Corporation\r\nCure foods\r\nKentz Engineers & Constr\r\nAujan Coca Cola Beverage\r\nRoseate Hotels & Resorts\r\nSkims\r\nK.D. Medical College Hos\r\nSerco Middle East\r\nThe Sports Gurukul\r\nPoddar Diamond\r\nNarmada Polymers\r\nAfrican Industries\r\nSrg Earth Resources\r\nAris Capital\r\nBritish American Tobacco\r\nBrunel Energy\r\nSreenidhi International\r\nWistron\r\nGrand Hotel\r\nNabard Consultancy Servi\r\nProtecon BTG\r\nHyper Panda\r\nKamal Fincap\r\nJollibee Foods Corporati\r\nReliance Strategic Manpo\r\nShri Ram Murti Smarak In\r\nElite Elevators\r\nTata STRIVE\r\nAl Hokair Fashion Retail\r\nHG Infra\r\nAstral Adhesives\r\nRajasthan Grameen Aajeev\r\nWestern India Transport\r\nTEXILA AMERICAN UNIVERSI\r\nCEDP SKiLL INSTITUTE\r\nCalibrated Healthcare Ne\r\nSaipem Contracting\r\nIndia Dye Chem\r\nSintex Industries Limite\r\nGalacon Infrastructure a\r\nActive Automobiles Tata\r\nTSMC\r\nLead Consultancy & Engin\r\nIrrigation Department Ka\r\nIspat Industries\r\niYogi\r\nReliance Tech Services\r\nSchool of Scholars\r\nPayoda Technologies\r\nEESoft Technologies\r\nInformation Dynamics\r\nBnp Paribas Securities\r\nKonyLabs IT Services\r\nInformatica Business Sol\r\nRedknee\r\nMobileum\r\nWizcraft International E\r\nAutomotive Axles\r\nAmira Pure Foods\r\nKumar Builders\r\nAmicorp Management India\r\nRPL TELECOM\r\nAtum It Services\r\nSupreme Petrochem\r\nBannari Amman Sugars\r\nSai Construction\r\nSS Engineers\r\nS K International\r\nInfineon Technologies\r\nV2soft\r\nTTSL\r\nJCBL\r\nFichtner Consulting Engi\r\nLuminous Infoways\r\nProvab Technosoft\r\nAppin Technology Lab\r\nChopra Industries\r\nEon Technologies\r\nNextGenVision Technology\r\nUber Projects\r\nLahmeyer International\r\nPKF Sridhar & Santhanam\r\nComnet Solutions\r\nSandesh\r\nUBM\r\nRegenerative Medical Ser\r\nOriental Cuisines\r\nTransparency Market Rese\r\nZeta Global\r\nRPP Infra Projects\r\nCable Corporation Of Ind\r\nAXA Technologies Shared\r\nBrainbees Solutions\r\nWorldpay\r\nNational Bank of Abu Dha\r\nDietech India\r\nHotel Ramada\r\nHitachi Solutions\r\nAvantha Business Solutio\r\nJ & M Technologies\r\nAmbience Group\r\nNICT\r\nAVA Merchandising Soluti\r\nStartrek Logistics\r\nKotak Mahindra Asset Man\r\nSIMPLEX ENGINEERING & FO\r\nDelval Flow Controls\r\nReed Elsevier\r\nVijayasri Organics\r\nMahindra Gujarat Tractor\r\nSS Group\r\nAmtech Electronics\r\nMultimetals\r\nAvantel\r\nStarsun Technology\r\nDSM\r\nCurrie & Brown\r\nGCL\r\nMicrochip Technology\r\nModern Steels\r\nGujarat State Petroleum\r\nCoastal Energen\r\nRakuten\r\nMagicrete Building Solut\r\nMerit Group\r\nCex Webuy Entertainment\r\nPSG College of Technolog\r\nAK Enterprises\r\nMETAL FORM\r\nWorldline india\r\nMore Supermarket\r\nPind Balluchi\r\nSunshine\r\nClassic Auto Tubes\r\nUnitech Power Transmissi\r\nWebguru Infosystems\r\nFootprints Collateral Se\r\nC\r\nFrench Motor Car Co.\r\nMastech Digital\r\nOld World Hospitality\r\nLink Intime\r\nInfodrive\r\nAshok\r\nQuality Services & Solut\r\nCovalense Technologies\r\nSwamina International\r\nThreyes Srinisons Harnes\r\nNarnolia Securities\r\nIWL\r\nEVOSYS\r\nGuru Teg Bahadur Hospita\r\nGrb Dairy Foods\r\nHartron Communication\r\nMIET Meerut\r\nInfocare Digital System\r\nRama group\r\nElement14\r\nBrahMos Aerospace\r\nPrecision Tech Enterpris\r\nAyurvet\r\nAlliance Infrastructure\r\nAir India Express\r\nAffinity Global Advertis\r\nGulfspic\r\nSeneca Global IT Service\r\nNims Hospital\r\nPathPartner Technology\r\nRhenus Logistics\r\nAIETS\r\nHotel Sea Princess\r\nMahalaxmi Construction\r\nEsolz Technologies\r\nHemmo Pharmaceuticals\r\nAllana Group of Companie\r\nShri Ram New Horizons\r\nGodavari Biorefineries\r\nElgi Rubber Company\r\nRajasthan Electronics &\r\nAppworx Infotech\r\nNIPA International\r\nWest Coast Pharmaceutica\r\nBARSYL\r\nRapid Global Business So\r\nMasters Management Consu\r\nMbit Wireless\r\nSofitel Luxury Hotel\r\nSurat Municipal Corporat\r\nCoastal Marine Construct\r\nGreat Eastern Trading Co\r\nSogex Oman India\r\nARC\r\nThinksynq Solutions\r\nMerlin Group\r\nJaguar Overseas\r\nTudip Technologies\r\nGrassroots BPO\r\nAvalon Cosmetics\r\nAdministrative College o\r\nParas Spices\r\nD Vois Ssv Broadband\r\nPramod Telecom\r\nUrbanpro\r\nDr. Amin Controllers\r\nPPS International\r\nSafechem Industries\r\nResponsive Industries\r\nPTCL\r\nIsha Foundation\r\nHealthians\r\nITELLIGENCE INDIA SOFTWA\r\nWaaree Group\r\nAnalytix Business Soluti\r\nVelex Logistics\r\nLotus Hospital\r\nRadio City\r\nManohar Chowdhry & Assoc\r\nCcd\r\nKwang Sung Brake\r\nMinda Automotive Solutio\r\nGSC Glass\r\nATMA\r\nSailfin Technologies\r\nFIL Industries\r\nManya\r\nMahavir Auto Diagnostics\r\nTiger Logistics India\r\nMisumi\r\nBenzo Chem Industries\r\nSkyline Engineering Cont\r\nRainbow School\r\nSamkrg Pistons and Rings\r\nAutosense\r\nInnovis Telecom Services\r\nTimezone Entertainment\r\nShirodkar Preci Comp\r\nShubham Flexible Packagi\r\nKhaitan Chemicals & Fert\r\nRCL\r\nKumar Elastomech\r\nEidiko Systems Integrato\r\nShyam Group\r\nKelvion\r\nMEDICO Healthcare Servic\r\nRohilkhand Medical Colle\r\nAdvance Metering Technol\r\nEverest Spices\r\nMody University Science\r\nUBS Cognizant\r\nP R Packaging\r\nMPEB\r\nRamada Caravela Beach Re\r\nSRS Cinemas\r\nChesa Dental Care Servic\r\nMetro Heart Institute Wi\r\nPci Analytics\r\nThe Chocolate Room\r\nSalwan Public School\r\nDiamond International\r\nEspirit Toyota\r\nLakhani Footwear\r\nShalimar Hatcheries\r\nChoice Chemtech\r\nCuratio Healthcare\r\nRatnadeep Super Market\r\nKarvy Insurance Reposito\r\nNTPC BHEL Power Projects\r\nNamdhari Seeds\r\nFSL\r\nAGFA HEALTHCARE INDIA\r\nNCMSL\r\nMaharishi Ayurveda Produ\r\nMitsubishi Hitachi Power\r\nANJ Turnkey Projects\r\nBank Alfalah\r\nStandard Radiators\r\nE\r\nJain Amar Clothing\r\nUtracon Structural Syste\r\nEcogreen Energy\r\nNMC Hospital\r\nT.K. Engineering Consort\r\nDangee Dums\r\nMargdarshak Financial Se\r\nInventiv International P\r\nGallantt Ispat\r\nMaire Tecnimont\r\nNirala india\r\nDsm Shared Services Indi\r\nSimmonds Marshall\r\nKMC Electronics\r\nOm Trans Logistics\r\nRamsis Engineering\r\nIIM Ahmedabad\r\nSephora\r\nJAAC TECHNO SERVICES\r\nHvac\r\nOnePlus\r\nPuratos Food Ingredients\r\nOrigoFinance\r\nEquinox Labs\r\nOptimal Transnational\r\nUnited Creation\r\nJarvis Technology and St\r\nRothe Erde India\r\nBhavna Software\r\nAnmol Feeds\r\nLedure Lighting\r\nCranedge\r\nSnapBizz Cloudtech\r\nRam Kripal Singh Constru\r\nAnnora Pharma\r\nManthan International Sc\r\nCoolwinks Technologies\r\nPrasar Bharati\r\nLiva Pharmaceuticals\r\nIRM Offshore & Marine En\r\nNif\r\nCorrival Corporate Consu\r\nEnergy Solutions Interna\r\nParnika Commercial & Est\r\nShri Ram Murti Smarak Co\r\nAga Khan Education Servi\r\nTII India\r\nContract Resources Petro\r\nFedders Electric & Engin\r\nSankalp Engineering & Se\r\nMudrakshi Hytech India\r\nKeshava Reddy School\r\nUtl Upsinverter.com\r\nSmartSchool Education\r\nRubber King Tyres\r\nEMRI(108)\r\nVignan Global Gen School\r\nRadius Corporate Solutio\r\nPullman & Novotel\r\nBRCM College of Engineer\r\nHudson's bay Company\r\nCrp Risk Management\r\nSHRI LAKSHMI STEEL SUPPL\r\nJharkhand State Liveliho\r\nICRI\r\nAbdullah A. Al\r\nIQ City Medical College\r\nEnviro Infra Engineers\r\nLubrizol Advanced Materi\r\nZalaris\r\nVishwa Bharati Public Sc\r\nNetafim Agricultural Fin\r\nThe Gujarat Cancer & Res\r\nDiamond Cement\r\nSTT Global Data Centres\r\nFairfield  Marriott. You can contact them at jane.wilson@intel.com or 1-555-123-3194. Skills: osx, system schematics, axure.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                11161,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                11187,
                11208,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                11212,
                11226,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                11236,
                11239,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                11241,
                11258,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                11260,
                11265,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Lowry Stephen is a network engineer intern at FedEx Express. You can contact them at john.doe@amazon.com or 321-654-8932. Skills: ez c, peoplesoft security development, operating forklift or other powered equipment.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                104,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                120,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                134,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                169,
                214,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Milburn Lewis is a business performance analyst at BIL Infratech. You can contact them at michael_wilson@tesla.net or 1-555-123-1480. Skills: cloud certifications, ml frameworks, vulnerability assessment techniques.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                164,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                214,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Westrip Jacy is a isv alliance manager at Thirumalai Chemicals. You can contact them at danielhernandez@adobe.org or 159-753-8993. Skills: iso 14000, risk management strategies, infrastructure setup and support.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                150,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                178,
                210,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Atkin Andy is a jr. network systems administrator at Sangeetha Mobile. You can contact them at sophiadoe@tesla.org or 159-753-9609. Skills: product financial analysis, sass or less, display and social ads.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                95,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                130,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                168,
                180,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                182,
                204,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rzepnicki Marek is a it business analytics & data warehousing at Highway Industries. You can contact them at michael.clark@oracle.com or 321-654-8849. Skills: firewall administration, etl integration development, sharepoint on prem.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                61,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                65,
                83,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                109,
                133,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                137,
                149,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                159,
                182,
