[
    {
        "text": "Leitão Ana is a database architect at Mahindra Powerol. You can contact them at jaysajul@gmail.com or 1-555-123-9159. Skills: system performance monitoring, strategic planning and analysis, warehousing environment.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                80,
                98,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                126,
                155,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                157,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                190,
                213,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Vaswani Suresh is a sr web developer at Proteus Co. You can contact them at hr@hawthornabudhabi.com or 321-654-7786. Skills: presto, statistical software proficiency, cache dba.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                76,
                99,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                125,
                131,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                133,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Lee Chris is a marketing planning data & consumables analyst at Hpcl Biofuels. You can contact them at asouthwell@jess.sch.ae or 321-654-5040. Skills: devops, fed wire transactions, powernet.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                64,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                103,
                125,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                141,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                151,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                159,
                180,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                182,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Lacking Kieran is a mgr site function at Eglo India. You can contact them at timkirk@uaeu.ac.ae or 159-753-8484. Skills: hardware repair, integration of 3rd party systems, augmented reality.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                95,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                99,
                111,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                121,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                189,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Court Mary is a production control and operations center agent at Government of Madhya Pra. You can contact them at ff@eurocomtek.com or 987-654-7375. Skills: server side technologies, experience managing a help desk, scalable data infrastructure design.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                62,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                66,
                90,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                116,
                133,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                137,
                149,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                159,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                185,
                216,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                218,
                253,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Choos Choo is a computer support specialist at Xome. You can contact them at lisa28071970@aim.com or 159-753-3236. Skills: touch interface development, enterprise services, safety and security systems.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                101,
                113,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                173,
                200,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Orecchio Sabrina is a area manager at Apothecon Pharmaceutical. You can contact them at oceanuae@eim.ae or 321-654-2204. Skills: high traffic website design, data definitions, operations strategy.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                103,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                119,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                129,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                176,
                195,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Gil Tomasz is a software engineering intern at Hurix Systems. You can contact them at humaira.majid@cig.ae or 321-654-6658. Skills: interaction scenario prototyping, facilitating planning sessions, marketing automation platforms.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                106,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                132,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                166,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                198,
                228,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Whitelaw Lynsey is a hurley part at Baxter Healthcare (Suzho. You can contact them at reevinay@gmail.com or 987-654-2430. Skills: server technologies, geospatial data visualization, computer systems imaging or installation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                104,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                120,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                151,
                180,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                182,
                222,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Nelson Wendy is a post software engineer at United Drilling Tools. You can contact them at mayasree@emirates.net.ae or 159-753-3458. Skills: technology related experience, valuations, msp.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                91,
                115,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                131,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                184,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bryce Shauna is a sales engineer at Radisson Hotels. You can contact them at mohammed.alrais@tecom.ae or 321-654-7813. Skills: digital, netcool, systems integration.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                117,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                127,
                134,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                143,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                145,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Goff Dani is a data scientist at Veeda Clinical Research. You can contact them at i.pineda@habibbank.com or 321-654-3580. Skills: risk evaluation methods, high availability replication, technology analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                104,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                120,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                184,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                186,
                205,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jones Amy is a gdi&a ford college graduate program at BARSYL. You can contact them at saleem@sitsme.com or 159-753-5732. Skills: financial and operational metrics, correspondent banking, technical analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                103,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                119,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                129,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                164,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                187,
                205,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Nemeth Cox Sue is a autonomy software engineer at Gimatex Industries. You can contact them at abdureata@gmail.com or 1-555-123-3938. Skills: data presentation, irb approval, automotive communication logs analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                131,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                160,
                172,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                174,
                212,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Moore Lisa is a servicenow systems administrator at JP Associates. You can contact them at info@pcsuae.com or 159-753-9609. Skills: leadership development, apache flink, paas environment.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                91,
                106,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                132,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                170,
                186,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Floors Doors is a employee fraud detection risk manager at REPCO HOME FINANCE. You can contact them at mtts@emirates.net.ae or 321-654-7813. Skills: fundamental statistical concepts, agile development, information security policies.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                103,
                123,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                149,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                200,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                202,
                231,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bueno Victoria is a communications coordinator at Cygnet Infotech. You can contact them at jobs@qstp.org.qa or 1-555-123-6372. Skills: security planning for projects, sales and business background, knowledge of structured analysis and systems design methodologies.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                91,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                198,
                263,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Irish Chanice is a m&a integration lead at Technocraft Industries. You can contact them at info@hallodubai.com or 987-654-7932. Skills: data modules design and development, business engagement, user replication policies.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                91,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                126,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                173,
                192,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                194,
                219,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dickson John is a stakeholder insights and analytics manager at Union Bank of India. You can contact them at kevin.birkett@gmail.com or 321-654-5040. Skills: architecture design for scalability, railroad coordination, patient education.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                64,
                83,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                109,
                132,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                148,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                158,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                195,
                216,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                218,
                235,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Campbell Billy is a engineering software administrator at Tata Advanced Systems. You can contact them at sanghvir@dubal.co.ae or 1-555-123-6097. Skills: gap closure plans, hardware and software knowledge, ai algorithms and architectures.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                58,
                79,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                105,
                125,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                143,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                153,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                203,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                205,
                236,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Petkov Momchil is a global strategy competitive analysis analyst at IndiaNivesh Securities. You can contact them at recruitment@alfardan.com.qa or 321-654-5944. Skills: performance improvement, development, technology adaptation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                64,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                68,
                90,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                116,
                143,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                147,
                159,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                169,
                192,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                194,
                205,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                207,
                228,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Roberts Andy is a pd&p coker stress engineer at Fusion Innovation. You can contact them at bangalorecareers@tcs.com or 159-753-8993. Skills: crm system knowledge, project scoping and estimation, training curriculum development.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                91,
                115,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                131,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                195,
                226,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Patel Maulik is a project administrator at Siddha Group. You can contact them at stuart_griffiths@masaood.com or 987-654-4996. Skills: it workflow processes, sales experience, crf part 11.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                109,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                176,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Yeman Liam is a database analyst intern at Micromatic Machine Tools. You can contact them at comdir@saif-zone.com or 159-753-9006. Skills: management information systems, sp ip network design, allfusion.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                93,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                169,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                171,
                191,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                193,
                202,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Brown Agnes is a full stack developer at Rexel. You can contact them at info@itp.com or 1-555-123-2481. Skills: wordpress, systems incident support and troubleshooting, new tool adoption.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                46,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                72,
                84,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                102,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                112,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                169,
                186,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mcclelland Jamie is a revenue collector at 6Tel Consultancy. You can contact them at corporatecommunications@alfuttaim.ae or 1-555-123-5602. Skills: regression models, data center and storage solutions, big data applications.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                121,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                149,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                168,
                201,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                203,
                224,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Gray Berniiee is a pega senior systems architect at Terminal Technologies (i. You can contact them at c.miserra@hellerconsult.com or 987-654-1944. Skills: helpdesk support, hp operation and orchestration, vehicle to vehicle connectivity.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                76,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                102,
                129,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                133,
                145,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                155,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                173,
                203,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                205,
                236,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Teixeira Bruno is a java developer for integration services at FabHotels. You can contact them at baris@jtmjv.ae or 1-555-123-7568. Skills: brand lift studies, it program management, qualitative and quantitative research.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                59,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                63,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                98,
                112,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                130,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                160,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                220,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Grulyo Roman is a business systems analyst specialist at Vulcan Express. You can contact them at palak@kbctechnologies.com or 321-654-6253. Skills: cognos toolsets, compute services, caesar ii software proficiency.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                53,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                97,
                122,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                138,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                148,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                165,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                213,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rayner Nicola is a engineering scientist at Wipro Digital. You can contact them at info@istithmar.ae or 159-753-7708. Skills: routing optimization, modern front end frameworks react, vmware esxi.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                126,
                146,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                148,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                194,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Knee Torin is a autopsy attendant at Avanti Feeds. You can contact them at aisan@emirates.net.ae or 159-753-8484. Skills: malware and security protection, automation of machine learning systems, spark job development.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                49,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                96,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                112,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                122,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                195,
                216,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Moulin Camille is a marketing specialist at Louis Dreyfus Commoditie. You can contact them at prakash@rgvtelecom.com or 321-654-2923. Skills: point of sale, compute benchmarking, it automation and orchestration.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                116,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                155,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                157,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                210,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bolton Natalie is a sustainability specialist at SODECIA. You can contact them at mojaber@gmail.com or 159-753-2647. Skills: supplier auditing, experience leading professional development programs, design and implementation of cloud networks.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                99,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                125,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                144,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                198,
                241,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hashhs Heisv is a sr solution architect at PG Electroplast. You can contact them at alzakoori@emirates.net.ae or 987-654-6210. Skills: services creation, materials research, pattern recognition.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                109,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                154,
                172,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                174,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Gildea Leanne is a salesforce marketing cloud developer at VIZIO. You can contact them at accounts@rashidprinters.ae or 987-654-4700. Skills: process improvement methodologies, web ui development, audio teleconferencing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                116,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                177,
                195,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                197,
                219,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Devlin Emily is a business & industrial network engineer at Saudi Binladin Group. You can contact them at safahrc@gmail.com or 321-654-8849. Skills: os performance tuning, search algorithms, scientific object oriented programming.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                60,
                80,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                106,
                123,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                149,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                189,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                191,
                229,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Agić Mido is a administrative business partner at Genpact Headstrong Capit. You can contact them at sales@rttdubai.com or 987-654-6828. Skills: design skills, data curation, monitoring tools integration.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                100,
                118,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                134,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                144,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                159,
                172,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                174,
                202,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sharaz Zuha is a analytics manager at NTT. You can contact them at mark@intagulf.ae or 987-654-6425. Skills: designing networks, architecture tradeoffs, quantitative and qualitative analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                41,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                87,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                109,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                153,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Duthie Jake is a billing database specialist at Rudrabhishek Enterprises. You can contact them at asad.warsi@coe.com.pk or 321-654-8159. Skills: cisco product integration expertise, hazard assessment, document control.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                98,
                119,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                135,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                145,
                180,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                182,
                199,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                201,
                217,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Partridge Scott is a php engineer at Claris Otsuka. You can contact them at ewmotors@emirates.net.ae or 987-654-4951. Skills: systems administration, vehicle to grid connectivity, security operations controls configuration and maintenance.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                76,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                126,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                150,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                180,
                238,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Holmes Richard is a strategic data analyst at Zeta Interactive Systems. You can contact them at ramesharakkal@herefind.com or 159-753-6636. Skills: high availability concepts, prototype testing, database engineering.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                96,
                122,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                138,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                148,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                176,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                195,
                215,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rory Bona is a it business analyst at Focus Academy for Career. You can contact them at nkhurram@gmail.com or 321-654-3876. Skills: contract preparation, open source, data center fabric switching technology.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                106,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                132,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                154,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                206,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Catello Laura is a it deputy administrator at Shyam Ferro Alloys. You can contact them at jstephen@varco.com or 321-654-9777. Skills: work order management, robotic camera operation, spreadsheet creation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                124,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                155,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                157,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                203,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dean Amy is a senior database administrator at BankBazaar. You can contact them at bassam_elassaad@trane.com or 159-753-6654. Skills: quality system requirements, automation test scripts, networking technologies understanding.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                124,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                186,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                188,
                225,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "O Londraigh Mattiu is a azure devops engineer at Damas Jewellery. You can contact them at osman@charteredtech.com or 1-555-123-9159. Skills: program delivery, acceptance testing procedures, mydata portal.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                131,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                159,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                190,
                203,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Myatt Lucy is a pd&p coker stress engineer at Metalsa. You can contact them at accounts1@junaid.ae or 159-753-1981. Skills: technical skills revenue cycle data analysis, trams database software, equipment tracking.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                53,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                98,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                114,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                124,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                170,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                195,
                213,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Wheatstone Robert is a social media analyst at Dell EMC. You can contact them at eeg@emirates.net.ae or 987-654-4376. Skills: source code and knowledge repositories, equipment upkeep, skincare expertise.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                126,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                166,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                184,
                202,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ledwards Mike is a strategy and operations manager at Minacs. You can contact them at cmtind@emirates.net.ae or 987-654-3449. Skills: code pipeline, reel creation, specification and documentation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                124,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                164,
                195,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Williamson Andy is a security roles at Delta Technology and Man. You can contact them at hr@elextric.ae or 321-654-1969. Skills: marketing, training management system, executive summaries.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                89,
                103,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                119,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                129,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                140,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                168,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Oakley Gemma is a infrastructure developer at Radico Khaitan. You can contact them at hr@intellicomcenters.com or 321-654-3910. Skills: product roadmap planning, enterprise reporting, core networking principles.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                126,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                162,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                184,
                210,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Wetoszka David is a redaction workstream lead at Škoda Auto India. You can contact them at sealants@eim.ae or 1-555-123-2475. Skills: managed care, aws products and services, navigating ambiguity.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                91,
                106,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                124,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                146,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                148,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                175,
                195,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Haggarty Lydia is a program analyst at RCS Technologies. You can contact them at utg@talk21.com or 1-555-123-5478. Skills: equipment evaluation for phytosanitary treatment, security test and evaluation, compensation programs.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                95,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                99,
                113,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                173,
                201,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                203,
                224,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hill Roger is a senior solutions design engineer at Carnival Cinemas. You can contact them at tea@drakewilliam.com or 321-654-5444. Skills: network analysis, excel functions, disaster recovery procedures.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                130,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                175,
                203,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Anderson Dean is a project management coordinator at Eleganz Interiors. You can contact them at hr@advatecgroup.com or 1-555-123-7270. Skills: proficiency with new and rapidly changing technologies and applications, data science life cycle, enterprise cloud adoption strategy.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                96,
                115,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                133,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                214,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                216,
                239,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                241,
                275,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ball Rachel is a senior big data software engineer at My Home Constructions. You can contact them at business@thuraya.com or 987-654-2589. Skills: unix scripting, phishing campaigns, dashboard designing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                101,
                121,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                137,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                202,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Oloughlin Paul is a expert software engineer in test at Aloha Technology. You can contact them at grandopt@eim.ae or 987-654-7498. Skills: data dictionary management, systems troubleshooting, deep learning algorithms and frameworks.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                52,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                56,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                98,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                192,
                231,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Greer Margaret is a project lead business intelligence at Bioworld Merchandising. You can contact them at careers@midland.com.qa or 987-654-9882. Skills: building codes knowledge, iso 2700x, behavioral analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                58,
                80,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                106,
                128,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                132,
                144,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                154,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                180,
                189,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                191,
                210,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Savalia Milan is a it software engineer consultant at Sara Suole. You can contact them at abhishetty1980@gmail.com or 159-753-5732. Skills: esd regulations, ms suite of products, hipaa and privacy guidelines.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                130,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                155,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                157,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                207,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sponder Kaya is a sponsored programs business analyst at Itc Sonar Kolkata. You can contact them at rjohnson@seatrade-middleeast.ae or 321-654-9777. Skills: researching data stores, customer complaint management, financial modeling.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                53,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                100,
                131,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                147,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                157,
                180,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                182,
                211,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                213,
                231,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Stanic Mia is a manager of security intelligence at Ajmal Perfumes. You can contact them at hr@kyndryl.com or 321-654-4534. Skills: usps regulations, integration standards like restful and soap web services, writing style development.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                92,
                106,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                132,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                150,
                206,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                208,
                233,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Anderson Aiden Charles is a full stack php developer at NIPA International. You can contact them at pierre.caunac@gmail.com or 159-753-9907. Skills: html5 and css, storage archive systems, application upgrades.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                22,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                52,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                56,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                100,
                123,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                149,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                164,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                189,
                209,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Gradowska Ewelina is a net full at Barclays. You can contact them at hr@karointl.com or 159-753-3236. Skills: mainframe systems knowledge, ms windows, media buying.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                43,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                69,
                84,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                110,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                139,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                151,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rmrs Andrea is a store operations learning program designer at Amazon. You can contact them at alaqmar@emirates.net.ae or 987-654-8546. Skills: flow diagrams, word processing, minitab.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                59,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                63,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                95,
                118,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                134,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                144,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                159,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                176,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mills Jesse is a biological scientist at Sparsh BPO Services. You can contact them at hr@cornichegroup.co or 1-555-123-8231. Skills: statistical programming r, incident response management, product leadership.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                160,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                190,
                208,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mcclelland Jamie is a semiconductor process integration engineer at Tops Security. You can contact them at atelier@eim.ae or 159-753-1981. Skills: tagging strategies, cash application, legal technologies and systems oversight.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                64,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                68,
                81,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                107,
                121,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                137,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                185,
                225,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rowson Anna is a chief architect at TVS & Sons. You can contact them at sreehari@emirates.net.ae or 321-654-9054. Skills: vendor communication, experience with pricing, product engineering.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                46,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                72,
                96,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                112,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                122,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                144,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                169,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Johnson Shane is a global strategy competitive analysis analyst at Reed Elsevier. You can contact them at istthrat@eim.ae or 159-753-2404. Skills: client experience, dell power products, network capacity analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                63,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                67,
                80,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                106,
                121,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                137,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                166,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                187,
                212,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mortiboy Ben is a it analyst at Agarwal Packers & Movers. You can contact them at amy.brown2004@gmail.com or 987-654-9882. Skills: sales targets achievement, cloud networking, user administration.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                28,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                32,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                176,
                195,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Heacock Adrian is a technical data analyst at Shakti Bhog Foods. You can contact them at info@rlm-metal.com or 159-753-7431. Skills: automation tools such as ansible, sql and databases, contract dispute resolution.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                89,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                184,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                186,
                213,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Piyush Prajapati is a content integration specialist at Coromandel Infotech Indi. You can contact them at fares@adsodxb.ae or 987-654-9788. Skills: construction monitoring and property condition assessments, strategic program management, feature acceptance criteria.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                52,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                56,
                80,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                106,
                122,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                138,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                148,
                206,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                208,
                236,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                238,
                265,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Oloughlin Paul is a o365 messaging architect at The Lalit. You can contact them at hana.yousuf@gmail.com or 321-654-5794. Skills: internet research, analyzer operation, openshift.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                104,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                120,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                169,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sands Suzanne is a family relations coord at Medicover Fertility. You can contact them at gsglp@emirates.net.ae or 1-555-123-5478. Skills: image denoising, mcmc sampling, image analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                111,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                169,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                171,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Claro Jeremiah is a sap basis and database administrator at SS Construction. You can contact them at hr@liwa.tv or 159-753-3421. Skills: network software and services implementation, health care it, cloud infrastructure design.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                60,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                101,
                111,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                197,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                199,
                226,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tony is a elementary nild educational therapist at Ankit Kumar. You can contact them at roger.hawa@ogilvy.com or 159-753-5836. Skills: prognostics and health management, ad server management, neuroimaging software.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                4,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                10,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                109,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                170,
                190,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                192,
                213,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rafiqi Annie is a integration architect at TVS Motor. You can contact them at daffy@rochesterwellness.com or 1-555-123-7270. Skills: lstm, software engineering lifecycle, six sigma green belt or black belt.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                52,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                78,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                139,
                169,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                171,
                205,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Greatrex Carly is a staff data & information architect at Dnata International. You can contact them at dvecor@emirates.net.ae or 987-654-9011. Skills: clear and concise report preparation, ad hoc reporting, networking protocols.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                58,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                103,
                125,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                141,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                151,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                189,
                205,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                207,
                227,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Lokesh Borole is a wireless network engineer at Societe Generale. You can contact them at ailene.kraken@gmail.com or 1-555-123-2404. Skills: forensics and analysis, chatbot, windows server implementation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                131,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                165,
                172,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                174,
                203,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Joinery Lawrenson is a payments assistant at Synthite Industries. You can contact them at harjinder@thakral.ae or 1-555-123-3513. Skills: semantic occupancy grids, phpunit, vsphere horizon view and vmware orchestrator.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                128,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                138,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                164,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                173,
                217,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Harrington Jennifer is a supply chain data analyst at Flex. You can contact them at ostemeier@emirates.net.ae or 1-555-123-4977. Skills: analytical tools and software development, stock replenishment, printer maintenance.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                109,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                180,
                199,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                201,
                220,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Harrington Jennifer is a expert software engineer in test at WaveCrest. You can contact them at igbcmail@igbc.org or 987-654-4144. Skills: security zones, subpoena generation, best practices implementation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                57,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                61,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                96,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                176,
                205,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Oloughlin Paul is a software quality engineer at Northwestern Mutual. You can contact them at ayman7@alqudra.ae or 321-654-1969. Skills: information retrieval, sap smart data integration, policy and procedure writing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                111,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                160,
                186,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                188,
                216,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meyer Kyle is a product analyst at Sanat Products. You can contact them at silvia@turnaround.ae or 987-654-2970. Skills: release management, electronic data processing, data loading mechanisms.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                49,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                95,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                99,
                111,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                121,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                141,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                169,
                192,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dhengale Pramod is a distinguished data scientist at Sabre Engineering. You can contact them at joel@abcom.ae or 1-555-123-7044. Skills: system and database performance optimization, functionality checks, predictive and decision models.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                96,
                109,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                203,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                205,
                235,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bellis Lee is a kind brand ambassador at BL Kashyap & Sons. You can contact them at info@tgpdubai.com or 987-654-7932. Skills: track it! help desk software, machine learning in predictive analytic technologies, system failure analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                117,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                127,
                155,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                157,
                209,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                211,
                234,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Smith Liam is a bilingual spanish retail sales consultant at TUI India. You can contact them at admin@gdsqatar.com.qa or 987-654-4972. Skills: exploratory analysis, sdn networks, information security control activities.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                57,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                61,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                96,
                117,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                133,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                165,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                179,
                218,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Harrison-Derbyshire Brooklynn is a full stack software developer at Tradeindiacom. You can contact them at neeta@peoplesource-me.com or 321-654-5525. Skills: understanding of information technology processes and controls, hardware evaluation, kpi development and tracking.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                29,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                35,
                64,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                68,
                81,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                107,
                132,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                148,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                158,
                220,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                222,
                241,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                243,
                271,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Coyle Meabh is a lead integration technician at eSense Learning. You can contact them at jk@agegraphics.net or 1-555-123-1480. Skills: micro strategy, storage provisioning, cloud adoption and automation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                89,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                151,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                173,
                202,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Vasava Sandip is a operations supervisor at Metro Infrasys. You can contact them at imtiaz.khoda@profile.ae or 321-654-9054. Skills: proxy, user account setup, transcription.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                140,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                160,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Thompson Tammy is a it etl developer at Mewar Hospital. You can contact them at das.kirloskar@kenexa.com or 1-555-123-8161. Skills: soc ii, system architectures, industrial iot.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                80,
                104,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                132,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                140,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                162,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rowson Anna is a technical retail experience manager at Aga Khan University Hosp. You can contact them at p.sanatkar@gmail.com or 159-753-4695. Skills: enterprise class storage systems and netapp filers, statistical computing, advanced report design.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                52,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                56,
                80,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                106,
                126,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                130,
                142,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                152,
                202,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                204,
                225,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                227,
                249,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ball Rachel is a vice president of data science at Sabyasachi Couture. You can contact them at razak@habtoormotors.com or 987-654-4972. Skills: assisting in lifting and placing caskets, project portfolio documentation, data warehousing methodology.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                95,
                118,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                134,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                144,
                184,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                186,
                217,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                219,
                247,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Day Ryan is a data entry specialist at Zinka Logistics Solution. You can contact them at maha.aljamal@fh.ae or 1-555-123-8775. Skills: azure or aws cloud systems, database connectivity, advanced manufacturing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                89,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                184,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                186,
                208,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Durham Ben is a marketing research analyst at Cadeploy Engineering. You can contact them at bakul.patwardhan@onmobile.com or 987-654-4700. Skills: service catalog management, information literacy, chatbots.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                92,
                121,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                137,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                175,
                195,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                197,
                205,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Painter Kim is a innovation strategist at Aasaanjobscom. You can contact them at forklift@emirates.net.ae or 159-753-8412. Skills: integration with internet of things devices, understanding of emerging digital trends, cloud infrastructure technologies.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                176,
                216,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                218,
                251,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Patel Krishna is a platform solution architect at Johns Hopkins University. You can contact them at af@sn3tech.com or 159-753-6188. Skills: enterprise data warehousing, network configuration development, online tools management.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                100,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                130,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                169,
                202,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                204,
                227,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Turner Kai is a data assistant at Affinity Express. You can contact them at tinko@emirates.net.ae or 321-654-9945. Skills: iso 27001, security logs monitoring, use case creation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                34,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                76,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                101,
                113,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                132,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                134,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                160,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Lindsay George is a information technology specialist at Lovely Professional Univ. You can contact them at hollow.awwad@gmail.com or 159-753-2900. Skills: data extraction, collaboration with architects, large datasets management.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                53,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                81,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                107,
                129,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                133,
                145,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                155,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                201,
