[
    {
        "text": "Donnell Jordan is a seasoned sr integration working at tce. Reach at consults@eim.ae Tel: +33 7696976 Experienced in zos operating, elastic cnotainer ecs, hexrays ida pro.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                55,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                69,
                84,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                90,
                101,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                117,
                130,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Shaw Leanne - performance @ reliable hubs engineerin. No contact provided. Proficient in office outlook, informix.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                108,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Simpson Abi is a seasoned lead working at ambience. Email at velmurugan@petronemirates.com Call +81 7019274807 Experienced in ilog cplex optimization studio.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                61,
                90,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                96,
                110,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                126,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tighe Shannon currently works as a deep learning devops at dada motors. Reach at kkkoshy@emirates.net.ae Call +61 41662508 Core skills include spark, application integration.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                35,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                104,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                150,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "May Ged currently works as a interactive developer at akshaya. Call +49 1519609303 Core skills include mysql, tax cmopliance tax, middleware.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                7,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                68,
                82,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                103,
                108,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                130,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Diakoumakis Pandelis - edison @ aegis associates. Email at sabjaan@aksugar.ae Tel: 159-753-7852 Proficient in project, nosql, mechanical plumbing mep design.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                53,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                64,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                115,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Summers Stephanie - associate application @ hirepro consulting. Reach at saidhmd@eim.ae Proficient in cgtech vericut cnc, shazam, requisitepro.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                22,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                78,
                92,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                125,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                133,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                135,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bennett Alice, a multimedia affiliated with university vermont, Email at masiclatm@emiratesfalcon.com Technical skills: slcak.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                27,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                73,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Knapp Edd (boiler operator at charoen pokphand) Phone number +81 9062502782 They specialize in productivity, angular.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                23,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                89,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                109,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                130,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kelly Denise is a seasoned deep learning scientist working at drishti soft. Tel: +81 80606005 Experienced in figma, central commnad.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                62,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                109,
                114,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bees Clare is a seasoned cyber security working at shree satya sai vidyalay. Email at ois@emirates.net.ae Experienced in microsystems java, openroads designer, hive.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                140,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                160,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Roberts Suzanne, a community health worker affiliated with keo international consul, No contact provided. Technical skills: mysql.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                83,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                124,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Allsopp Adam is a seasoned web working at integrated wireless solu. Call +33 6170448 Experienced in javascript object notation json, java message jms.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                73,
                84,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                100,
                131,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                133,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Holden Ned, a jr network systems from xplore, Reach at rafidtr@eim.ae Phone: 159-753-9275 Key expertise: business bi, frx.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                52,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                77,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                113,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Edwards Jordan (crop at omax autos) Email: hr@amgd.ae Tel: 1-555-123-5602 They specialize in puppet.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                28,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                30,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                57,
                67,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                73,
                87,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                107,
                113,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Render Jack, a machine learning services from eris lifesciences, email adel.abdul.ghani@philips.com Key expertise: red aht wildfly, spring framework.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                140,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Malviya Nikhil - intern @ huber suhner electronics. Reach at romit@emirates.net.ae Phone number +81 7063675072 Proficient in skm analysis tools.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                28,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                31,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                87,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                101,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Clulee Jamie currently works as a expert test at gracure pharmaceuticals. Email: surbhs@gmail.com Core skills include binar yninja.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                34,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Johnson Jaime, a retail sales affiliated with amec foster wheeler, Reach at ahsind@eim.ae Phone number +44 791173788012 Technical skills: mongodb, mobile explorer mme.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                76,
                89,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                119,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                138,
                145,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                147,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "ashwini hospital employs Palmer Susan as a environmental scientist. Phone number +33 7594604 Skills: angular, transportation tms.",
        "entities": [
            [
                25,
                37,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                43,
                66,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                16,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                92,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                101,
                108,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                128,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Irons Dean, a autonomous driving intern from tema, Reach at equipment@wotek.com Phone: +33 65873007 Key expertise: reutres westlaw, qualys cloud platform.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                57,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                68,
                87,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                95,
                107,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Murrihy Nardein G, a operation vehicle manufacturing from tvs sons, Email at michael@electradubai.ae Tel: 1-555-123-7044 Key expertise: esp sdk, sas, activex.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                66,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                128,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                144,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                153,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Walker Michelle (edison at delhi author) email cho2007@sch.ae Call +34 6111100737 They specialize in ptv vissim.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                29,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                53,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                61,
                75,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                115,
                125,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Murray Alexander, a strategy competitive analysis from galvion, Email: dubai@sovereigngroup.com Phone number +33 69640103 Key expertise: cocoa, relational database.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                24,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                57,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                63,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                103,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                145,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Lakatos Emese, a governance affiliated with raks pharma, Reach at george.titus@icalain.ae Call +44 780010136827 Technical skills: pandas.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                27,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                89,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                95,
                111,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Milano De Souza Larissa currently works as a procurement at acute informatics. Email: info@emirates-plaza.com Core skills include websphere, architect, magellan firmware.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                23,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                45,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                60,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                109,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                130,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                141,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                169,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Mohsin Pathan, a bi from magicbricks, Call +49 16071402064 Key expertise: onenote.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                27,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                44,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                51,
                66,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                82,
                89,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Mcmann Douglas, a sales enablement from diaspark infotech, Phone: +44 78007071042 Key expertise: pvsyst.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                22,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                74,
                89,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                105,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "cryoviva biotech employs Murzyn Jakub as a senior solutions. email jassim.saif@emirates.com Skills: netmeeting.",
        "entities": [
            [
                25,
                37,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                43,
                59,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                16,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                91,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Weaver Ben is a seasoned senior geophysicist working at shivalik ind. Call +1 3038312646 Experienced in red hat openshift, mcneel rhinoceros.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                56,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                88,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                104,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mcvie Megan, a machine learning technical trainer affiliated with marvel realtors, Reach at amendez@bjservices.ae Phone: +33 6817600 Technical skills: vuejs, microstation, javamin composer.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                66,
                81,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                92,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                151,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rmrs Andrea currently works as a systems vii at alphataraxia. email neale@dulsco.co.ae Core skills include facebook.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                33,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                68,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Khan Irfan currently works as a supplier qa at okaya power. Email at shierra.balcarse@fairs-exhibs.com Phone number +33 7480440 Core skills include pipeline.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                32,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                69,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                148,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sorger Jozsef currently works as a brighter at flatworld mortgage proce. Reach at ahghatwary@gmail.com Phone number +61 4366473 Core skills include facebook.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                35,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                148,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Howard Micha (shipping receiving at hdfc credila) Email: abhi@hid.ae Phone: +1 20278888836 They specialize in azure sentinel, primavera project portfolio.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                26,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                71,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                90,
                104,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                124,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                140,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Jaskevičius Darius (spark at jecrc university) Phone: +81 7012469313 They specialize in sap erp, cognos reportent.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                32,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                34,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                68,
                82,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                102,
                109,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Robinson Georgia, a assistant vice chancellor affiliated with bch electric, Email: sara.mohammadi@sama-dubai.com Technical skills: figma, red hat linux.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                62,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                112,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Palmer Sue currently works as a senior machine learning at apps associates. Email: info@waterflow.org Core skills include netezza twinfin, qradar isem, looker analytics.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                32,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "dopet employs Dunn Sara as a maria goeppert mayer fellowship. Email at keweiss@menet.net Call +61 49646275 Skills: productivity, hris, azur esentinel.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                23,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                5,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                71,
                88,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                94,
                106,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                115,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                133,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Hussain Hamzah, a webmaster from offshore infrastructures, email anna@jpinternational-uae.com Phone: +55 3113012829 Key expertise: tivoli, xerces java parser, java message jms.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                22,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                73,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                145,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                147,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Milburn Lewis (sr governance at jsw severfield structure) Phone number +55 1182473692 They specialize in puppet, web content.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                27,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                119,
                125,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "emerson innovation cente employs Ohanlon Ashleigh as a quality coordinator. Reach at ctancr@emirates.net.ae Phone number +49 17059222616 Skills: chatbot, structure dquery sql, atlassian abmboo.",
        "entities": [
            [
                33,
                49,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                55,
                74,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                24,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                136,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                145,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "jayoti vidyapeeth women employs Love Marissa as a customer services operations. Email at rajesh.babu@veoliawater.com Call +55 21841561 Skills: blackbaud raisers.",
        "entities": [
            [
                32,
                44,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                50,
                78,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                23,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                89,
                116,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                134,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Butler Ian, a magnetic sensor device from camelot integrated inc, Email at almansur@emirates.net.ae Phone: +1 6465619590 Key expertise: dynamics, silverlight.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                128,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                144,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                154,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Rozinger Szabina, a quality assurance from cms, Email at hr@tekedge.com Key expertise: active directory, cognos reportnet.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                24,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                65,
                79,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                95,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Hill Roger - senior network services @ exide. Phone: 987-654-8546 Proficient in hechsm, hardware descriptionh dl.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                49,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                70,
                "PHONE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "petron const employs Barot Dipak as a mobile master. Email at infotv@mbc.ae Call 321-654-4534 Skills: moz search engine optimization seo, iseries accses, github.",
        "entities": [
            [
                21,
                32,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                38,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                12,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                75,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                102,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                154,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Sharma Janardan - permitting associate @ arabtec construction. Email: sintl@emirates.net.ae Phone number +1 41590958717 Proficient in vuecentric mortgagedashboard, sdk, microsystems java persistence api.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                96,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                124,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                169,
                172,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                174,
                207,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Tobby Eric - network system @ ultratech cement. Email: hr@relianceidc.com Phone: +61 4908575 Proficient in compute engine gce, word, directx.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                78,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                86,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                112,
                130,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                132,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                145,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Atkin Andy (assistant chief bldg at nayara) email josen@mailme.com Phone: +33 712571671 They specialize in hadoop, mastercam computeraided design manufacturing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                24,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                64,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                101,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                121,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Wardle Callum, a account executive fraud solutions from gsec, Reach at jgale@jcdubai.sch.ae Tel: 987-654-3981 Key expertise: national instruments labview, stduio, php.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                58,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                64,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                99,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                117,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                171,
                174,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Singleton Susan (urban farmer installation team member at melstar information tech) Phone number +55 3116325566 They specialize in springshare libguides.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                29,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                68,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                72,
                96,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                111,
                125,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                145,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "brandix employs Di Monte Martina as a merchandising operations. email info@brandsco.com Skills: sourcesafe, uinx, optionvue options analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                16,
                32,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                38,
                62,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                7,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                70,
                87,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                96,
                106,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rogers Justin, a admissions affiliated with apis, Email at Adib.Farha@CROWN HEALTH SERVICES.COM Technical skills: acrobat, lotus notes, openroads designer.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                27,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                95,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                134,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mullin Anna currently works as a onsite client mobility at foodpanda. Email at czshj@emirates.net.ae Phone number +55 31033284 Core skills include payroll, internet iis, wordpress.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                33,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                126,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                170,
                179,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Harbon Chris - vp technology @ best sellers. Tel: +1 41579007524 Proficient in aix, transportation, etap.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                36,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                55,
                69,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                84,
                87,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                89,
                103,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                109,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Mckean Phil, a msbi from bp poddar hospital, Reach at malmospm@emirates.net.ae Call +55 111952900 Key expertise: structured query sql, dynamics marketing, azure.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                27,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                33,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                92,
                105,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                121,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                143,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Neville Jenni, a staff scientist from chm hill, Reach at tracktack@gmail.com Key expertise: resource access facility racf, rose xde.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                65,
                84,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Buggy Eddie, a program operations from metalsa, Email: schuylerdsouza@gmail.com Call +44 7800670082 Key expertise: magellan firmware, gcode, web browser.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                87,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                93,
                107,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                142,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Smith Dee is a seasoned patient benefits working at cosmo infrasolutions. Email at mbagshi@gmail.com Tel: +81 703506555 Experienced in hvie, hexrays ida pro.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                119,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "igi aviation employs Hewitson Lottie as a cyber security job. Phone: +1 3031788693 Skills: microsystems java servlet api, drupal, tivoli.",
        "entities": [
            [
                21,
                36,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                42,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                12,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                69,
                82,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                91,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                128,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                130,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Burns Michael currently works as a sr scientist at volvo. Email at cbrandt@pi.ac.ae Phone: +49 15174125395 Core skills include ilog.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                35,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                91,
                106,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                127,
                131,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Heath Samuel, a deployment functionality technician from ion trading, Email at hr@westcoast.ae Tel: +44 74004377161 Key expertise: analysst notebook.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                59,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                65,
                76,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                87,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Haughey Caleb - senior machine learning scientist @ cargo motors. email kkonsult.uae@eim.ae Phone: +351 9329509260 Proficient in marketo marketing automation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                96,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                119,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Chris Hargreaves Amy Hargreaves - network communication @ affinity global advertis. Phone: +1 6460673842 Proficient in numbers mac, vuecentric mortgagedashboard, marketo marketing automation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                36,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                39,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                63,
                87,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                96,
                109,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                124,
                135,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                137,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                195,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Badham Sophie currently works as a fiscal at perkinelmer. Tel: 321-654-4302 Core skills include mastercam compuetraided design manufacturing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                35,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                75,
                "PHONE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Cotterill Amy is a seasoned security working at software ag. Email at smita.kandiraju@ge.com Phone number +61 41662508 Experienced in websphere.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                70,
                92,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                118,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                143,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Azad Tahmid, a senior solutions design affiliated with landmark, Email at gbei@emirates.net.ae Phone: +81 809184903 Technical skills: office shareponit moss, esri arcgis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                55,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                74,
                94,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                158,
                169,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Bennett Alice - hr partner @ achievers spot. Email at ezaldeen@evolvence.com Proficient in sas, statacorp stata.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                34,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                81,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                96,
                99,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                101,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Abdi Ali is a seasoned desk immigration assistant working at ciel hr. Email: scholfield@pbworld.com Experienced in customer relationship, hypertext markup html.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                8,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                61,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                99,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                138,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Birks Gem, a production quality from sharda hospital, email saritake@up.ae Key expertise: android, geographic gis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                68,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                98,
                105,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Hawkins Kieran (technology sales at fiberhome) Phone: +49 16010552022 They specialize in slack, kali linux, web framework.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                28,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                30,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                68,
                83,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                103,
                108,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                135,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mcguire Conal is a seasoned microservice developer working at indian metals ferro al. Email at it@ow-group.com Phone number +55 31926967 Experienced in catia, drupal.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                62,
                84,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                95,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                136,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                152,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                159,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Kanani Shrey, a research study assistant from bader al mulla brothers, Email at avinashwadhwa@gmail.com Key expertise: bing ads, tax compliance tax.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                111,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                135,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                137,
                155,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sax Carla, a jr affiliated with sonalysts, Email: m.samaty@sharjah.ac.ae Technical skills: chatbot, informatica.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                13,
                15,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                32,
                41,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                50,
                72,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                91,
                98,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jones Carrie is a seasoned brighter working at jarvis st. Email: recruitment@blore.tcs.co.in Phone number +33 79536212 Experienced in yourkit java profiler, aspnet.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                65,
                92,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                118,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                155,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                157,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mcewan Charmaine, a crop affiliated with relevance lab, email nurol@nuroluae.com Technical skills: iphoto, frx.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                24,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                99,
                105,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Teixeira Bruno currently works as a sustainability at biophore pharmaceu. Email at alan.l@eostek.com Phone number +1 2024250384 Core skills include national instruments labview.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                36,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                148,
                176,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Scott Anna, a scientist from casagrand, Call +33 7896066 Key expertise: hris.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                46,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                53,
                64,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                80,
                84,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Donaghy Emer, a solutions designer from aparajitha corporate ser, email company@eim.ae Tel: +34 622517290 Key expertise: azure sentinel, maya nastran, redis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                80,
                94,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                113,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                129,
                143,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                145,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                159,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Whitbread Abbie currently works as a associate scientist at arcadia. Reach at hr@tawjeehmsfa.ae Core skills include slides, hyeprtext markup html.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                37,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                60,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                78,
                95,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Lowry Stephen is a seasoned ovr trainer working at jaya shree textiles. Email at alaazaky@emirates.net.ae Phone: +34 6224059728 Experienced in mathworks matlab, tensorflow, project.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                161,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                173,
                180,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "vertex homes employs Muller Andy as a inside sales territory representative. email hrwd@mmaa.gov.qa Phone: +81 900699111 Skills: workspace, operational store ods.",
        "entities": [
            [
                21,
                32,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                38,
                75,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                12,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                99,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                120,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                129,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                140,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Abbas Ali, a starts coordinator affiliated with zuri hotels resort, Email at emelnikova@n-tele.com Call +49 151074454 Technical skills: learning lms, operational store dos, applicant tarcking.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                13,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                98,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                117,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Roberts Suzanne, a admission affiliated with galfar al misnad enginee, Email at sudhakar@barakat-uae.com Call +1 6464588022 Technical skills: fraud abuse.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                28,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                80,
                104,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Burns Michael, a training content developer from intercontinental consult, email swapv84@gmail.com Key expertise: effects, basic.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                81,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                89,
                106,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Brown Agnes, a staten island lead fulfillment associate from kochartech, Email at info-uae@proxyintl.com Call +61 49286825 Key expertise: productivity.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                63,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                69,
                79,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                112,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                130,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                146,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "woodland employs Thrussell-Day Stephanie as a dps. Phone number +61 428764571 Skills: microsystems java servlet api, pms, drawberry.",
        "entities": [
            [
                17,
                40,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                46,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                8,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                64,
                77,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                86,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                131,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "mann hummel filter employs Rowe Kai as a gdia operations. Email: oindri.mandal@onmobile.com Phone number 321-654-3007 Skills: python experimental economics toolkit peet, office frontpage.",
        "entities": [
            [
                27,
                35,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                41,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                18,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                65,
                91,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                117,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                126,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                170,
                186,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "macys employs Driver Balal as a user researcher. Reach at ali@dubailaw.ae Call +351 96910796 Skills: dynamics gp, canalyzer, notes.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                26,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                32,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                5,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                73,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                79,
                92,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                101,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                125,
                130,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "tecumseh employs Hazell Martin as a supply technician. Reach at milcocup@emirates.net.ae Skills: atlassian jira, hyperterminal, bioconductor.",
        "entities": [
            [
                17,
                30,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                36,
                53,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                8,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                64,
                88,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                97,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                113,
                126,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                128,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Protovinne Zatonyi Monika currently works as a maria goeppert mayer fellowship at aswartha condition monit. Email: mmzafar@emirates.net.ae Phone: +61 4908575 Core skills include sps samos.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                47,
                78,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                82,
                106,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                115,
                138,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                146,
                157,
                "PHONE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Wallace Stephen, a market intelligence senior affiliated with whisker, Call +351 9659270844 Technical skills: database.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                62,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                76,
                91,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                110,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Hunt Jason - training content developer @ vero moda. Email at nevilleperes@gmail.com Phone number +81 707806408 Proficient in checkout, spss answertree, hirs.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                89,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                141,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Prajapati Anand (movidius deep learning scientist at comsol inc) Email at stef.dehauwere@jandenul.com Tel: +33 6350019 They specialize in mechanical plumbing mep design.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                29,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                63,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                67,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                115,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                152,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Carter Anne currently works as a vice president bi at threads. email emma@euromedia.ae Phone: +44 740071520730 Core skills include requisitepro.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                33,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                69,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                94,
                110,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                143,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mindaugas Mindaugas is a seasoned end user services working at cube construction engine. Email: transwld@emirates.net.ae Experienced in jmeter, binaryn inja.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                34,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                63,
                87,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                96,
                120,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Kennedy Debbie - product support @ cipla pharmaceutical. Email: tariqmunirbutt5@emirates.net.ae Phone number +55 1151925652 Proficient in ilog logicnet xe, iseries access.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                69,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                128,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                161,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Mclean Paddy - training @ siddheshwar. email ariel@saharaglass.com Phone number 159-753-4695 Proficient in figma, kinesis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                28,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                31,
                42,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                50,
                71,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                112,
                117,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                126,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Marsh Cassie - systems operations night shift @ weizmann forex. Phone: +351 913259917 Proficient in lniux, cognos business.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                76,
                90,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                112,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Laverick Maureen is a seasoned technical operations co working at petrojet. Reach at mohd.charaf@arabtecp.ae Phone: +44 740001275301 Experienced in axatpa, federated records, djanog.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                66,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                156,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Wheatstone Robert, a human resources assistant from leonia holistic destinat, Phone number +61 4488225 Key expertise: shazam.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                60,
                84,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                99,
                110,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                126,
                132,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Regan Chris, a desktop support affiliated with bestseller retail, Email at fawazsls@emirates.net.ae Technical skills: ruby rails, portswigger burp suite.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                99,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                128,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                130,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ewan Andrew currently works as a associate principal regulatory writer at soc experts. Reach at shaun@alcfz.com Call +33 60367422 Core skills include navisworks jetstream, kali linux, quickboosk.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                33,
                70,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                74,
                85,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                96,
                111,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                150,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                172,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hill Roger, a research study assistant affiliated with shree renuka sugars, Reach at rainbowf@emirates.net.ae Technical skills: final uct studio, disassembler, bing ads.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                55,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                109,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                146,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                160,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "suroj buildcon employs Chris Hargreaves Amy Hargreaves as a omnichannel. Reach at info@alfattan.com Tel: +55 2128445399 Skills: geographic gis, microsystems java, basicnet compact framework cf.",
        "entities": [
            [
                23,
                54,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                60,
                71,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                14,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                99,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                119,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                128,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                144,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                163,
                192,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Cullen Jack (product safety at namaste foods) Email: munzer@dmi.ae They specialize in hibernate orm, emerson firstvue value sizing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                113,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                144,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Goodrum Shane currently works as a brighter at xalta food beverages. email sanjive.khosla@tecom.ae Phone: +34 611480443 Core skills include powerpoint.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                35,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                98,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                119,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Sophia Kew-Moss Rene - social media mis reporting @ jay jay mills. Email at yogbhatt@emirates.net Proficient in project, geographic gis, office outlook.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                142,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Close Tracie - associate solutions @ xpressbees. Reach at murtuza@online-dubai.com Phone: 1-555-123-6776 Proficient in xactware xactimate, xp professional.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                52,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                87,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                95,
                109,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                124,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                144,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Cowan Cheryl - molding packer @ kohinoor speciality food. Email at alex2406@gmail.com Phone number +351 9121595848 Proficient in forsk atoll, looker analytics, ilog.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                72,
                90,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                119,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                145,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                147,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                165,
                169,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mcdermott Michael, a vmware systems affiliated with mgm medical college ho, Email at kavitha.sasi@polyclean.ae Phone number +33 794385684 Technical skills: jmeter.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                137,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                156,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Stephens Brenda currently works as a solution at cybernetik. email jobs@cnbcarabia.com Phone number +55 3127080679 Core skills include transportation, office hsarepoint moss.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                37,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                114,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Myatt Lucy is a seasoned aws iaas developer working at saraswati vidya mandir. Email: etihadpalace@etihad.ae Tel: +81 70092248 Experienced in mongodb, rose xde, vuecentric mortgagedashboard.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                55,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                126,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                151,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                161,
                189,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Demers Melohnie, a digital forensics ediscovery senior associate affiliated with mahindra tractors, Email: jshams23@gmail.com Technical skills: dynamodb, go, netmeeting.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                64,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                81,
                98,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                107,
                125,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                144,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                154,
                156,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                158,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ahmed Tahmina, a facilities systems affiliated with upl unit, Email: ceo@khoie.com Call +61 4428138 Technical skills: sourcseafe, python.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                60,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                69,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "carlson rezidor hotel gr employs Gowing Lita as a urban farmer installation team member. email info@dubai.sun.com Skills: mitre attck.",
        "entities": [
            [
                33,
                44,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                50,
                87,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                24,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                95,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                133,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Brady Michelle (full stack developers at kewal kiran clothing) email trcbrynden@ntlworld.com They specialize in nodejs, access.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                28,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                30,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                55,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                106,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                132,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                134,
                140,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Shingles Jasmine, a development itam affiliated with advance valves global, Email: info@dubaimaritimecity.ae Call +55 11338031 Technical skills: infosphere warehouse.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                126,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                145,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Richardson Sophie (learning producer at sneha farms) email mailrenis@rediffmail.com Call +81 70596184 They specialize in basicnet compact framework cf, informatica.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                31,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                33,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                73,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                166,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tonde Rahul currently works as a sr staff at rsp design consultants. Reach at mdnair@emirates.net.ae Phone: +55 21459254 Core skills include plsql.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                33,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                78,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                120,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                146,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Gillingwater Charlie, a claims principal solutions from national steel agro, Reach at julius@gipdubai.com Tel: +55 3116570597 Key expertise: safari, frx frx, clearcase.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                28,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                32,
                58,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                64,
                83,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                133,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                149,
                155,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                157,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                166,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Walker Meg (senior development at psg college technolog) email nayyer1@emirates.net.ae Phone: +81 9089667535 They specialize in java message jms.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                24,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Wootton Yvonne, a syep service learning facilitator from icrisat, Email: carly.shaw@maunsell.com Key expertise: moz search engine optmiization seo, great plains personal keeper, iseries access.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                22,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                59,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                65,
