[
    {
        "text": "Contact Teague Sharon, a family relations coord from machino plastics, email dawny@cbd.ae Phone number 1-555-123-2468 Key expertise: lotus approach.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                89,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                117,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Kamal Shannon (principle at hgs international servic) Phone: 1-555-123-5288 They specialize in eclipes ide, visual studionet, optionvue options analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                27,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                89,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                122,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                140,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kelly Denise is a seasoned claims working at broadridge sol. Call 987-654-7932 Experienced in articulate storyline, primavera enterprise project portfolio management.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                78,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                94,
                114,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Urtula Loren currently works as a real world evidence informatician at spiro. Email: cheryl.lyon@workz.ae Tel: 159-753-7114 Core skills include notes, visual basicnet.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                34,
                67,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                71,
                76,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                144,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                151,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sandle New Chloe is a seasoned dps working at st stephens hospital. Email at i.naqvi@habibbank.com Call 1-555-123-9159 Experienced in windwos, mainstage.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                98,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                104,
                118,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Ray Sk - unity developer @ scope eknowledge. Reach at mazen@agadubai.com Tel: 321-654-3755 Proficient in revit.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                32,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                77,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                83,
                95,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                110,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Hyslop Donald, a team from cremica food, Phone: 159-753-7114 Key expertise: tablaeu, active server pages asp, checkout.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                35,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                56,
                68,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                93,
                116,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                126,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ntn-Thssn Xavier is a seasoned media operations assistant working at malabar compani. Email at 200413819@uaeu.ac.ae Phone: 1-555-123-8231 Experienced in turbotax.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                57,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                69,
                84,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                95,
                115,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                137,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                153,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Tomlinson Kathy - boiler operator @ century pulp paper. Email: venu@aldesme.com Call 1-555-123-1742 Proficient in powerpoint, unreal technology unreal engine.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                68,
                84,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                90,
                104,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                119,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "arya employs Donaghy Emer as a developer integration services. Reach at colourpalette@gmail.com Skills: iseries cacess.",
        "entities": [
            [
                13,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                61,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                4,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                72,
                95,
                "EMAIL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Carpenter Josh, a store operations learning program designer affiliated with burckhardt compression, Tel: 321-654-8159 Technical skills: spss amos, office frontpage.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                77,
                99,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                106,
                118,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                146,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                148,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Hart Daniel - testing @ adani ports special. Tel: 159-753-9773 Proficient in check processing control system cpsc.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                26,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                29,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                55,
                67,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                82,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Tony (technical editor at vedang radio) Email at PK@globalboiler.cpm Tel: 159-753-2904 They specialize in customer relationshpi management crm, elastic container service ecs.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                52,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                158,
                187,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "shaze luxury retail employs Davies Sarah as a deep learning. Tel: 159-753-7114 Skills: books ngram viewre, sql developer.",
        "entities": [
            [
                28,
                40,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                46,
                59,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                19,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                78,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                107,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Gillard Sian (move coordinator at discord) email anil.singh@tradingengineers.com Phone number 1-555-123-3194 They specialize in red hat wildfly, esri arcsde.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                26,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                94,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                159,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Murzyn Jakub, a machine learning artificial intelligence senior scientist from cp aquaculture, Phone: 1-555-123-4742 Key expertise: active server pages asp, windows, sap.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                81,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                87,
                101,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                110,
                124,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                165,
                172,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                174,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "convergent communication employs Mcguire Ewan as a senior network services. Email: sales@haris.com Skills: maya.",
        "entities": [
            [
                33,
                45,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                51,
                74,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                24,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                98,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "interglobe qu employs Webster Hayley as a mobile app developer. Email: alian1@emirates.net.ae Phone number 1-555-123-8775 Skills: checkout, hercas, php.",
        "entities": [
            [
                22,
                36,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                42,
                62,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                13,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                71,
                93,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                148,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Marsh Cassie, a sr reporting visualization affiliated with arabian bemco contractin, Reach at sameer@nit.uae.net Tel: 321-654-2353 Technical skills: restful api.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                42,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                83,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                94,
                112,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                130,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                149,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Stares Elliot (application developer at acebright pharma) Email: dubai.lab@bodycote.com Phone number 159-753-8412 They specialize in windows, vue compensation management.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                27,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Robinson Georgia is a seasoned program support assistant working at instakart. Email: amalik@desconfze.ae Experienced in database, web content management system cms.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                68,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Ahmed Tahmina (research scientist at bharti hospital) Email at comatoria@gmail.com Phone number 159-753-2904 They specialize in express pcie, sheets, pipeline.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                27,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                96,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                142,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                164,
                172,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Goodrum Shane is a seasoned senior machine learning scientist working at united capital club. Email at deepak.khullar@ae.standardchartered.com Tel: 321-654-5216 Experienced in frontpage, nmap, visual studionet.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                61,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                73,
                92,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                103,
                142,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                148,
                160,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                176,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                187,
                191,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                193,
                209,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hannah Jade currently works as a artificial intelligence senior at chiripal. Tel: 1-555-123-6372 Core skills include system testing, unix, azure.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                33,
                63,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                67,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                96,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                117,
                131,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                133,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                139,
                144,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Allen Chelsea currently works as a lead systems at trident automobiles. No contact provided. Core skills include office outlook, xsan.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                35,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                51,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                113,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                133,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "aon hewitt employs Thompson Tammy as a sitecore. Reach at mahmoodi@emirates.net.ae Phone number 159-753-9849 Skills: forefront identify manager, systems management server.",
        "entities": [
            [
                19,
                33,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                39,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                10,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                96,
                108,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                117,
                143,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                145,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Lewis Melissa, a helpdesk from blue origin, Phone: 159-753-5150 Key expertise: middleware, federated records management.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                33,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                71,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                87,
                97,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                99,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "West Lucy is a seasoned development itam working at cox kings global servi. Email: narulla@emirates.net.ae Phone number 1-555-123-2468 Experienced in tivoli identity management tim.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                106,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                134,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                150,
                180,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Dean Jasmine - infotainment system test @ arya. email ammar.tawfeek@gaj-uae.ae Tel: 1-555-123-5478 Proficient in javascript.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                89,
                103,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                118,
                128,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Whitfield Toby, a trading intern affiliated with diamond cement, Reach at info@dubailand.ae Tel: 159-753-2404 Technical skills: react redux.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                32,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                74,
                91,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                97,
                109,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                128,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Richardson Sophie - risk @ ntc. email thomas.george@bmtconline.com Phone: 1-555-123-2730 Proficient in webspehre.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                22,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                32,
                35,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                43,
                71,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                79,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jairam Jagdish, a hr services affiliated with talentedge, Call 321-654-4435 Technical skills: cognos.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                75,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                94,
                100,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Joseph Obialo - technology centers @ aress software educa. Email at mmsivakumar@rediffmail.com Proficient in infosphere warehouse, access.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                73,
                99,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                134,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                136,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "modi naturals employs Gohil Kuldeepsinh as a full. Email at gl-abu.dhabi@germanlloyd.org Phone: 159-753-4340 Skills: java message service jsm, bootstrap.",
        "entities": [
            [
                22,
                39,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                45,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                13,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                88,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                96,
                108,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                152,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Robinson Kimbo is a seasoned machine learning services working at sciformix. Email at alafra@maktoob.com Experienced in ilog cplex optimization studio, peoplesoft.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                66,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                104,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                162,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Jacobs Sarah, a gas quality from thomson, Reach at 23.farid@gmail.com Phone: 321-654-3725 Key expertise: visual studionet, cisco webex.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                48,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                77,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                113,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "hill international employs Stevens Matt as a shop clerk. Email at abhijit.tradelinks@gmail.com Phone: 159-753-7431 Skills: optionvue options analysis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                27,
                39,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                45,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                18,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                94,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                114,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kennedy Debbie is a seasoned developer test working at mckesson. No contact provided. Experienced in catia.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                55,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                101,
                106,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Malik Shafiq, a test evaluation technician from jaypee hospital, Email at mrtcdxb@emirates.net.ae Phone number 987-654-1844 Key expertise: scholar, image composite editor.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                56,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                105,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                119,
                131,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Uttley Stevie, a provider program administrative from pitambari, Reach at adppoc@emirates.net.ae Tel: 159-753-3141 Key expertise: tivoli netview distribution manager, word.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                62,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                104,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                138,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                175,
                179,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Perston Robert, a developer test from applus velosi, Email at bonika.juneja@libertascapital.com Phone: 321-654-2279 Key expertise: matwhorks simulink, kniesis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                22,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                70,
                103,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                111,
                123,
                "PHONE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Burns Charlotte, a infotainment system test from uttara foods feeds, Call 321-654-4302 Key expertise: visual basic scripting edition vbscript.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                23,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                94,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                110,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Floors Doors - associate digital @ sulekhacom. email sharjah1@emirates.net.ae Phone: 159-753-6636 Proficient in cognos business intelligence.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                82,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                90,
                102,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                117,
                145,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Allsopp Adam - material handler @ spoton. Reach at c2trading@gmail.com Call 159-753-4695 Proficient in web services aws cloudformation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                17,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                20,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                45,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                56,
                75,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                108,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Lloyd Lauren (master systems principal psjh at nbcuniversal) Call 987-654-1844 They specialize in visual interdev, azure sentinel.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                26,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                57,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                61,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                80,
                92,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                112,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                143,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Chandler Chris currently works as a technical apprentice at ministry health. email dtalharoon@gmail.com Phone number 159-753-8412 Core skills include transactsql, interactive ssytem productivity facility ispf.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                36,
                56,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                60,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                103,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                150,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "blockit inc employs Ball Jake as a client executive. Reach at peter_anwander@gmx.de Call 1-555-123-1154 Skills: bootstrap, wodrpress, border gateway protocol bgp.",
        "entities": [
            [
                20,
                29,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                35,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                11,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                83,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                89,
                103,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                112,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                134,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Morgan Sophie, a senior bi from rural developme, Email at info@fairytalesdoha.com Tel: 321-654-9108 Key expertise: rational robot.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                89,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                95,
                107,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Gillingwater Charlie (bookkeeper at jayoti vidyapeeth women) Email: riyas@adwea.ae Tel: 987-654-6373 They specialize in prel, outlook, esri arcgis survey.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                34,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                36,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                96,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                114,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                140,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Pradhan Neha, a team from foxconn, Reach at thage@tabreed.com Key expertise: ansible.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                28,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                34,
                41,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                52,
                69,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                92,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "adi sports employs Turner Sian as a quality improvement. Reach at hr@medicorpqatar.com Skills: qradar siem, servicenow, mechanical electrical plumbing mep design.",
        "entities": [
            [
                19,
                30,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                36,
                55,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                10,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                95,
                106,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                161,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mannan Sameen, a sourcing affiliated with era infra, Email at sonny.karlsson@dfdstransport.se Tel: 987-654-2430 Technical skills: restful api, perforce, works.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                25,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                93,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                99,
                111,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                143,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                153,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Alexander Mathew - ad operations @ home first compa. email gulpec@emirates.net.ae Tel: 987-654-3449 Proficient in translate client, forefronti dentify manager, henry schein dentrix.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                64,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                92,
                104,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                119,
                135,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                165,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Whittaker Jackie (jr deployment at futuresoft) Call 987-654-4700 They specialize in check processing control system cpsc.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                30,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                32,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                78,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                98,
                134,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Desai Bhupen, a hr services affiliated with pride purple, No contact provided. Technical skills: websphere, activesync, video editing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                27,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                97,
                106,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                133,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Patel Deep - control desk spec @ smart ims. Phone: 1-555-123-2468 Proficient in sas, infosphere warehouse.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                18,
                35,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                56,
                70,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                85,
                88,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                90,
                110,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Desai Bhupen is a seasoned mobile technology working at pps international. Reach at shainu@rbkme.co.ae Phone number 987-654-2036 Experienced in gcode, bootstrap, vector canalyzer.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                56,
                73,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                84,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                128,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                144,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                151,
                160,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                162,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Yeman Liam (communication change management at eben) Email: b.raghavan@whitbybird.ae Phone number 1-555-123-2475 They specialize in business applications.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                24,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                57,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                61,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                74,
                98,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                112,
                126,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                146,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "nitco employs Jim Wee as a technical retail experience. Email: kate.goh@dubaifestivalcity.com Call 159-753-5150 Skills: hris.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                5,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                63,
                93,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                99,
                111,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                120,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Donofrio Elisha is a seasoned sr full stack developer working at thermax. Email at shoenet@emirates.net.ae Experienced in terraform, spss amos, student information systems sis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                30,
                53,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                65,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                106,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                122,
                131,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                133,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                144,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "sbi insurance employs Ga Claudio as a lead fulfillment associate. email netcom@emirates.net.ae Skills: books ngram viewer, imovie, visio.",
        "entities": [
            [
                22,
                32,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                38,
                64,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                13,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                72,
                94,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                121,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                131,
                136,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Simmonds Caleb (edison at jecrc university) Reach at hrd@emrfm.com Phone: 321-654-5444 They specialize in esri arcgis survey.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                28,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                30,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                67,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                100,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                120,
                138,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Roberts Suzanne, a usda commodities from avra laboratories, email julian.skyrme@adspa.ae Phone number 159-753-1731 Key expertise: rust programming language, sun microsystems java srevlet api.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                23,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                43,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                74,
                96,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                110,
                122,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                138,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Parry Olivia currently works as a scada at saudi oger. Call 1-555-123-2468 Core skills include altassian bamboo, revit.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                34,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                53,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                74,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                113,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Webster Hayley is a seasoned service working at damac properties. Email at ismarine@eim.ae Call 321-654-9054 Experienced in red hat wildfly.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                48,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                90,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                96,
                108,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                124,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Wasilewski Jarosław - senior level @ secure value. email nourg@sahm.ae Tel: 987-654-5177 Proficient in ruby rails, frx frx.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                24,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                75,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                108,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mckenna Scott, a aws devops affiliated with madras radiators pre, No contact provided. Technical skills: visual basic appilcations vba, sun microsystems java persistence api, system testing.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                27,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                136,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                175,
                189,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hart Daniel, a testing affiliated with western railway, Phone number 159-753-1011 Technical skills: ilog, revit, soliidty.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                22,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                54,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                69,
                81,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                100,
                104,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                106,
                111,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Siwak Magda - aftermarket senior @ vcare call. No contact provided. Proficient in informix, pvsyst, virtual srever.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                40,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                87,
                95,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                97,
                103,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "orient craft employs Harrison-Derbyshire Brooklynn as a material handler. Email at indiravergis@rediffmail.com Phone number 1-555-123-2404 Skills: onfolio, solidity, psvyst.",
        "entities": [
            [
                21,
                50,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                56,
                72,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                12,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                138,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                147,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                156,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet O Londraigh Mattiu - chehalis @ jobby. Email: jacob@admasco.ae Call 987-654-2970 Proficient in red hta wildfly.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                23,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                37,
                42,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                51,
                67,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                73,
                85,
                "PHONE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Gray Matthew is a seasoned deskside support technician job working at rg. Reach at DXBHR-Recruitment@aramex.com Tel: 987-654-1844 Experienced in frontpage.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                58,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                70,
                72,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                111,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                129,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                145,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Baxter Barry, a rma associate return merchandise authorization from robinsons cargo logi, Reach at nrammal@partnerandpartner.ae Phone number 987-654-4385 Key expertise: exchange, cognos.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                70,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                76,
                96,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                107,
                135,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                161,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                177,
                185,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                187,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Robinson Kimbo currently works as a associate solution at aig. Reach at rany@saderediteurs.com Tel: 987-654-4053 Core skills include mcneel rhinoceros, high level shader language hlsl.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                36,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                58,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                72,
                94,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                112,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                150,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                152,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Skelton Jasmine - senior cyber security @ dr agarwals eye hospit. Email at vivek.kale@bentley.nl Proficient in bioconductor.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                23,
                44,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                80,
                101,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                116,
                128,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Peek Sabrina, a network system from cdm smith, No contact provided. Key expertise: fraud abuse management system.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                44,
                53,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                91,
                120,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mckinnon Julie currently works as a corporate development associate at shivam autozone. Email: jobs@cityservices.ae Call 1-555-123-3513 Core skills include mongodb, unreal technology unreal engine, qradar siem.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                36,
                67,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                71,
                86,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                95,
                115,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                121,
                135,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                156,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                165,
                196,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                198,
                209,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Desai Bhupen is a seasoned computer support technician working at scaleneworks. Email: baltco@emirates.net.ae Phone number 159-753-9907 Experienced in dynamodb.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                54,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                66,
                78,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                87,
                109,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                123,
                135,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                151,
                159,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Westrip Jacy, a inside sales territory representative from hotel ramada, Email: recruitment.group@gdi.com.qa Phone: 159-753-9275 Key expertise: creative cloud.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                61,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                67,
                79,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                88,
                116,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                136,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                152,
                166,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Robinson Frank currently works as a technical lead at keya foods international. Email at r.barloso@bnengineers.com Tel: 1-555-123-2730 Core skills include vuecentric mortgagedashboard.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                36,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                78,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                89,
                114,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                134,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                155,
                183,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Smith Stacie is a seasoned communications training program lead working at simpolo vitrified. Call 321-654-5662 Experienced in python tools visual studio ptvs, web content management system cms, thomson reuters westlaw.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                63,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                75,
                92,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                99,
                111,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                127,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                160,
                193,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                195,
                218,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Joinery Lawrenson, a technical sourcer from xavient, Email at bharat.bhatia@conares.com Phone number 159-753-9773 Key expertise: tax compliance property tax management, slack, statacrop stata.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                70,
                95,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                137,
                175,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                177,
                182,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Metcalfe Alice (rvp sales at arvind fashions) Reach at sijithdas@gmail.com Phone number 1-555-123-7044 They specialize in interactive system productivity facility ispf, web services aws.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                28,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                30,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                69,
                88,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                116,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                181,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                183,
                199,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "eastman exports global employs Stubbs Aaron as a open positions national immigrant justice center. Email: lesnt@eim.ae Tel: 159-753-9609 Skills: sun microysstems java.",
        "entities": [
            [
                31,
                43,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                49,
                97,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                22,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                106,
                118,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                136,
                "PHONE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Vaswani Suresh currently works as a geospatial at pearvisa immigration ser. Reach at aysha.shamsi@uaeu.ac.ae Tel: 1-555-123-5285 Core skills include javamin composer, powershell.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                36,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                85,
                108,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                128,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                149,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                177,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Howard Micha, a graduate admissions records evaluator from technico, Phone number 159-753-9609 Key expertise: qradar isem, quickbooks, websphere mq.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                61,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                67,
                75,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                102,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                143,
                155,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Tyson Darryl, a library assistant from ledure lighting, email mcibik@teledyne.com Phone: 321-654-7786 Key expertise: netmeeting.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                70,
                89,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                97,
                109,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                125,
                135,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Glass John-James is a seasoned automation working at arshiya international. Email: cashmere@emirates.net.ae Phone: 159-753-2847 Experienced in resource access control facility racf, acrobat.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                83,
                107,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                127,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                143,
                180,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                182,
                189,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Barakat Sultz (associate product at arcop associates) No contact provided. They specialize in springshaer libguides.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                27,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet King Stephenrichard - sales marketing intern @ thyssenkrupp. Email at resume@delphi.com Proficient in iwork, bootstrap.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                24,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                49,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                52,
                64,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                92,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                107,
                112,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                114,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Azad Tahmid - system sfo @ forbes marshall. email udfact@emirates.net.ae Phone: 987-654-3352 Proficient in sap concur, figma.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                32,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                55,
                77,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                97,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                112,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                124,
                129,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Rowson Anna - network performance @ haldex. Tel: 987-654-6707 Proficient in semrush, safari, inventory control system.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                47,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                54,
                66,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                81,
                88,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                90,
                96,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                98,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Driver Balal, a vehicle diagnostics tool test from opportunity consulta, Email at mohanad.nahas@db.com Phone: 1-555-123-3513 Key expertise: business intelligence bi.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                20,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                24,
                53,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                79,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                90,
                110,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                118,
                132,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                148,
                172,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Christodoulou Felicity, a movidius deep learning scientist affiliated with rinder, Reach at field@qatar.tamu.edu Phone number 321-654-6340 Technical skills: kinesis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                22,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                58,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                75,
                81,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                92,
                112,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                126,
                138,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                157,
                164,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "James Neil, a ux designer affiliated with boston childrens hospital, email info@alsagareng.com Phone: 987-654-4951 Technical skills: aspnet.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                10,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                14,
                25,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                94,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                102,
                114,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                133,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "cisco employs Stewart Mark as a digital solution. Email at sideeque@broadandqatar.com Skills: gcode, rational doors, catia.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                26,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                32,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                5,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                94,
                99,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                101,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                122,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Smith Courtneyy, a general affiliated with rajiv gandhi mahila vika, email fredelyn@picodubai.com Tel: 159-753-7895 Technical skills: numbers mac, onfolio.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                26,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                67,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                134,
                145,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                147,
                154,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Eld Tom, a developer ray optics from rajasthan antibiotics, Email at jwhitehead@etihad.ae Call 159-753-8993 Key expertise: guidance encase enteprrise, office, sa perp.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                66,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                77,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                159,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Harris Dean is a seasoned remote help desk tech working at lemon tree hotels. Email at r.antony@osrammiddleeast.com Phone number 159-753-2463 Experienced in visual, db.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                26,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                76,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                87,
                115,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                129,
                141,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                157,
                163,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                165,
                167,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tyrrell Pauly is a seasoned hr working at itc hotels. email info@danwayindustries.com Phone: 1-555-123-5285 Experienced in web services aws sagemaker.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                28,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                42,
                52,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                60,
                85,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                93,
                107,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mills Rhonda is a seasoned quality technologist working at radisson hotels. email icebergmedia@dubaimediacity.net Phone number 987-654-4385 Experienced in accounting, web browser, elastic compute cloud ec.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                47,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                59,
                74,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                82,
                113,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                127,
                139,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                155,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                167,
                178,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                180,
                204,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mclean Paddy currently works as a social media mis reporting at ubs cognizant. Phone: 159-753-1011 Core skills include portswigger burp suite.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                34,
                60,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                64,
                77,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                86,
                98,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                119,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Polley Zak, a intrusion detection system from syncom healthcare, email g4sresumes@gmail.com Key expertise: ansys simulation, project management, digital analytics.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                71,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                99,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                115,
                131,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                133,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                153,
                170,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bell Deborah is a seasoned cmms working at edenred. email mikdad@westernfurniture-uae.com Tel: 159-753-5911 Experienced in content management systems cms, web content management system cms.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                31,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                58,
                89,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                95,
                107,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                153,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                155,
                188,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Brennan Clair, a end from syncom formulations indi, Phone number 321-654-5444 Key expertise: rust programming language.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                21,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                25,
                28,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                34,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                73,
                85,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                101,
                126,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Wootton Yvonne - growth scientist @ almoayyed contracting gr. Email at z.logistics@flagtelecom.com Tel: 159-753-9609 Proficient in skm systems analysis power tools.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                38,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                41,
                65,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                76,
                103,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                109,
                121,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                136,
                168,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Goff Dani currently works as a internal audit at mw high tech projects. Email at sendcvdxb@gmail.com Phone: 159-753-7852 Core skills include audition, phootshop, publisher.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                9,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                31,
                45,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                49,
                70,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                81,
                100,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                120,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                141,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                162,
                171,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Patel Maulik currently works as a baker helper at makrocare. Reach at ray.shaw@petrofac.com Tel: 987-654-5961 Core skills include apache subversion svn, team foundatoin server, servicenwo.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                34,
                46,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                50,
                59,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                70,
                91,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                97,
                109,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                130,
                151,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dhengale Pramod, a strategy operations associate affiliated with npcc, Email: haiderco@emirates.net.ae Tel: 321-654-2923 Technical skills: director, cognos reportnet.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                15,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                65,
                69,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                78,
                102,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                108,
                120,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                139,
                147,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                149,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Regan Pete, a quality hopkins from nsh corp, email barbara.thompson@almasa.com Phone number 1-555-123-6097 Key expertise: great plains presonal keeper, apache jmeter.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                37,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                51,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                59,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                114,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                160,
                173,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bagworth Laura is a seasoned baker helper working at foods inns. Email: careers@memarketing.ae Call 987-654-4996 Experienced in kinesis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                29,
                41,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                53,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                72,
                94,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                100,
                112,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                128,
                135,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "satyam auto components employs Lakatos Emese as a acquisition security. email aikram@acron.bz Call 159-753-3141 Skills: fraud abuse management system, clodu.",
        "entities": [
            [
                31,
                44,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                50,
                70,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                22,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                78,
                93,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                99,
                111,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                120,
                149,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Everton Brooke currently works as a managing delivery at thomas cook. Tel: 321-654-3580 Core skills include onenote, postman.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                14,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                36,
                53,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                57,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                87,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                108,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                117,
                124,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Binns Shirl (backend at svatantra microfin) Email: betai@betag.com Phone: 1-555-123-2730 They specialize in extensible application markup language xaml.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                38,
                56,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                65,
                80,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                88,
                102,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                122,
                165,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Hunt Jason, a senior management from jumbo finvest, email mnpfzco@emirates.net.ae Call 159-753-4559 Key expertise: windows preinstallation environment.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                39,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                45,
                58,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                66,
                89,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                95,
                107,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                123,
                158,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Thomas Harold - technical recruiter @ ferromatik milacron. Reach at vrenihofer@muro.ch Phone number 159-753-8715 Proficient in costimater.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                62,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                73,
                91,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                117,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                132,
                142,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Minter Freddie - junior quantitative researcher @ novelerp. email ndamudi@gmail.com Tel: 159-753-9006 Proficient in inevntor, rational functional tester, rational.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                19,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                22,
                52,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                55,
                63,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                71,
                88,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                94,
                106,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                131,
                157,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "bank york mel employs Murzyn Jakub as a wafer metrology development. email mk.agate@gmail.com Tel: 321-654-4302 Skills: hechms, vue beneftis manager, mechanical electrical plumbing mep design.",
        "entities": [
            [
                22,
                34,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                40,
                67,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                13,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                75,
                93,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                99,
                111,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                120,
                126,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                150,
                191,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mortiboy Ben, a hbo continuity affiliated with rao, No contact provided. Technical skills: jenikns ci, visual basicnet compact framework cf, verilog.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                12,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                16,
                30,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                47,
                50,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                103,
                139,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                141,
                148,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Johnson Nigel, a statistician affiliated with rockman, Email: amartcme@emirates.net.ae Technical skills: iwork numbers, single signon sso.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                13,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                17,
                29,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                46,
                53,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                86,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                105,
                118,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                120,
                137,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Birkett Sarah - senior security @ eclerx. Email: info@astf.net Phone number 159-753-6631 Proficient in webmaster tools.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                18,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                21,
                36,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                39,
                45,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                54,
                67,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                81,
                93,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                108,
                123,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach Brett James (environmental scientist at deepak nitrite) Email at medical@ssb.gov.qa Tel: 321-654-1908 They specialize in primavera enterprise project portfolio management, ltous.",
        "entities": [
            [
                14,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                50,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                68,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                79,
                97,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                103,
                115,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                135,
                184,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Contact Mctaggart Karen, a innovation strategist from crystal, Tel: 159-753-5911 Key expertise: student information systems sis.",
        "entities": [
            [
                8,
                23,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                27,
                48,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                54,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                68,
                80,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                96,
                127,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "saburi tlc employs Shingles Jasmine as a geospatial. Email at raghu@mezonss.com Call 1-555-123-9835 Skills: activex, iwork pagse, applescript.",
        "entities": [
            [
                19,
                35,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                41,
                51,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                0,
                10,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                79,
                "EMAIL"
            ],
            [
                85,
                99,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                108,
                115,
                "SKILL"
            ],
            [
                130,
                141,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meet Bower Sarah - associate application @ accurate cor. Tel: 159-753-6636 Proficient in outage management sysetm oms, analytics.",
        "entities": [
            [
                5,
                16,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                19,
                40,
                "JOB_TITLE"
            ],
            [
                43,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                62,
                74,
                "PHONE"
            ],
            [
                119,
                128,
                "SKILL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Cleo Kyesha, a visiting researcher affiliated with wise, Email at rajesh@sarauae.ae Technical skills: cognos planning.",
        "entities": [
            [
                0,
                11,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                15,
                34,
                "JOB_TITLE"
